[
  {
    "id": 1,
    "uuid": "15d28dbe-f581-454b-b9e4-be5ef447778e",
    "topic": "biology",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.042163",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 8,
    "question": "What is the powerhouse of the cell?",
    "options": [
      "Nucleus",
      "Mitochondria",
      "Ribosome",
      "Chloroplast"
    ],
    "answer": "Mitochondria"
  },
  {
    "id": 3,
    "uuid": "fdbfeab7-1bf6-4ae0-89e7-938608ed8146",
    "topic": "operations",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.042435",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 2,
    "question": "What is 42 + 39?",
    "options": [
      "81",
      "78",
      "72",
      "79"
    ],
    "answer": "81"
  },
  {
    "id": 4,
    "uuid": "53a55c7a-a69e-4cab-87b8-caff279aa943",
    "topic": "countries",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.042591",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 4,
    "question": "Which country has the capital city 'Tokyo'?",
    "options": [
      "China",
      "South Korea",
      "Japan",
      "Thailand"
    ],
    "answer": "Japan"
  },
  {
    "id": 5,
    "uuid": "268a24c3-c782-4973-a1d1-260341d1e11e",
    "topic": "problem solving",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.042909",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 7,
    "question": "If 5 pencils cost $10, how much do 8 pencils cost?",
    "options": [
      "12",
      "16",
      "18",
      "20"
    ],
    "answer": "16"
  },
  {
    "id": 6,
    "uuid": "554df23e-c83b-4989-ace5-92e6185a3b43",
    "topic": "operations",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.043035",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 6,
    "question": "What is 26 \u00d7 17?",
    "options": [
      "439",
      "441",
      "442",
      "434"
    ],
    "answer": "442"
  },
  {
    "id": 7,
    "uuid": "7a26a304-308d-434b-b298-fbe5d6a74c57",
    "topic": "spelling",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.043051",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 8,
    "question": "Which is the correct spelling?",
    "options": [
      "accommodate",
      "accomadate",
      "acommodate",
      "accomodate"
    ],
    "answer": "accommodate"
  },
  {
    "id": 10,
    "uuid": "4bc8e546-f58c-4589-9bbd-fcdc13c06ab0",
    "topic": "grammar",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.043082",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 9,
    "question": "Which is correct: ___ going to the park tomorrow?",
    "options": [
      "there",
      "their",
      "they're"
    ],
    "answer": "they're"
  },
  {
    "id": 12,
    "uuid": "55c1cbd9-da0d-4685-afe3-331d14793eea",
    "topic": "operations",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.043106",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 5,
    "question": "What is 49 - 4?",
    "options": [
      "49",
      "39",
      "55",
      "45"
    ],
    "answer": "45"
  },
  {
    "id": 15,
    "uuid": "16b3f445-8f35-4511-8450-a354717eed23",
    "topic": "fractions",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.043176",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 5,
    "question": "Simplify: 7/7 + 8/9",
    "options": [
      "15/9",
      "20/9",
      "17/9",
      "19/9"
    ],
    "answer": "17/9"
  },
  {
    "id": 16,
    "uuid": "7a9a6f75-01b7-451a-baa9-fd9242c0187d",
    "topic": "geometry",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.043184",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 7,
    "question": "What is the sum of interior angles of a triangle?",
    "options": [
      "90",
      "180",
      "270",
      "360"
    ],
    "answer": "180"
  },
  {
    "id": 19,
    "uuid": "eca16ba1-f0a9-4eb1-9dfb-555463446f1b",
    "topic": "operations",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.043237",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "question": "What is 36 - 42?",
    "options": [
      "-14",
      "-6",
      "-10",
      "-2"
    ],
    "answer": "-6"
  },
  {
    "id": 25,
    "uuid": "c29054dd-39fe-4392-a4f4-5895799b7bce",
    "topic": "trigonometry",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.043286",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 4,
    "question": "What is sin(45\u00b0)?",
    "options": [
      "\u221a2/2",
      "1/2",
      "0",
      "1",
      "\u221a3/2"
    ],
    "answer": "\u221a2/2"
  },
  {
    "id": 26,
    "uuid": "9aa766ed-92b0-4106-aa8c-9c8cfb06c684",
    "topic": "geometry",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.043297",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 4,
    "question": "How many sides does a square have?",
    "options": [
      "3",
      "4",
      "5",
      "6"
    ],
    "answer": "4"
  },
  {
    "id": 30,
    "uuid": "f92fc159-6bb8-4ad9-97e8-cac8877f39d1",
    "topic": "operations",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.043334",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 9,
    "question": "What is 31 \u00d7 9?",
    "options": [
      "281",
      "282",
      "279",
      "275"
    ],
    "answer": "279"
  },
  {
    "id": 31,
    "uuid": "37919e43-e4db-4009-a4d9-c11044ae3af7",
    "topic": "operations",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.043347",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 9,
    "question": "What is 4 - 22?",
    "options": [
      "-17",
      "-13",
      "-9",
      "-18"
    ],
    "answer": "-18"
  },
  {
    "id": 34,
    "uuid": "94550948-270a-49f9-b8da-d578cfff83a0",
    "topic": "fractions",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.043403",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 3,
    "question": "Simplify: 5/4 + 9/9",
    "options": [
      "9/4",
      "8/4",
      "6/4",
      "7/4"
    ],
    "answer": "9/4"
  },
  {
    "id": 35,
    "uuid": "ce3af15d-ff0f-444c-9541-40c45c3171a2",
    "topic": "trigonometry",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.043414",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 5,
    "question": "What is sin(0\u00b0)?",
    "options": [
      "1",
      "1/2",
      "\u221a3/2",
      "0",
      "\u221a2/2"
    ],
    "answer": "0"
  },
  {
    "id": 38,
    "uuid": "d7909b57-dba6-48fe-a5da-c5a5269ed384",
    "topic": "fractions",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.043495",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 7,
    "question": "Simplify: 6/9 + 3/9",
    "options": [
      "1/1",
      "0/1",
      "-1/1",
      "-2/1"
    ],
    "answer": "1/1"
  },
  {
    "id": 45,
    "uuid": "a462f65c-a8c7-4742-8f08-ac9441df577e",
    "topic": "geometry",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.043549",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "question": "What is the formula for the area of a circle?",
    "options": [
      "2\u03c0r",
      "\u03c0r^2",
      "\u03c0d",
      "r^2"
    ],
    "answer": "\u03c0r^2"
  },
  {
    "id": 47,
    "uuid": "885d2fce-20a6-44fd-9725-02df308364a4",
    "topic": "fractions",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.043586",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 7,
    "question": "Simplify: 7/3 + 4/9",
    "options": [
      "22/9",
      "24/9",
      "27/9",
      "25/9"
    ],
    "answer": "25/9"
  },
  {
    "id": 52,
    "uuid": "1cd949f6-dfee-4d76-b92c-81af34651a83",
    "topic": "operations",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.043628",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 6,
    "question": "What is 22 \u00f7 11 (integer division)?",
    "options": [
      "-2",
      "10",
      "-4",
      "2"
    ],
    "answer": "2"
  },
  {
    "id": 53,
    "uuid": "38dc31bf-8cee-408f-a253-2e1567fea5bd",
    "topic": "operations",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.043644",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "question": "What is 48 \u00f7 3 (integer division)?",
    "options": [
      "14",
      "16",
      "11",
      "18"
    ],
    "answer": "16"
  },
  {
    "id": 56,
    "uuid": "516a7db4-d747-4c38-8168-9ea4a2ee040b",
    "topic": "trigonometry",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.043672",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 6,
    "question": "What is sin(60\u00b0)?",
    "options": [
      "1/2",
      "0",
      "1",
      "\u221a2/2",
      "\u221a3/2"
    ],
    "answer": "\u221a3/2"
  },
  {
    "id": 61,
    "uuid": "fa53ed23-b9d9-45b9-b038-1dc996cb85de",
    "topic": "fractions",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.043739",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 8,
    "question": "Simplify: 7/8 + 2/2",
    "options": [
      "17/8",
      "15/8",
      "14/8",
      "16/8"
    ],
    "answer": "15/8"
  },
  {
    "id": 65,
    "uuid": "343e934b-1560-497b-bec3-152ad24845af",
    "topic": "fractions",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.043794",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 9,
    "question": "Simplify: 3/6 + 4/8",
    "options": [
      "0/1",
      "2/1",
      "-2/1",
      "1/1"
    ],
    "answer": "1/1"
  },
  {
    "id": 69,
    "uuid": "993b113e-89eb-4f8a-895b-e7ec4768d043",
    "topic": "fractions",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.043848",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 10,
    "question": "Simplify: 7/2 + 2/8",
    "options": [
      "15/4",
      "17/4",
      "14/4",
      "16/4"
    ],
    "answer": "15/4"
  },
  {
    "id": 72,
    "uuid": "f3bf2879-225a-47da-8686-c10a2ef5e9f5",
    "topic": "operations",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.043880",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 7,
    "question": "What is 11 \u00f7 15 (integer division)?",
    "options": [
      "0",
      "2",
      "5",
      "9"
    ],
    "answer": "0"
  },
  {
    "id": 74,
    "uuid": "f236b5bf-b7c5-4b02-bba5-c7ad6fbfa877",
    "topic": "operations",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.043901",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 7,
    "question": "What is 45 + 13?",
    "options": [
      "68",
      "58",
      "63",
      "54"
    ],
    "answer": "58"
  },
  {
    "id": 87,
    "uuid": "81bc89f2-6be6-4527-933b-391da5a0d8c7",
    "topic": "operations",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.043998",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 8,
    "question": "What is 34 \u00f7 19 (integer division)?",
    "options": [
      "-7",
      "1",
      "8",
      "-1"
    ],
    "answer": "1"
  },
  {
    "id": 98,
    "uuid": "76937994-483d-486d-a6d8-5397a73b0afb",
    "topic": "fractions",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.044100",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "question": "Simplify: 4/4 + 8/3",
    "options": [
      "9/3",
      "11/3",
      "10/3",
      "14/3"
    ],
    "answer": "11/3"
  },
  {
    "id": 101,
    "uuid": "bf837b6c-1c64-45b2-85b3-035a98d9e8cc",
    "topic": "fractions",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.044142",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 8,
    "question": "Simplify: 9/2 + 2/7",
    "options": [
      "64/14",
      "65/14",
      "68/14",
      "67/14"
    ],
    "answer": "67/14"
  },
  {
    "id": 106,
    "uuid": "7317a594-72f8-41db-956f-baebb929abc4",
    "topic": "operations",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.044196",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 8,
    "question": "What is 33 - 7?",
    "options": [
      "22",
      "36",
      "26",
      "19"
    ],
    "answer": "26"
  },
  {
    "id": 109,
    "uuid": "80d15684-8dba-4f96-8b09-1df2af60f8e0",
    "topic": "fractions",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.044237",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 9,
    "question": "Simplify: 2/5 + 8/8",
    "options": [
      "7/5",
      "4/5",
      "10/5",
      "5/5"
    ],
    "answer": "7/5"
  },
  {
    "id": 110,
    "uuid": "c9942698-a6b6-4edc-8b11-47a5167ed46e",
    "topic": "fractions",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.044266",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 4,
    "question": "Simplify: 2/6 + 6/8",
    "options": [
      "13/12",
      "11/12",
      "15/12",
      "12/12"
    ],
    "answer": "13/12"
  },
  {
    "id": 111,
    "uuid": "811d42ed-09b4-45d0-b5a7-43d69c9b54fa",
    "topic": "fractions",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.044309",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 3,
    "question": "Simplify: 7/8 + 7/9",
    "options": [
      "121/72",
      "122/72",
      "119/72",
      "120/72"
    ],
    "answer": "119/72"
  },
  {
    "id": 112,
    "uuid": "245ae3fd-4f29-4be4-82f9-b7ab7f259009",
    "topic": "operations",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.044332",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "question": "What is 46 + 34?",
    "options": [
      "82",
      "72",
      "80",
      "75"
    ],
    "answer": "80"
  },
  {
    "id": 113,
    "uuid": "5ec0088d-fce5-4c0a-afda-23aa77524835",
    "topic": "fractions",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.044367",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 6,
    "question": "Simplify: 1/6 + 7/8",
    "options": [
      "25/24",
      "27/24",
      "28/24",
      "26/24"
    ],
    "answer": "25/24"
  },
  {
    "id": 114,
    "uuid": "26178820-b707-4e6c-bcf5-fd5536a7dd38",
    "topic": "operations",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.044380",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 6,
    "question": "What is 18 - 34?",
    "options": [
      "-16",
      "-6",
      "-12",
      "-14"
    ],
    "answer": "-16"
  },
  {
    "id": 120,
    "uuid": "64bf1385-4366-41cc-b3c6-52b4bafb54a7",
    "topic": "operations",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.044440",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 6,
    "question": "What is 2 \u00d7 35?",
    "options": [
      "67",
      "73",
      "69",
      "70"
    ],
    "answer": "70"
  },
  {
    "id": 121,
    "uuid": "e3870208-a13f-4325-9de9-ceb7458b5546",
    "topic": "trigonometry",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.044453",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 8,
    "question": "What is sin(90\u00b0)?",
    "options": [
      "1/2",
      "1",
      "\u221a3/2",
      "0",
      "\u221a2/2"
    ],
    "answer": "1"
  },
  {
    "id": 139,
    "uuid": "37d96942-1a5b-4d94-a586-b90a630c9ccb",
    "topic": "operations",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.044619",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 10,
    "question": "What is 48 \u00d7 11?",
    "options": [
      "537",
      "521",
      "531",
      "528"
    ],
    "answer": "528"
  },
  {
    "id": 150,
    "uuid": "b21885f3-d67b-413b-9c33-c9a8e1bdb0da",
    "topic": "fractions",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.044723",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 5,
    "question": "Simplify: 6/3 + 7/8",
    "options": [
      "24/8",
      "21/8",
      "22/8",
      "23/8"
    ],
    "answer": "23/8"
  },
  {
    "id": 155,
    "uuid": "9c1fcbb3-2707-44a3-8b18-f5d5165c5264",
    "topic": "operations",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.044765",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 2,
    "question": "What is 8 - 43?",
    "options": [
      "-35",
      "-39",
      "-37",
      "-45"
    ],
    "answer": "-35"
  },
  {
    "id": 158,
    "uuid": "7800052d-8478-4577-8c93-7b03053881f4",
    "topic": "operations",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.044789",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 2,
    "question": "What is 32 \u00d7 2?",
    "options": [
      "64",
      "54",
      "67",
      "59"
    ],
    "answer": "64"
  },
  {
    "id": 160,
    "uuid": "1f382a18-2c7c-45ba-8494-d1534727f79e",
    "topic": "fractions",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.044826",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 3,
    "question": "Simplify: 3/6 + 2/4",
    "options": [
      "-1/1",
      "0/1",
      "3/1",
      "1/1"
    ],
    "answer": "1/1"
  },
  {
    "id": 161,
    "uuid": "8ddf0d17-1793-4762-b4bf-37379d99f1d7",
    "topic": "operations",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.044839",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 7,
    "question": "What is 46 \u00d7 4?",
    "options": [
      "184",
      "177",
      "186",
      "178"
    ],
    "answer": "184"
  },
  {
    "id": 168,
    "uuid": "6d076182-9b95-4dc2-9d2e-a7e2ba141fa8",
    "topic": "operations",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.044894",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 8,
    "question": "What is 18 + 36?",
    "options": [
      "54",
      "61",
      "64",
      "51"
    ],
    "answer": "54"
  },
  {
    "id": 171,
    "uuid": "769be69a-d08a-498d-9183-981fb567d865",
    "topic": "fractions",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.044944",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "question": "Simplify: 4/8 + 9/9",
    "options": [
      "0/2",
      "3/2",
      "4/2",
      "6/2"
    ],
    "answer": "3/2"
  },
  {
    "id": 172,
    "uuid": "8a84b0b3-5fd9-4b84-b874-5e3a80657ee9",
    "topic": "operations",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.044956",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "question": "What is 31 \u00d7 18?",
    "options": [
      "558",
      "568",
      "559",
      "560"
    ],
    "answer": "558"
  },
  {
    "id": 173,
    "uuid": "164407fe-b26f-4a29-a31a-b58ba8815b9b",
    "topic": "fractions",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.044980",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 7,
    "question": "Simplify: 9/3 + 5/3",
    "options": [
      "14/3",
      "17/3",
      "11/3",
      "16/3"
    ],
    "answer": "14/3"
  },
  {
    "id": 179,
    "uuid": "f631fd71-644b-499d-8620-5b3a04f07a2d",
    "topic": "fractions",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.045057",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 2,
    "question": "Simplify: 1/9 + 1/2",
    "options": [
      "9/18",
      "11/18",
      "13/18",
      "12/18"
    ],
    "answer": "11/18"
  },
  {
    "id": 184,
    "uuid": "d3311d13-e8d9-4935-9974-a04b92f45ba1",
    "topic": "fractions",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.045113",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 4,
    "question": "Simplify: 1/3 + 8/7",
    "options": [
      "33/21",
      "28/21",
      "29/21",
      "31/21"
    ],
    "answer": "31/21"
  },
  {
    "id": 187,
    "uuid": "b1374d69-3764-4c05-90c3-3ee94e595d94",
    "topic": "operations",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.045141",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 10,
    "question": "What is 18 - 32?",
    "options": [
      "-18",
      "-24",
      "-14",
      "-4"
    ],
    "answer": "-14"
  },
  {
    "id": 189,
    "uuid": "5b04e472-e83d-470b-868d-cc425c6fdf0a",
    "topic": "fractions",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.045163",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 10,
    "question": "Simplify: 9/5 + 3/3",
    "options": [
      "12/5",
      "15/5",
      "16/5",
      "14/5"
    ],
    "answer": "14/5"
  },
  {
    "id": 197,
    "uuid": "80cebb79-a1c1-42e6-9592-db1df1b0848e",
    "topic": "operations",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.045225",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 7,
    "question": "What is 47 + 15?",
    "options": [
      "65",
      "62",
      "60",
      "69"
    ],
    "answer": "62"
  },
  {
    "id": 200,
    "uuid": "d22a42f9-aec2-47c3-ad21-8218135372c3",
    "topic": "operations",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.045254",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 4,
    "question": "What is 31 + 28?",
    "options": [
      "69",
      "57",
      "59",
      "67"
    ],
    "answer": "59"
  },
  {
    "id": 208,
    "uuid": "faa79723-eadf-4414-a0b5-925392ccf682",
    "topic": "fractions",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.045320",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 9,
    "question": "Simplify: 1/9 + 1/6",
    "options": [
      "6/18",
      "2/18",
      "7/18",
      "5/18"
    ],
    "answer": "5/18"
  },
  {
    "id": 209,
    "uuid": "f9894ada-41d1-4485-8748-e1d48708a684",
    "topic": "operations",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.045335",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 8,
    "question": "What is 19 \u00f7 4 (integer division)?",
    "options": [
      "1",
      "7",
      "13",
      "4"
    ],
    "answer": "4"
  },
  {
    "id": 213,
    "uuid": "70a4f336-19f1-4bf0-a15d-935b447a6a5a",
    "topic": "operations",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.045391",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 8,
    "question": "What is 39 + 46?",
    "options": [
      "85",
      "79",
      "93",
      "81"
    ],
    "answer": "85"
  },
  {
    "id": 216,
    "uuid": "18b6f8f6-8c57-4d67-a973-9d0b50a46608",
    "topic": "operations",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.045417",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 5,
    "question": "What is 9 \u00f7 17 (integer division)?",
    "options": [
      "1",
      "-1",
      "0",
      "10"
    ],
    "answer": "0"
  },
  {
    "id": 220,
    "uuid": "6ba233f2-6361-43a6-9767-db1da1c57ec7",
    "topic": "fractions",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.045473",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 4,
    "question": "Simplify: 1/5 + 9/2",
    "options": [
      "45/10",
      "49/10",
      "47/10",
      "46/10"
    ],
    "answer": "47/10"
  },
  {
    "id": 226,
    "uuid": "fc88a6be-c2aa-4f04-af5c-e41dddae81e6",
    "topic": "operations",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.045524",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 7,
    "question": "What is 41 - 15?",
    "options": [
      "26",
      "35",
      "22",
      "30"
    ],
    "answer": "26"
  },
  {
    "id": 228,
    "uuid": "86b40012-c68a-4bd9-aafb-85d4a61b934b",
    "topic": "operations",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.045549",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 8,
    "question": "What is 24 + 1?",
    "options": [
      "15",
      "26",
      "32",
      "25"
    ],
    "answer": "25"
  },
  {
    "id": 231,
    "uuid": "3ff76bc4-f3a0-4f83-8110-86050221e093",
    "topic": "operations",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.045579",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 3,
    "question": "What is 13 \u00d7 13?",
    "options": [
      "166",
      "169",
      "167",
      "164"
    ],
    "answer": "169"
  },
  {
    "id": 236,
    "uuid": "de0986e9-3588-4ec2-b235-ae1e211cccc4",
    "topic": "fractions",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.045639",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 6,
    "question": "Simplify: 9/8 + 2/3",
    "options": [
      "43/24",
      "41/24",
      "46/24",
      "44/24"
    ],
    "answer": "43/24"
  },
  {
    "id": 238,
    "uuid": "25d32938-7bfa-4098-a7f0-50b6e39bd83a",
    "topic": "trigonometry",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.045655",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 3,
    "question": "What is sin(30\u00b0)?",
    "options": [
      "1",
      "\u221a3/2",
      "0",
      "1/2",
      "\u221a2/2"
    ],
    "answer": "1/2"
  },
  {
    "id": 252,
    "uuid": "ed6356a9-5ee1-43d9-b4b8-2b6ba8263596",
    "topic": "fractions",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.045767",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 4,
    "question": "Simplify: 6/6 + 9/3",
    "options": [
      "4/1",
      "1/1",
      "2/1",
      "7/1"
    ],
    "answer": "4/1"
  },
  {
    "id": 253,
    "uuid": "66cd9ad5-88ed-4811-83d9-23eb1ce75cef",
    "topic": "operations",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.045780",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 7,
    "question": "What is 30 \u00d7 33?",
    "options": [
      "990",
      "994",
      "993",
      "991"
    ],
    "answer": "990"
  },
  {
    "id": 254,
    "uuid": "9b69923e-ae88-44db-977a-41de85e65d68",
    "topic": "operations",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.045791",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 9,
    "question": "What is 12 - 29?",
    "options": [
      "-25",
      "-19",
      "-17",
      "-7"
    ],
    "answer": "-17"
  },
  {
    "id": 261,
    "uuid": "5df50c13-b969-4d73-988c-e41bd60be9b9",
    "topic": "operations",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.045851",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 8,
    "question": "What is 31 - 42?",
    "options": [
      "-14",
      "-9",
      "-11",
      "-15"
    ],
    "answer": "-11"
  },
  {
    "id": 267,
    "uuid": "6a31d740-edf5-433b-85c0-933a81b69032",
    "topic": "fractions",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.045913",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 6,
    "question": "Simplify: 5/2 + 8/7",
    "options": [
      "51/14",
      "50/14",
      "49/14",
      "53/14"
    ],
    "answer": "51/14"
  },
  {
    "id": 268,
    "uuid": "0b0ce47d-3aa4-4efa-bb77-4347a44f6027",
    "topic": "operations",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.045926",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 7,
    "question": "What is 37 - 3?",
    "options": [
      "42",
      "34",
      "28",
      "44"
    ],
    "answer": "34"
  },
  {
    "id": 273,
    "uuid": "12d37bd5-ae71-4999-93f5-c2177d5a3be1",
    "topic": "fractions",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.045984",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 6,
    "question": "Simplify: 4/3 + 7/6",
    "options": [
      "4/2",
      "7/2",
      "3/2",
      "5/2"
    ],
    "answer": "5/2"
  },
  {
    "id": 275,
    "uuid": "0baa60cf-6144-4a36-87f4-f888dc6cc7d3",
    "topic": "fractions",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.046008",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 7,
    "question": "Simplify: 6/8 + 7/4",
    "options": [
      "3/2",
      "5/2",
      "2/2",
      "6/2"
    ],
    "answer": "5/2"
  },
  {
    "id": 283,
    "uuid": "65b25f5c-399f-4ac0-87b9-7497089b9b9f",
    "topic": "operations",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.046069",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 7,
    "question": "What is 48 \u00d7 6?",
    "options": [
      "289",
      "288",
      "298",
      "292"
    ],
    "answer": "288"
  },
  {
    "id": 287,
    "uuid": "8ecae97b-1f92-4307-8909-2bae17531ca6",
    "topic": "fractions",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.046119",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 9,
    "question": "Simplify: 5/6 + 2/5",
    "options": [
      "40/30",
      "34/30",
      "37/30",
      "38/30"
    ],
    "answer": "37/30"
  },
  {
    "id": 294,
    "uuid": "49351a7b-9004-413e-a03b-b9fdff4c7f22",
    "topic": "operations",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.046171",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 8,
    "question": "What is 17 - 8?",
    "options": [
      "13",
      "1",
      "14",
      "9"
    ],
    "answer": "9"
  },
  {
    "id": 295,
    "uuid": "64e82b56-706f-4428-aa4f-9422862b005b",
    "topic": "fractions",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.046196",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 2,
    "question": "Simplify: 8/6 + 3/4",
    "options": [
      "22/12",
      "28/12",
      "26/12",
      "25/12"
    ],
    "answer": "25/12"
  },
  {
    "id": 297,
    "uuid": "f1b51aff-fe67-49f9-b2f5-cb6ca8834a58",
    "topic": "fractions",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.046229",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 8,
    "question": "Simplify: 2/2 + 5/4",
    "options": [
      "8/4",
      "11/4",
      "7/4",
      "9/4"
    ],
    "answer": "9/4"
  },
  {
    "id": 298,
    "uuid": "96eeadab-bfbf-49f5-8339-80bf46444c3b",
    "topic": "operations",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.046241",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "question": "What is 41 + 34?",
    "options": [
      "77",
      "79",
      "74",
      "75"
    ],
    "answer": "75"
  },
  {
    "id": 303,
    "uuid": "70433f38-da75-4a36-9366-75dc8df7d5d8",
    "topic": "operations",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.046281",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 7,
    "question": "What is 27 + 33?",
    "options": [
      "60",
      "56",
      "70",
      "67"
    ],
    "answer": "60"
  },
  {
    "id": 306,
    "uuid": "b01799d6-fa41-4f09-a5d0-5efe561a7f4b",
    "topic": "operations",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.046306",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 5,
    "question": "What is 26 \u00d7 42?",
    "options": [
      "1082",
      "1094",
      "1092",
      "1088"
    ],
    "answer": "1092"
  },
  {
    "id": 311,
    "uuid": "ac54f7fb-8f9e-4fd8-b1c1-2cab3986b29e",
    "topic": "fractions",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.046362",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 8,
    "question": "Simplify: 5/3 + 6/8",
    "options": [
      "27/12",
      "31/12",
      "29/12",
      "32/12"
    ],
    "answer": "29/12"
  },
  {
    "id": 315,
    "uuid": "5320e0ea-b483-4932-89e0-cd2946617559",
    "topic": "operations",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.046393",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "question": "What is 15 + 2?",
    "options": [
      "20",
      "17",
      "14",
      "16"
    ],
    "answer": "17"
  },
  {
    "id": 316,
    "uuid": "0417e59f-832b-45e6-a701-b6920f168b5c",
    "topic": "fractions",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.046416",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 6,
    "question": "Simplify: 6/9 + 5/5",
    "options": [
      "5/3",
      "2/3",
      "7/3",
      "3/3"
    ],
    "answer": "5/3"
  },
  {
    "id": 317,
    "uuid": "27e1ca52-e82c-4275-bc3f-d834b4be57f2",
    "topic": "fractions",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.046461",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 6,
    "question": "Simplify: 5/7 + 1/8",
    "options": [
      "50/56",
      "49/56",
      "46/56",
      "47/56"
    ],
    "answer": "47/56"
  },
  {
    "id": 319,
    "uuid": "bd840023-2a20-47b8-a53a-663c06edfd98",
    "topic": "operations",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.046483",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "question": "What is 43 - 16?",
    "options": [
      "33",
      "36",
      "27",
      "29"
    ],
    "answer": "27"
  },
  {
    "id": 321,
    "uuid": "21381d3f-2346-42ba-9412-d7d2062b8683",
    "topic": "fractions",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.046529",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 7,
    "question": "Simplify: 4/4 + 2/4",
    "options": [
      "1/2",
      "3/2",
      "6/2",
      "4/2"
    ],
    "answer": "3/2"
  },
  {
    "id": 323,
    "uuid": "3d1aecdc-c519-42ef-a283-94604708b428",
    "topic": "fractions",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.046556",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 4,
    "question": "Simplify: 4/5 + 7/4",
    "options": [
      "51/20",
      "52/20",
      "50/20",
      "49/20"
    ],
    "answer": "51/20"
  },
  {
    "id": 335,
    "uuid": "885252bb-7b34-40d0-be05-4855966449f4",
    "topic": "fractions",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.046746",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 2,
    "question": "Simplify: 4/2 + 1/7",
    "options": [
      "14/7",
      "16/7",
      "17/7",
      "15/7"
    ],
    "answer": "15/7"
  },
  {
    "id": 339,
    "uuid": "188419b3-2efb-42c4-b93d-d651c85197e7",
    "topic": "operations",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.046786",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 3,
    "question": "What is 42 \u00f7 8 (integer division)?",
    "options": [
      "2",
      "5",
      "-4",
      "10"
    ],
    "answer": "5"
  },
  {
    "id": 341,
    "uuid": "0d9a51c2-1618-4d14-9054-30620257dd69",
    "topic": "fractions",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.046831",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 7,
    "question": "Simplify: 1/3 + 2/8",
    "options": [
      "8/12",
      "7/12",
      "4/12",
      "9/12"
    ],
    "answer": "7/12"
  },
  {
    "id": 345,
    "uuid": "5dd3cad2-35e1-4e87-806a-4f84e93b012e",
    "topic": "operations",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.046873",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 6,
    "question": "What is 7 \u00f7 17 (integer division)?",
    "options": [
      "3",
      "10",
      "0",
      "-1"
    ],
    "answer": "0"
  },
  {
    "id": 346,
    "uuid": "fe9b22d9-b22c-499d-8a3c-b8939f826391",
    "topic": "fractions",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.046906",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "question": "Simplify: 3/5 + 8/4",
    "options": [
      "16/5",
      "10/5",
      "13/5",
      "14/5"
    ],
    "answer": "13/5"
  },
  {
    "id": 347,
    "uuid": "dcb7f758-269e-4901-8545-5413152e6260",
    "topic": "fractions",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.046937",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 2,
    "question": "Simplify: 4/6 + 7/9",
    "options": [
      "14/9",
      "10/9",
      "13/9",
      "15/9"
    ],
    "answer": "13/9"
  },
  {
    "id": 349,
    "uuid": "c95449d1-bf3a-4a1e-a33a-3257ae7d557a",
    "topic": "operations",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.046959",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 2,
    "question": "What is 38 \u00f7 16 (integer division)?",
    "options": [
      "-5",
      "-7",
      "2",
      "-8"
    ],
    "answer": "2"
  },
  {
    "id": 355,
    "uuid": "82a910b7-6281-4832-951c-0aac5377ea59",
    "topic": "operations",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.047018",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 6,
    "question": "What is 30 \u00f7 5 (integer division)?",
    "options": [
      "-4",
      "6",
      "-1",
      "15"
    ],
    "answer": "6"
  },
  {
    "id": 367,
    "uuid": "c46ed018-2a65-4ce7-b6aa-cc149efd8d5a",
    "topic": "fractions",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.047145",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 3,
    "question": "Simplify: 8/3 + 5/9",
    "options": [
      "31/9",
      "26/9",
      "29/9",
      "27/9"
    ],
    "answer": "29/9"
  },
  {
    "id": 381,
    "uuid": "169625c3-9759-41fe-af83-97982d3157c1",
    "topic": "operations",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.047291",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 2,
    "question": "What is 20 - 4?",
    "options": [
      "17",
      "16",
      "19",
      "18"
    ],
    "answer": "16"
  },
  {
    "id": 383,
    "uuid": "8c662c04-3e7a-4c1f-8815-e4b04ff03fbb",
    "topic": "fractions",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.047319",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 10,
    "question": "Simplify: 5/5 + 8/9",
    "options": [
      "16/9",
      "17/9",
      "18/9",
      "15/9"
    ],
    "answer": "17/9"
  },
  {
    "id": 387,
    "uuid": "208c7afe-a416-4a3d-b0b3-265b369a792a",
    "topic": "operations",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.047358",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 5,
    "question": "What is 22 - 10?",
    "options": [
      "12",
      "9",
      "3",
      "7"
    ],
    "answer": "12"
  },
  {
    "id": 388,
    "uuid": "41d8d166-f409-4f92-a6b1-6cb75d9c2533",
    "topic": "fractions",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.047390",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 9,
    "question": "Simplify: 1/8 + 6/8",
    "options": [
      "6/8",
      "7/8",
      "9/8",
      "10/8"
    ],
    "answer": "7/8"
  },
  {
    "id": 390,
    "uuid": "670d005d-3e62-4e29-afef-f6baa93ec2b7",
    "topic": "operations",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.047418",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 4,
    "question": "What is 46 \u00f7 6 (integer division)?",
    "options": [
      "1",
      "7",
      "15",
      "11"
    ],
    "answer": "7"
  },
  {
    "id": 392,
    "uuid": "a5a26419-33ad-4eb8-98ea-de859ffbccc5",
    "topic": "operations",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.047440",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 6,
    "question": "What is 24 + 47?",
    "options": [
      "74",
      "73",
      "71",
      "65"
    ],
    "answer": "71"
  },
  {
    "id": 394,
    "uuid": "4bbefa46-0174-4bdf-9e55-d3abfa8bd476",
    "topic": "operations",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.047465",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 2,
    "question": "What is 8 \u00d7 33?",
    "options": [
      "272",
      "267",
      "264",
      "258"
    ],
    "answer": "264"
  },
  {
    "id": 398,
    "uuid": "7608f7ae-098d-4fce-9d74-980b90492674",
    "topic": "operations",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.047544",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 5,
    "question": "What is 8 + 8?",
    "options": [
      "21",
      "26",
      "16",
      "9"
    ],
    "answer": "16"
  },
  {
    "id": 407,
    "uuid": "5d79fb71-578e-4534-a315-d32a0eaf901c",
    "topic": "fractions",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.047653",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 3,
    "question": "Simplify: 3/2 + 9/9",
    "options": [
      "8/2",
      "4/2",
      "2/2",
      "5/2"
    ],
    "answer": "5/2"
  },
  {
    "id": 410,
    "uuid": "fe66174b-0412-422c-9d43-6979dce7b36e",
    "topic": "fractions",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.047724",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 3,
    "question": "Simplify: 7/2 + 4/6",
    "options": [
      "25/6",
      "22/6",
      "28/6",
      "26/6"
    ],
    "answer": "25/6"
  },
  {
    "id": 415,
    "uuid": "53741a1d-92da-4f5b-b739-7f60f30a0e26",
    "topic": "operations",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.047768",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 10,
    "question": "What is 16 - 3?",
    "options": [
      "9",
      "13",
      "12",
      "7"
    ],
    "answer": "13"
  },
  {
    "id": 417,
    "uuid": "d17a4087-4d38-4578-b923-3aacaf8a8424",
    "topic": "fractions",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.047811",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 5,
    "question": "Simplify: 7/3 + 9/6",
    "options": [
      "25/6",
      "23/6",
      "22/6",
      "21/6"
    ],
    "answer": "23/6"
  },
  {
    "id": 431,
    "uuid": "ae7f2628-3615-4876-aa33-1fe3caf6532d",
    "topic": "fractions",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.047966",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 4,
    "question": "Simplify: 5/2 + 9/4",
    "options": [
      "20/4",
      "21/4",
      "19/4",
      "17/4"
    ],
    "answer": "19/4"
  },
  {
    "id": 437,
    "uuid": "4d121812-ce61-4994-b625-adaed2e8cb03",
    "topic": "operations",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.048118",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 8,
    "question": "What is 6 \u00d7 48?",
    "options": [
      "295",
      "288",
      "293",
      "278"
    ],
    "answer": "288"
  },
  {
    "id": 444,
    "uuid": "be12105a-14e6-4002-b127-d921068afd57",
    "topic": "fractions",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.048190",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 9,
    "question": "Simplify: 2/7 + 3/7",
    "options": [
      "3/7",
      "4/7",
      "2/7",
      "5/7"
    ],
    "answer": "5/7"
  },
  {
    "id": 447,
    "uuid": "55c7a8c5-b433-481a-8819-5f7ffd15b9ba",
    "topic": "operations",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.048219",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 6,
    "question": "What is 30 \u00f7 2 (integer division)?",
    "options": [
      "15",
      "5",
      "16",
      "24"
    ],
    "answer": "15"
  },
  {
    "id": 452,
    "uuid": "04044b99-777c-4734-9933-0bc4ae2ccf67",
    "topic": "fractions",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.048264",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 7,
    "question": "Simplify: 7/3 + 8/2",
    "options": [
      "21/3",
      "17/3",
      "19/3",
      "22/3"
    ],
    "answer": "19/3"
  },
  {
    "id": 455,
    "uuid": "16227c32-cdc3-4e67-af8e-b40a3c471377",
    "topic": "fractions",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.048302",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "question": "Simplify: 9/6 + 2/9",
    "options": [
      "31/18",
      "34/18",
      "29/18",
      "33/18"
    ],
    "answer": "31/18"
  },
  {
    "id": 459,
    "uuid": "d2f037f2-66f8-4462-979e-0f9b55d1e5f5",
    "topic": "fractions",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.048350",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 9,
    "question": "Simplify: 4/9 + 5/3",
    "options": [
      "19/9",
      "22/9",
      "21/9",
      "20/9"
    ],
    "answer": "19/9"
  },
  {
    "id": 461,
    "uuid": "05469cea-2cfc-4397-aeff-d63e91d417fa",
    "topic": "fractions",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.048373",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 7,
    "question": "Simplify: 3/7 + 9/2",
    "options": [
      "67/14",
      "72/14",
      "71/14",
      "69/14"
    ],
    "answer": "69/14"
  },
  {
    "id": 462,
    "uuid": "93331df0-13ac-4026-87b8-4771b7ed5a39",
    "topic": "operations",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.048385",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 9,
    "question": "What is 28 \u00d7 31?",
    "options": [
      "867",
      "873",
      "868",
      "860"
    ],
    "answer": "868"
  },
  {
    "id": 463,
    "uuid": "9c54c412-1632-49a3-9981-7a58b5970549",
    "topic": "fractions",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.048409",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 2,
    "question": "Simplify: 4/6 + 2/6",
    "options": [
      "-1/1",
      "3/1",
      "1/1",
      "4/1"
    ],
    "answer": "1/1"
  },
  {
    "id": 465,
    "uuid": "a98481bb-b0dd-4485-ae06-1debd9de5dab",
    "topic": "fractions",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.048432",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "question": "Simplify: 4/4 + 4/3",
    "options": [
      "4/3",
      "6/3",
      "7/3",
      "5/3"
    ],
    "answer": "7/3"
  },
  {
    "id": 471,
    "uuid": "9d14f02f-999b-4f48-bee0-39beaef7ff3f",
    "topic": "operations",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.048477",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 3,
    "question": "What is 20 \u00d7 8?",
    "options": [
      "158",
      "160",
      "163",
      "161"
    ],
    "answer": "160"
  },
  {
    "id": 472,
    "uuid": "7ccecd02-5b02-4536-81f5-ef76d87eee2e",
    "topic": "operations",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.048489",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 7,
    "question": "What is 1 \u00d7 4?",
    "options": [
      "0",
      "4",
      "9",
      "3"
    ],
    "answer": "4"
  },
  {
    "id": 473,
    "uuid": "78ac2894-7043-432b-8a6e-27c1b7f9acff",
    "topic": "fractions",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.048512",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 6,
    "question": "Simplify: 5/9 + 6/7",
    "options": [
      "88/63",
      "91/63",
      "86/63",
      "89/63"
    ],
    "answer": "89/63"
  },
  {
    "id": 483,
    "uuid": "03017b3c-07ea-450e-8e25-28801d2e7230",
    "topic": "operations",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.048616",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 7,
    "question": "What is 9 \u00f7 18 (integer division)?",
    "options": [
      "1",
      "0",
      "-2",
      "7"
    ],
    "answer": "0"
  },
  {
    "id": 489,
    "uuid": "f033dc7d-dab9-4513-9925-af24ddc7f9f6",
    "topic": "fractions",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.048699",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 5,
    "question": "Simplify: 1/4 + 4/2",
    "options": [
      "11/4",
      "9/4",
      "12/4",
      "10/4"
    ],
    "answer": "9/4"
  },
  {
    "id": 492,
    "uuid": "fdde395f-cb5a-4247-a963-50fbc0515c33",
    "topic": "fractions",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.048770",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "question": "Simplify: 5/4 + 5/2",
    "options": [
      "18/4",
      "15/4",
      "13/4",
      "17/4"
    ],
    "answer": "15/4"
  },
  {
    "id": 504,
    "uuid": "27f1b931-9575-400f-9ae2-6d5a1dd88ab0",
    "topic": "fractions",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.048887",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 2,
    "question": "Simplify: 4/9 + 3/6",
    "options": [
      "16/18",
      "17/18",
      "15/18",
      "14/18"
    ],
    "answer": "17/18"
  },
  {
    "id": 505,
    "uuid": "2f993013-818e-4258-a15c-dd8652b7ecf3",
    "topic": "fractions",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.048918",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 10,
    "question": "Simplify: 2/8 + 4/9",
    "options": [
      "26/36",
      "25/36",
      "22/36",
      "27/36"
    ],
    "answer": "25/36"
  },
  {
    "id": 507,
    "uuid": "dd6da092-88bb-40bc-b825-f7e1b3622164",
    "topic": "operations",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.048942",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "question": "What is 49 + 42?",
    "options": [
      "85",
      "83",
      "91",
      "88"
    ],
    "answer": "91"
  },
  {
    "id": 514,
    "uuid": "fdf1a7d5-0448-438a-ac81-569ddb3856c2",
    "topic": "operations",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.049010",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 2,
    "question": "What is 15 \u00f7 5 (integer division)?",
    "options": [
      "3",
      "2",
      "13",
      "4"
    ],
    "answer": "3"
  },
  {
    "id": 520,
    "uuid": "20e8f1d8-a84f-4a17-829e-c2ad9fd964bd",
    "topic": "fractions",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.049089",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 3,
    "question": "Simplify: 5/6 + 6/3",
    "options": [
      "16/6",
      "19/6",
      "20/6",
      "17/6"
    ],
    "answer": "17/6"
  },
  {
    "id": 539,
    "uuid": "9ecd9ef3-9c33-4597-a486-88a030833c86",
    "topic": "fractions",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.049274",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 4,
    "question": "Simplify: 2/2 + 6/7",
    "options": [
      "11/7",
      "16/7",
      "13/7",
      "12/7"
    ],
    "answer": "13/7"
  },
  {
    "id": 541,
    "uuid": "fc7129a3-ba9d-4047-bbe1-d1e8ac904675",
    "topic": "fractions",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.049302",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 8,
    "question": "Simplify: 2/4 + 7/2",
    "options": [
      "6/1",
      "1/1",
      "3/1",
      "4/1"
    ],
    "answer": "4/1"
  },
  {
    "id": 542,
    "uuid": "714a8837-28ad-4f20-8ecd-22da4487ff08",
    "topic": "fractions",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.049341",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 8,
    "question": "Simplify: 1/4 + 6/4",
    "options": [
      "4/4",
      "5/4",
      "7/4",
      "8/4"
    ],
    "answer": "7/4"
  },
  {
    "id": 543,
    "uuid": "a2dde249-dd07-40fb-a560-89310ad68188",
    "topic": "fractions",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.049359",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 3,
    "question": "Simplify: 9/6 + 8/8",
    "options": [
      "4/2",
      "8/2",
      "7/2",
      "5/2"
    ],
    "answer": "5/2"
  },
  {
    "id": 544,
    "uuid": "55e1cc31-990d-4e43-bf50-51931791e4aa",
    "topic": "operations",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.049373",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 9,
    "question": "What is 42 - 3?",
    "options": [
      "39",
      "34",
      "45",
      "29"
    ],
    "answer": "39"
  },
  {
    "id": 546,
    "uuid": "d7385969-945b-4edb-80e0-0ff99597b195",
    "topic": "fractions",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.049424",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 3,
    "question": "Simplify: 5/3 + 9/8",
    "options": [
      "69/24",
      "65/24",
      "68/24",
      "67/24"
    ],
    "answer": "67/24"
  },
  {
    "id": 556,
    "uuid": "a1b96872-da59-429d-8fbe-7239236c5557",
    "topic": "operations",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.049515",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 2,
    "question": "What is 16 + 18?",
    "options": [
      "25",
      "42",
      "39",
      "34"
    ],
    "answer": "34"
  },
  {
    "id": 561,
    "uuid": "3dd66fd8-c378-4099-8311-9d8c8a2dae12",
    "topic": "fractions",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.049593",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 9,
    "question": "Simplify: 3/9 + 2/3",
    "options": [
      "4/1",
      "1/1",
      "-1/1",
      "3/1"
    ],
    "answer": "1/1"
  },
  {
    "id": 570,
    "uuid": "7abfe05c-b393-4b4f-8113-8f258542d20b",
    "topic": "operations",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.049677",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 3,
    "question": "What is 10 \u00d7 50?",
    "options": [
      "505",
      "492",
      "507",
      "500"
    ],
    "answer": "500"
  },
  {
    "id": 579,
    "uuid": "dd6311b3-1676-4a44-aa9f-a033186e74cd",
    "topic": "operations",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.049752",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 7,
    "question": "What is 40 + 42?",
    "options": [
      "89",
      "72",
      "82",
      "79"
    ],
    "answer": "82"
  },
  {
    "id": 580,
    "uuid": "2935c688-5115-4adb-9bd7-a10d7b595ffc",
    "topic": "fractions",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.049773",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 9,
    "question": "Simplify: 7/3 + 4/8",
    "options": [
      "17/6",
      "14/6",
      "20/6",
      "19/6"
    ],
    "answer": "17/6"
  },
  {
    "id": 589,
    "uuid": "8b784ebc-9cf0-41d6-aac3-6a5cc5c6b573",
    "topic": "operations",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.049861",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "question": "What is 39 \u00f7 2 (integer division)?",
    "options": [
      "24",
      "22",
      "19",
      "20"
    ],
    "answer": "19"
  },
  {
    "id": 591,
    "uuid": "a3d65e17-e782-4466-93d2-713dd42da437",
    "topic": "fractions",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.049894",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 5,
    "question": "Simplify: 2/6 + 7/3",
    "options": [
      "11/3",
      "8/3",
      "7/3",
      "10/3"
    ],
    "answer": "8/3"
  },
  {
    "id": 592,
    "uuid": "a4338882-ae63-4c59-8921-e04129b3c5a1",
    "topic": "fractions",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.049910",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 8,
    "question": "Simplify: 1/3 + 7/7",
    "options": [
      "4/3",
      "3/3",
      "2/3",
      "7/3"
    ],
    "answer": "4/3"
  },
  {
    "id": 594,
    "uuid": "ab126a77-f843-4042-90ec-70a5d551dc6a",
    "topic": "fractions",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.049944",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 6,
    "question": "Simplify: 7/7 + 7/2",
    "options": [
      "10/2",
      "7/2",
      "12/2",
      "9/2"
    ],
    "answer": "9/2"
  },
  {
    "id": 596,
    "uuid": "1ea48910-7b38-47ab-80a2-64c005b4a080",
    "topic": "fractions",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.049979",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 8,
    "question": "Simplify: 8/4 + 8/7",
    "options": [
      "25/7",
      "22/7",
      "19/7",
      "24/7"
    ],
    "answer": "22/7"
  },
  {
    "id": 597,
    "uuid": "afd41ea3-3874-4014-9aa4-20c3bec15d4f",
    "topic": "fractions",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.050005",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 4,
    "question": "Simplify: 8/3 + 1/5",
    "options": [
      "43/15",
      "44/15",
      "41/15",
      "45/15"
    ],
    "answer": "43/15"
  },
  {
    "id": 600,
    "uuid": "c675370c-ce9f-4214-8621-b852526d11eb",
    "topic": "operations",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.050032",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 7,
    "question": "What is 24 + 24?",
    "options": [
      "48",
      "47",
      "54",
      "41"
    ],
    "answer": "48"
  },
  {
    "id": 603,
    "uuid": "17481347-23ba-4945-b0da-c5a3be8ff10e",
    "topic": "fractions",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.050079",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 10,
    "question": "Simplify: 8/8 + 6/4",
    "options": [
      "5/2",
      "6/2",
      "3/2",
      "4/2"
    ],
    "answer": "5/2"
  },
  {
    "id": 607,
    "uuid": "eedaf3b1-8eae-46bc-a361-4c27fadb96bc",
    "topic": "operations",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.050112",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 8,
    "question": "What is 43 \u00f7 7 (integer division)?",
    "options": [
      "3",
      "10",
      "6",
      "13"
    ],
    "answer": "6"
  },
  {
    "id": 609,
    "uuid": "b9547a5c-5ff2-4cf8-92b3-64c6490c3bac",
    "topic": "operations",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.050132",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "question": "What is 24 \u00d7 15?",
    "options": [
      "359",
      "363",
      "360",
      "358"
    ],
    "answer": "360"
  },
  {
    "id": 610,
    "uuid": "369c351c-6520-4753-9253-3fcfd69a7685",
    "topic": "operations",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.050145",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 4,
    "question": "What is 2 \u00d7 10?",
    "options": [
      "29",
      "26",
      "20",
      "15"
    ],
    "answer": "20"
  },
  {
    "id": 613,
    "uuid": "5599ccdb-4edd-458d-89f4-f7c88527a44f",
    "topic": "fractions",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.050176",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 9,
    "question": "Simplify: 7/5 + 2/4",
    "options": [
      "19/10",
      "20/10",
      "16/10",
      "21/10"
    ],
    "answer": "19/10"
  },
  {
    "id": 614,
    "uuid": "5518d294-2c78-4656-8dbd-e38bf621c04f",
    "topic": "fractions",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.050192",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 10,
    "question": "Simplify: 6/5 + 2/3",
    "options": [
      "31/15",
      "30/15",
      "28/15",
      "25/15"
    ],
    "answer": "28/15"
  },
  {
    "id": 619,
    "uuid": "9d065884-d4b6-496b-bf12-7a0460d73599",
    "topic": "operations",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.050233",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 10,
    "question": "What is 18 - 6?",
    "options": [
      "2",
      "22",
      "20",
      "12"
    ],
    "answer": "12"
  },
  {
    "id": 621,
    "uuid": "d239c7f9-7b25-4264-b8ab-7e9c3ad9e535",
    "topic": "fractions",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.050257",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 2,
    "question": "Simplify: 2/3 + 8/7",
    "options": [
      "36/21",
      "41/21",
      "38/21",
      "35/21"
    ],
    "answer": "38/21"
  },
  {
    "id": 625,
    "uuid": "b5798da5-04b2-4b4b-916f-bfc095ecec45",
    "topic": "fractions",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.050303",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 2,
    "question": "Simplify: 5/2 + 3/2",
    "options": [
      "3/1",
      "1/1",
      "5/1",
      "4/1"
    ],
    "answer": "4/1"
  },
  {
    "id": 629,
    "uuid": "a5b92b9b-401b-46b5-aaa6-7f65de25cc73",
    "topic": "fractions",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.050339",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 5,
    "question": "Simplify: 4/7 + 2/5",
    "options": [
      "32/35",
      "33/35",
      "34/35",
      "31/35"
    ],
    "answer": "34/35"
  },
  {
    "id": 642,
    "uuid": "33bba130-0ffc-4e7c-801f-7c944ec48ac1",
    "topic": "operations",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.050455",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 6,
    "question": "What is 8 \u00d7 12?",
    "options": [
      "97",
      "91",
      "96",
      "99"
    ],
    "answer": "96"
  },
  {
    "id": 645,
    "uuid": "c34f8529-09ac-4061-90f6-23aac705c3d8",
    "topic": "operations",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.050478",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 7,
    "question": "What is 21 + 45?",
    "options": [
      "62",
      "74",
      "66",
      "70"
    ],
    "answer": "66"
  },
  {
    "id": 651,
    "uuid": "2d3c05d4-bed9-4ff1-a220-bc836880588d",
    "topic": "operations",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.050524",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 4,
    "question": "What is 18 + 27?",
    "options": [
      "45",
      "38",
      "40",
      "49"
    ],
    "answer": "45"
  },
  {
    "id": 652,
    "uuid": "ae824537-446a-4011-8905-8f843dcd214e",
    "topic": "operations",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.050535",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 6,
    "question": "What is 19 + 2?",
    "options": [
      "25",
      "20",
      "21",
      "15"
    ],
    "answer": "21"
  },
  {
    "id": 653,
    "uuid": "96bb77ff-08f2-4543-a44c-97ac33adbcb1",
    "topic": "operations",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.050545",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 2,
    "question": "What is 5 + 31?",
    "options": [
      "36",
      "34",
      "39",
      "35"
    ],
    "answer": "36"
  },
  {
    "id": 656,
    "uuid": "4a9f8769-1240-4741-b407-6553a810ce7e",
    "topic": "operations",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.050568",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "question": "What is 26 \u00f7 16 (integer division)?",
    "options": [
      "11",
      "-6",
      "2",
      "1"
    ],
    "answer": "1"
  },
  {
    "id": 657,
    "uuid": "c0e16d2f-4dd8-4f64-8f78-a1359b2feff0",
    "topic": "operations",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.050579",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 9,
    "question": "What is 9 \u00d7 7?",
    "options": [
      "60",
      "66",
      "58",
      "63"
    ],
    "answer": "63"
  },
  {
    "id": 658,
    "uuid": "83692b55-dced-4c22-8e36-5824d953b337",
    "topic": "operations",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.050604",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 10,
    "question": "What is 45 \u00d7 4?",
    "options": [
      "179",
      "173",
      "171",
      "180"
    ],
    "answer": "180"
  },
  {
    "id": 661,
    "uuid": "9e8277e1-53b4-47bc-aa9c-f2f4e333318b",
    "topic": "fractions",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.050669",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 8,
    "question": "Simplify: 6/4 + 7/9",
    "options": [
      "41/18",
      "42/18",
      "38/18",
      "43/18"
    ],
    "answer": "41/18"
  },
  {
    "id": 665,
    "uuid": "1a2d7ec5-1029-47de-a4c9-70c4e52361e1",
    "topic": "operations",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.050720",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 5,
    "question": "What is 43 \u00f7 13 (integer division)?",
    "options": [
      "-4",
      "-1",
      "3",
      "8"
    ],
    "answer": "3"
  },
  {
    "id": 668,
    "uuid": "0fb4fe7c-d826-4448-9913-d7c612bb81fc",
    "topic": "fractions",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.050755",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 5,
    "question": "Simplify: 4/7 + 7/9",
    "options": [
      "88/63",
      "86/63",
      "85/63",
      "83/63"
    ],
    "answer": "85/63"
  },
  {
    "id": 672,
    "uuid": "bf9243dc-f452-4be3-9501-9263f8bb0cd5",
    "topic": "fractions",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.050792",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 4,
    "question": "Simplify: 5/2 + 8/9",
    "options": [
      "62/18",
      "58/18",
      "60/18",
      "61/18"
    ],
    "answer": "61/18"
  },
  {
    "id": 673,
    "uuid": "3591abbd-a68a-4bb0-a637-e47bfbc698fd",
    "topic": "fractions",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.050813",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 4,
    "question": "Simplify: 7/8 + 9/7",
    "options": [
      "121/56",
      "118/56",
      "120/56",
      "123/56"
    ],
    "answer": "121/56"
  },
  {
    "id": 684,
    "uuid": "94b92b3c-1297-4b22-a4c7-c134f9319647",
    "topic": "fractions",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.050949",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 10,
    "question": "Simplify: 1/9 + 7/7",
    "options": [
      "7/9",
      "8/9",
      "9/9",
      "10/9"
    ],
    "answer": "10/9"
  },
  {
    "id": 686,
    "uuid": "498ac3b5-b21f-4ad6-a57a-b9d84eacb8f0",
    "topic": "operations",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.050967",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 3,
    "question": "What is 32 \u00f7 4 (integer division)?",
    "options": [
      "-1",
      "16",
      "8",
      "-2"
    ],
    "answer": "8"
  },
  {
    "id": 692,
    "uuid": "0440ae5e-0e2b-437a-83ff-d2c01ceb9aca",
    "topic": "operations",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.051011",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 3,
    "question": "What is 23 \u00d7 20?",
    "options": [
      "469",
      "465",
      "466",
      "460"
    ],
    "answer": "460"
  },
  {
    "id": 705,
    "uuid": "05b205ac-99c8-4908-ada6-bd8609bcba4a",
    "topic": "fractions",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.051131",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "question": "Simplify: 9/6 + 9/4",
    "options": [
      "18/4",
      "14/4",
      "15/4",
      "12/4"
    ],
    "answer": "15/4"
  },
  {
    "id": 715,
    "uuid": "04437a43-3b3d-4239-b72e-f695b5bc8054",
    "topic": "fractions",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.051217",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 10,
    "question": "Simplify: 4/6 + 3/8",
    "options": [
      "24/24",
      "26/24",
      "25/24",
      "23/24"
    ],
    "answer": "25/24"
  },
  {
    "id": 717,
    "uuid": "6dee9ae3-8b95-4807-8d7b-7560f9dc9fc5",
    "topic": "fractions",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.051245",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 7,
    "question": "Simplify: 7/8 + 2/4",
    "options": [
      "11/8",
      "10/8",
      "12/8",
      "13/8"
    ],
    "answer": "11/8"
  },
  {
    "id": 722,
    "uuid": "9a1d0723-5ea6-42f2-9681-65f7d537881d",
    "topic": "fractions",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.051289",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "question": "Simplify: 9/6 + 1/8",
    "options": [
      "13/8",
      "11/8",
      "15/8",
      "10/8"
    ],
    "answer": "13/8"
  },
  {
    "id": 725,
    "uuid": "1cb88ab2-714c-403b-8db0-c2b5698ca820",
    "topic": "operations",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.051316",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 3,
    "question": "What is 8 + 48?",
    "options": [
      "52",
      "62",
      "56",
      "50"
    ],
    "answer": "56"
  },
  {
    "id": 729,
    "uuid": "efaab76e-a3f5-4369-8379-f9fa978a025a",
    "topic": "operations",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.051353",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 9,
    "question": "What is 33 \u00f7 2 (integer division)?",
    "options": [
      "9",
      "15",
      "16",
      "18"
    ],
    "answer": "16"
  },
  {
    "id": 731,
    "uuid": "0da071b0-5119-441f-80ed-9161eb4b88c5",
    "topic": "fractions",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.051387",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 7,
    "question": "Simplify: 3/5 + 3/5",
    "options": [
      "6/5",
      "8/5",
      "5/5",
      "3/5"
    ],
    "answer": "6/5"
  },
  {
    "id": 733,
    "uuid": "b8c0327a-2dd0-41ec-8e2b-eeed82ae709d",
    "topic": "fractions",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.051415",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "question": "Simplify: 1/6 + 8/3",
    "options": [
      "16/6",
      "18/6",
      "14/6",
      "17/6"
    ],
    "answer": "17/6"
  },
  {
    "id": 739,
    "uuid": "51235951-3b04-48eb-b751-266b64378e7d",
    "topic": "fractions",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.051470",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 7,
    "question": "Simplify: 3/7 + 6/9",
    "options": [
      "23/21",
      "25/21",
      "21/21",
      "26/21"
    ],
    "answer": "23/21"
  },
  {
    "id": 741,
    "uuid": "9129b898-1242-4fd5-bb35-3df70adeb114",
    "topic": "fractions",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.051503",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "question": "Simplify: 9/6 + 3/7",
    "options": [
      "28/14",
      "26/14",
      "27/14",
      "30/14"
    ],
    "answer": "27/14"
  },
  {
    "id": 742,
    "uuid": "76aced0a-1bae-4286-bf67-1ff313b79ae6",
    "topic": "fractions",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.051519",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 2,
    "question": "Simplify: 4/3 + 2/9",
    "options": [
      "17/9",
      "14/9",
      "13/9",
      "16/9"
    ],
    "answer": "14/9"
  },
  {
    "id": 745,
    "uuid": "e45d2865-7c35-449e-9532-198eb345ad3c",
    "topic": "operations",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.051552",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 8,
    "question": "What is 12 + 21?",
    "options": [
      "35",
      "27",
      "33",
      "37"
    ],
    "answer": "33"
  },
  {
    "id": 750,
    "uuid": "1ab4400b-205d-40da-980d-4f57a9492c0d",
    "topic": "operations",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.051590",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 10,
    "question": "What is 24 \u00f7 19 (integer division)?",
    "options": [
      "8",
      "-7",
      "1",
      "-4"
    ],
    "answer": "1"
  },
  {
    "id": 758,
    "uuid": "83181d34-0e85-4084-8fd1-f5fa4371e15c",
    "topic": "operations",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.051654",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 9,
    "question": "What is 15 \u00d7 19?",
    "options": [
      "286",
      "285",
      "277",
      "287"
    ],
    "answer": "285"
  },
  {
    "id": 763,
    "uuid": "113487c9-fe4b-43d9-82e1-57652b0c2daa",
    "topic": "operations",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.051712",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "question": "What is 3 \u00f7 9 (integer division)?",
    "options": [
      "0",
      "-6",
      "-9",
      "-4"
    ],
    "answer": "0"
  },
  {
    "id": 765,
    "uuid": "09a79072-13a7-4953-89f0-09a26eef804f",
    "topic": "operations",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.051731",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "question": "What is 23 \u00f7 20 (integer division)?",
    "options": [
      "-7",
      "10",
      "1",
      "8"
    ],
    "answer": "1"
  },
  {
    "id": 768,
    "uuid": "f9803123-ef83-4efd-b04a-f0070b07c6d2",
    "topic": "operations",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.051758",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "question": "What is 2 - 50?",
    "options": [
      "-46",
      "-41",
      "-39",
      "-48"
    ],
    "answer": "-48"
  },
  {
    "id": 773,
    "uuid": "842eca9a-f5f2-4366-bc58-8a97357ba1a1",
    "topic": "operations",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.051806",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "question": "What is 16 + 15?",
    "options": [
      "39",
      "31",
      "21",
      "28"
    ],
    "answer": "31"
  },
  {
    "id": 775,
    "uuid": "96e2b6d5-b6ab-4798-82ba-0cd32427760f",
    "topic": "operations",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.051825",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 10,
    "question": "What is 9 - 29?",
    "options": [
      "-29",
      "-20",
      "-19",
      "-21"
    ],
    "answer": "-20"
  },
  {
    "id": 789,
    "uuid": "c9d906b6-0e84-4e9f-a5dd-292c625fe3b8",
    "topic": "operations",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.051997",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 5,
    "question": "What is 32 \u00d7 3?",
    "options": [
      "94",
      "98",
      "96",
      "104"
    ],
    "answer": "96"
  },
  {
    "id": 793,
    "uuid": "65d2f942-3ab5-4750-b84f-f5dbcd130ef1",
    "topic": "fractions",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.052047",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 5,
    "question": "Simplify: 7/2 + 5/2",
    "options": [
      "5/1",
      "7/1",
      "9/1",
      "6/1"
    ],
    "answer": "6/1"
  },
  {
    "id": 799,
    "uuid": "4e699a69-1bcc-43d3-a75c-7371b7ce8485",
    "topic": "operations",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.052097",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "question": "What is 18 \u00d7 44?",
    "options": [
      "792",
      "799",
      "784",
      "789"
    ],
    "answer": "792"
  },
  {
    "id": 802,
    "uuid": "0441fd51-13ee-47ee-911d-70590c4e612c",
    "topic": "operations",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.052127",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 10,
    "question": "What is 29 \u00f7 2 (integer division)?",
    "options": [
      "19",
      "14",
      "24",
      "15"
    ],
    "answer": "14"
  },
  {
    "id": 806,
    "uuid": "a2ba8445-e59e-49c7-ab1a-c80067250ae7",
    "topic": "fractions",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.052173",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "question": "Simplify: 1/5 + 2/2",
    "options": [
      "6/5",
      "4/5",
      "8/5",
      "7/5"
    ],
    "answer": "6/5"
  },
  {
    "id": 808,
    "uuid": "b3f5a17b-25b6-49d9-bde5-22b21b463a1f",
    "topic": "operations",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.052192",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 6,
    "question": "What is 46 \u00d7 17?",
    "options": [
      "772",
      "789",
      "783",
      "782"
    ],
    "answer": "782"
  },
  {
    "id": 814,
    "uuid": "b5d431e4-daba-43d5-bb3a-673e3d990807",
    "topic": "operations",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.052239",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 3,
    "question": "What is 21 \u00d7 39?",
    "options": [
      "829",
      "819",
      "822",
      "820"
    ],
    "answer": "819"
  },
  {
    "id": 839,
    "uuid": "719caf61-59b0-4698-9040-a5e83b258f78",
    "topic": "fractions",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.052441",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 3,
    "question": "Simplify: 8/5 + 3/9",
    "options": [
      "26/15",
      "29/15",
      "27/15",
      "28/15"
    ],
    "answer": "29/15"
  },
  {
    "id": 840,
    "uuid": "e2fb31ff-3a58-4c57-a8a5-abf9e2788ca9",
    "topic": "operations",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.052453",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 3,
    "question": "What is 28 - 2?",
    "options": [
      "26",
      "20",
      "18",
      "32"
    ],
    "answer": "26"
  },
  {
    "id": 847,
    "uuid": "2ed3da77-3e59-4129-898e-cd3c038c20e6",
    "topic": "operations",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.052510",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 9,
    "question": "What is 38 \u00d7 38?",
    "options": [
      "1446",
      "1444",
      "1454",
      "1448"
    ],
    "answer": "1444"
  },
  {
    "id": 854,
    "uuid": "1fed77c9-d08c-474b-bf47-52441e9d8e46",
    "topic": "fractions",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.052582",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 3,
    "question": "Simplify: 2/6 + 5/9",
    "options": [
      "7/9",
      "6/9",
      "9/9",
      "8/9"
    ],
    "answer": "8/9"
  },
  {
    "id": 856,
    "uuid": "b97bfeb2-b7fe-4dc5-b7cd-c0ed7beb6f20",
    "topic": "operations",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.052602",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 8,
    "question": "What is 35 - 35?",
    "options": [
      "0",
      "5",
      "1",
      "-10"
    ],
    "answer": "0"
  },
  {
    "id": 867,
    "uuid": "19183fa6-e6ef-4377-afb4-c143c13432ca",
    "topic": "operations",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.052688",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 8,
    "question": "What is 16 \u00f7 8 (integer division)?",
    "options": [
      "0",
      "2",
      "7",
      "-2"
    ],
    "answer": "2"
  },
  {
    "id": 870,
    "uuid": "cb5e7a97-4362-4b6d-9c18-07d6ecfa0001",
    "topic": "operations",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.052717",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 8,
    "question": "What is 27 \u00d7 45?",
    "options": [
      "1215",
      "1225",
      "1217",
      "1224"
    ],
    "answer": "1215"
  },
  {
    "id": 880,
    "uuid": "3a70c66a-fa04-4231-aa81-796c13f6ae63",
    "topic": "fractions",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.052805",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 9,
    "question": "Simplify: 8/9 + 7/5",
    "options": [
      "102/45",
      "103/45",
      "104/45",
      "100/45"
    ],
    "answer": "103/45"
  },
  {
    "id": 885,
    "uuid": "15689ad1-016b-4d23-9f4f-34de67912b0f",
    "topic": "fractions",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.052892",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 6,
    "question": "Simplify: 9/5 + 2/7",
    "options": [
      "74/35",
      "70/35",
      "71/35",
      "73/35"
    ],
    "answer": "73/35"
  },
  {
    "id": 889,
    "uuid": "fa56314a-4967-499e-8b08-d3b536070999",
    "topic": "fractions",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.052940",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 9,
    "question": "Simplify: 9/8 + 4/6",
    "options": [
      "42/24",
      "43/24",
      "46/24",
      "41/24"
    ],
    "answer": "43/24"
  },
  {
    "id": 891,
    "uuid": "090b578c-4b51-4b37-bd01-50d3a183eb98",
    "topic": "operations",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.052958",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 5,
    "question": "What is 49 + 34?",
    "options": [
      "85",
      "89",
      "88",
      "83"
    ],
    "answer": "83"
  },
  {
    "id": 892,
    "uuid": "087d770a-7e1d-42d4-8507-ed445e98a48e",
    "topic": "operations",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.052968",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 3,
    "question": "What is 15 - 41?",
    "options": [
      "-26",
      "-35",
      "-28",
      "-33"
    ],
    "answer": "-26"
  },
  {
    "id": 894,
    "uuid": "49414078-21e4-4f07-9106-0a5a60740aeb",
    "topic": "operations",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.052988",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 6,
    "question": "What is 48 - 35?",
    "options": [
      "13",
      "15",
      "21",
      "6"
    ],
    "answer": "13"
  },
  {
    "id": 910,
    "uuid": "bf1c1dc2-d310-46b8-80c2-26d93ce4bd5b",
    "topic": "operations",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.053155",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 6,
    "question": "What is 21 \u00f7 1 (integer division)?",
    "options": [
      "21",
      "19",
      "17",
      "28"
    ],
    "answer": "21"
  },
  {
    "id": 915,
    "uuid": "dbeb8618-f96d-438e-b0dd-b833a74c41f0",
    "topic": "fractions",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.053218",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 3,
    "question": "Simplify: 1/4 + 9/3",
    "options": [
      "10/4",
      "16/4",
      "11/4",
      "13/4"
    ],
    "answer": "13/4"
  },
  {
    "id": 917,
    "uuid": "22394627-8cdc-4a63-bc05-3332e7e76961",
    "topic": "fractions",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.053246",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 10,
    "question": "Simplify: 9/8 + 7/2",
    "options": [
      "37/8",
      "36/8",
      "39/8",
      "34/8"
    ],
    "answer": "37/8"
  },
  {
    "id": 919,
    "uuid": "63e19a26-f429-487d-acf7-ffa5db417e57",
    "topic": "fractions",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.053267",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 8,
    "question": "Simplify: 3/6 + 9/5",
    "options": [
      "23/10",
      "26/10",
      "25/10",
      "24/10"
    ],
    "answer": "23/10"
  },
  {
    "id": 922,
    "uuid": "e2094d85-870b-4ee4-95f3-d3ddec5a3609",
    "topic": "fractions",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.053315",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 9,
    "question": "Simplify: 9/9 + 1/7",
    "options": [
      "7/7",
      "5/7",
      "8/7",
      "6/7"
    ],
    "answer": "8/7"
  },
  {
    "id": 925,
    "uuid": "6169b2c8-6c97-4750-b616-ee2b56645086",
    "topic": "fractions",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.053344",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 7,
    "question": "Simplify: 2/7 + 9/5",
    "options": [
      "73/35",
      "75/35",
      "70/35",
      "72/35"
    ],
    "answer": "73/35"
  },
  {
    "id": 927,
    "uuid": "7617a57a-3310-4968-883c-593015f7154e",
    "topic": "fractions",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.053368",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 6,
    "question": "Simplify: 2/5 + 5/4",
    "options": [
      "33/20",
      "30/20",
      "34/20",
      "32/20"
    ],
    "answer": "33/20"
  },
  {
    "id": 930,
    "uuid": "f8a34545-b9a7-41f7-9fe8-5f79b53e92a9",
    "topic": "fractions",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.053405",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 6,
    "question": "Simplify: 3/4 + 8/2",
    "options": [
      "19/4",
      "16/4",
      "18/4",
      "17/4"
    ],
    "answer": "19/4"
  },
  {
    "id": 935,
    "uuid": "98ecedec-862b-4f7a-9113-4bc2d17c8f77",
    "topic": "fractions",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.053449",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 3,
    "question": "Simplify: 7/9 + 8/6",
    "options": [
      "19/9",
      "21/9",
      "16/9",
      "20/9"
    ],
    "answer": "19/9"
  },
  {
    "id": 936,
    "uuid": "a22c66bc-e491-427c-b11d-641c3ce34bac",
    "topic": "operations",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.053461",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 3,
    "question": "What is 24 \u00d7 30?",
    "options": [
      "720",
      "716",
      "729",
      "723"
    ],
    "answer": "720"
  },
  {
    "id": 937,
    "uuid": "4d022638-abcc-4f60-87c3-b0adf2604660",
    "topic": "operations",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.053471",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 6,
    "question": "What is 13 \u00d7 29?",
    "options": [
      "367",
      "377",
      "383",
      "373"
    ],
    "answer": "377"
  },
  {
    "id": 940,
    "uuid": "3b363402-d85e-4c09-91f4-889c79ccddb8",
    "topic": "operations",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.053499",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "question": "What is 37 \u00f7 20 (integer division)?",
    "options": [
      "5",
      "1",
      "6",
      "11"
    ],
    "answer": "1"
  },
  {
    "id": 942,
    "uuid": "b538afef-8da6-4492-9ee1-31ab3d8d0238",
    "topic": "fractions",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.053535",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 9,
    "question": "Simplify: 3/4 + 2/8",
    "options": [
      "-2/1",
      "3/1",
      "4/1",
      "1/1"
    ],
    "answer": "1/1"
  },
  {
    "id": 945,
    "uuid": "a00e7716-8adf-4d44-91ec-600a759bbda3",
    "topic": "operations",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.053562",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 2,
    "question": "What is 43 \u00f7 2 (integer division)?",
    "options": [
      "21",
      "27",
      "17",
      "13"
    ],
    "answer": "21"
  },
  {
    "id": 946,
    "uuid": "619326bf-4415-4818-8af7-fc957520e28a",
    "topic": "fractions",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.053583",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 9,
    "question": "Simplify: 8/2 + 5/5",
    "options": [
      "3/1",
      "6/1",
      "7/1",
      "5/1"
    ],
    "answer": "5/1"
  },
  {
    "id": 952,
    "uuid": "bdcafb4e-53db-4a08-9cdd-d0bb6b82ea95",
    "topic": "operations",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.053628",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 5,
    "question": "What is 50 + 11?",
    "options": [
      "57",
      "71",
      "61",
      "62"
    ],
    "answer": "61"
  },
  {
    "id": 961,
    "uuid": "32152573-4f72-49aa-9b5d-005fb2ffface",
    "topic": "fractions",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.053703",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 9,
    "question": "Simplify: 1/8 + 3/5",
    "options": [
      "32/40",
      "31/40",
      "29/40",
      "28/40"
    ],
    "answer": "29/40"
  },
  {
    "id": 965,
    "uuid": "56879fb8-3cc1-4e47-b595-e997a1306c3b",
    "topic": "operations",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.053734",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 10,
    "question": "What is 8 - 34?",
    "options": [
      "-26",
      "-22",
      "-21",
      "-32"
    ],
    "answer": "-26"
  },
  {
    "id": 968,
    "uuid": "62e41485-bb00-46fd-aefc-f700c33d52d2",
    "topic": "fractions",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.053767",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 10,
    "question": "Simplify: 6/6 + 3/9",
    "options": [
      "7/3",
      "2/3",
      "5/3",
      "4/3"
    ],
    "answer": "4/3"
  },
  {
    "id": 976,
    "uuid": "6dcac1ca-2e5f-4be9-ae7d-a882e10c3b51",
    "topic": "fractions",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.053833",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 3,
    "question": "Simplify: 3/7 + 1/3",
    "options": [
      "16/21",
      "14/21",
      "15/21",
      "19/21"
    ],
    "answer": "16/21"
  },
  {
    "id": 978,
    "uuid": "ae8a38e6-e37a-4d5b-853b-6ca16fce30e6",
    "topic": "fractions",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.053856",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 4,
    "question": "Simplify: 4/4 + 5/6",
    "options": [
      "9/6",
      "11/6",
      "14/6",
      "8/6"
    ],
    "answer": "11/6"
  },
  {
    "id": 979,
    "uuid": "7d9d5ad4-adc6-482f-bba3-9c9993c054f7",
    "topic": "fractions",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.053871",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 4,
    "question": "Simplify: 9/7 + 1/9",
    "options": [
      "88/63",
      "86/63",
      "87/63",
      "85/63"
    ],
    "answer": "88/63"
  },
  {
    "id": 985,
    "uuid": "7b6c6742-48ad-4510-9298-b25e3101b698",
    "topic": "operations",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.053945",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 2,
    "question": "What is 15 - 39?",
    "options": [
      "-18",
      "-27",
      "-23",
      "-24"
    ],
    "answer": "-24"
  },
  {
    "id": 989,
    "uuid": "909b1f95-219d-4aa8-8c7a-6d4dc01c236c",
    "topic": "fractions",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.053993",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 8,
    "question": "Simplify: 5/6 + 7/9",
    "options": [
      "28/18",
      "29/18",
      "27/18",
      "26/18"
    ],
    "answer": "29/18"
  },
  {
    "id": 991,
    "uuid": "480be462-1264-46ee-8d53-a305da4cba18",
    "topic": "operations",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.054011",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 7,
    "question": "What is 11 - 21?",
    "options": [
      "-4",
      "-2",
      "-10",
      "-8"
    ],
    "answer": "-10"
  },
  {
    "id": 997,
    "uuid": "d4b24cf7-4e6c-4f2f-9f95-6096ee50ff5d",
    "topic": "operations",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.054085",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 5,
    "question": "What is 30 + 19?",
    "options": [
      "53",
      "42",
      "49",
      "54"
    ],
    "answer": "49"
  },
  {
    "id": 1000,
    "uuid": "74f28e1c-d504-489b-8531-de1bdd1265a0",
    "topic": "fractions",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.054135",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 9,
    "question": "Simplify: 5/7 + 7/2",
    "options": [
      "61/14",
      "56/14",
      "58/14",
      "59/14"
    ],
    "answer": "59/14"
  },
  {
    "id": 1017,
    "uuid": "0d780bf0-0a90-4db0-9b80-da442b09b4b6",
    "topic": "operations",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.054257",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 2,
    "question": "What is 27 + 14?",
    "options": [
      "41",
      "39",
      "44",
      "35"
    ],
    "answer": "41"
  },
  {
    "id": 1033,
    "uuid": "ed26f490-afc6-41b4-b2f7-22396daadf26",
    "topic": "fractions",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.054382",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 9,
    "question": "Simplify: 6/8 + 7/2",
    "options": [
      "16/4",
      "20/4",
      "17/4",
      "18/4"
    ],
    "answer": "17/4"
  },
  {
    "id": 1034,
    "uuid": "f9a41e76-592d-4963-a9bc-7bdbbee381e7",
    "topic": "fractions",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.054402",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 7,
    "question": "Simplify: 7/3 + 2/8",
    "options": [
      "29/12",
      "32/12",
      "31/12",
      "28/12"
    ],
    "answer": "31/12"
  },
  {
    "id": 1057,
    "uuid": "d1038d41-19bf-4dc8-bfb1-efba283df1fc",
    "topic": "fractions",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.054571",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 7,
    "question": "Simplify: 8/3 + 6/4",
    "options": [
      "23/6",
      "22/6",
      "27/6",
      "25/6"
    ],
    "answer": "25/6"
  },
  {
    "id": 1073,
    "uuid": "55b3dfb1-4faa-424e-b248-236fb8cd0fdd",
    "topic": "fractions",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.054736",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 3,
    "question": "Simplify: 3/4 + 5/8",
    "options": [
      "13/8",
      "10/8",
      "9/8",
      "11/8"
    ],
    "answer": "11/8"
  },
  {
    "id": 1074,
    "uuid": "79f868bd-c67d-4896-bdde-ac9061c7ae39",
    "topic": "operations",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.054748",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 9,
    "question": "What is 17 \u00f7 16 (integer division)?",
    "options": [
      "1",
      "2",
      "-4",
      "10"
    ],
    "answer": "1"
  },
  {
    "id": 1078,
    "uuid": "f8fbcabd-c249-4ede-b629-bf00d2dd6fc5",
    "topic": "fractions",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.054799",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 6,
    "question": "Simplify: 8/8 + 1/3",
    "options": [
      "3/3",
      "5/3",
      "2/3",
      "4/3"
    ],
    "answer": "4/3"
  },
  {
    "id": 1080,
    "uuid": "a1a9f24c-c955-4792-a354-0f5f3a9fc03a",
    "topic": "operations",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.054816",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 6,
    "question": "What is 48 - 34?",
    "options": [
      "10",
      "14",
      "15",
      "5"
    ],
    "answer": "14"
  },
  {
    "id": 1086,
    "uuid": "4d2b7355-1420-4daf-8d2e-d51f0f084940",
    "topic": "fractions",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.054874",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "question": "Simplify: 1/6 + 9/6",
    "options": [
      "7/3",
      "2/3",
      "3/3",
      "5/3"
    ],
    "answer": "5/3"
  },
  {
    "id": 1095,
    "uuid": "42d6b20b-efd7-4870-9ce7-8b36432cd60a",
    "topic": "operations",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.054946",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 7,
    "question": "What is 38 + 28?",
    "options": [
      "76",
      "70",
      "66",
      "62"
    ],
    "answer": "66"
  },
  {
    "id": 1100,
    "uuid": "f41f3291-3f10-4b68-a9e4-d1db284f88f0",
    "topic": "fractions",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.055044",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 2,
    "question": "Simplify: 8/2 + 6/9",
    "options": [
      "14/3",
      "12/3",
      "11/3",
      "17/3"
    ],
    "answer": "14/3"
  },
  {
    "id": 1109,
    "uuid": "84ef0dfb-06da-4579-a222-95a3abd5782d",
    "topic": "fractions",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.055128",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 4,
    "question": "Simplify: 3/7 + 9/9",
    "options": [
      "10/7",
      "12/7",
      "11/7",
      "13/7"
    ],
    "answer": "10/7"
  },
  {
    "id": 1114,
    "uuid": "cba415a2-8e46-4e94-b678-93171f06a80e",
    "topic": "operations",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.055187",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 5,
    "question": "What is 27 - 23?",
    "options": [
      "2",
      "-6",
      "4",
      "8"
    ],
    "answer": "4"
  },
  {
    "id": 1124,
    "uuid": "d50ec380-c528-4044-b559-f591a09b2700",
    "topic": "fractions",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.055291",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 9,
    "question": "Simplify: 2/7 + 7/4",
    "options": [
      "60/28",
      "57/28",
      "58/28",
      "55/28"
    ],
    "answer": "57/28"
  },
  {
    "id": 1130,
    "uuid": "4bc40a25-f152-40eb-a41c-a085fd080d7f",
    "topic": "fractions",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.055354",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 3,
    "question": "Simplify: 6/9 + 4/9",
    "options": [
      "12/9",
      "10/9",
      "9/9",
      "8/9"
    ],
    "answer": "10/9"
  },
  {
    "id": 1135,
    "uuid": "9994ae7f-c345-4480-9b27-b50d613c2fce",
    "topic": "operations",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.055399",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 2,
    "question": "What is 37 + 28?",
    "options": [
      "65",
      "71",
      "70",
      "72"
    ],
    "answer": "65"
  },
  {
    "id": 1137,
    "uuid": "4f3f0c88-679f-4ec0-bcb4-6924efb0b8b8",
    "topic": "fractions",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.055438",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 8,
    "question": "Simplify: 9/3 + 8/5",
    "options": [
      "23/5",
      "20/5",
      "26/5",
      "25/5"
    ],
    "answer": "23/5"
  },
  {
    "id": 1138,
    "uuid": "1dfe3f1b-3f69-47c5-89c9-b4879446457b",
    "topic": "fractions",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.055465",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 10,
    "question": "Simplify: 6/3 + 3/7",
    "options": [
      "20/7",
      "18/7",
      "17/7",
      "19/7"
    ],
    "answer": "17/7"
  },
  {
    "id": 1141,
    "uuid": "92faf96a-308a-47cd-85ea-947934354ce7",
    "topic": "fractions",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.055573",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 4,
    "question": "Simplify: 5/5 + 6/9",
    "options": [
      "7/3",
      "5/3",
      "8/3",
      "3/3"
    ],
    "answer": "5/3"
  },
  {
    "id": 1142,
    "uuid": "385a5726-1c76-4993-8bfd-946e62ae879b",
    "topic": "fractions",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.055617",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 2,
    "question": "Simplify: 4/6 + 3/3",
    "options": [
      "6/3",
      "2/3",
      "8/3",
      "5/3"
    ],
    "answer": "5/3"
  },
  {
    "id": 1147,
    "uuid": "fa78028a-0b6f-4a2a-b6ee-941626268454",
    "topic": "operations",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.055663",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 8,
    "question": "What is 9 + 29?",
    "options": [
      "28",
      "38",
      "42",
      "40"
    ],
    "answer": "38"
  },
  {
    "id": 1160,
    "uuid": "b4913972-a6aa-4f55-96d9-cf7715e96667",
    "topic": "operations",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.055782",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 5,
    "question": "What is 9 - 34?",
    "options": [
      "-31",
      "-34",
      "-20",
      "-25"
    ],
    "answer": "-25"
  },
  {
    "id": 1164,
    "uuid": "7e68874d-41f6-4b08-8cd3-6d4641dd911d",
    "topic": "fractions",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.055842",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "question": "Simplify: 6/3 + 3/2",
    "options": [
      "7/2",
      "9/2",
      "5/2",
      "6/2"
    ],
    "answer": "7/2"
  },
  {
    "id": 1165,
    "uuid": "f311c286-077c-4494-84bf-588d8817b677",
    "topic": "operations",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.055855",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 3,
    "question": "What is 22 \u00f7 2 (integer division)?",
    "options": [
      "5",
      "11",
      "14",
      "2"
    ],
    "answer": "11"
  },
  {
    "id": 1174,
    "uuid": "6c3074ca-b287-4fa4-b33b-148cb77e13ee",
    "topic": "fractions",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.055949",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 3,
    "question": "Simplify: 4/3 + 2/8",
    "options": [
      "20/12",
      "16/12",
      "19/12",
      "18/12"
    ],
    "answer": "19/12"
  },
  {
    "id": 1177,
    "uuid": "851cec41-8e97-431d-bfb0-5e127aeb3c7b",
    "topic": "operations",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.055982",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 4,
    "question": "What is 48 + 25?",
    "options": [
      "63",
      "73",
      "68",
      "69"
    ],
    "answer": "73"
  },
  {
    "id": 1178,
    "uuid": "4fae326e-6f38-455d-8540-42c72949e922",
    "topic": "fractions",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.056001",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 8,
    "question": "Simplify: 7/7 + 1/9",
    "options": [
      "9/9",
      "10/9",
      "13/9",
      "8/9"
    ],
    "answer": "10/9"
  },
  {
    "id": 1181,
    "uuid": "486285b7-0f59-4615-a536-12415c73033e",
    "topic": "fractions",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.056033",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 2,
    "question": "Simplify: 5/7 + 8/9",
    "options": [
      "101/63",
      "103/63",
      "104/63",
      "98/63"
    ],
    "answer": "101/63"
  },
  {
    "id": 1183,
    "uuid": "732e5a63-09cf-4d4b-afce-129fe9274235",
    "topic": "operations",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.056073",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 3,
    "question": "What is 35 + 9?",
    "options": [
      "37",
      "41",
      "48",
      "44"
    ],
    "answer": "44"
  },
  {
    "id": 1191,
    "uuid": "599476fa-b02d-4421-9d2e-14dfb0ce8298",
    "topic": "fractions",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.056142",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 2,
    "question": "Simplify: 9/2 + 9/7",
    "options": [
      "79/14",
      "81/14",
      "83/14",
      "82/14"
    ],
    "answer": "81/14"
  },
  {
    "id": 1192,
    "uuid": "5f7e5a50-5ddf-488f-b2f3-ef23bca64c78",
    "topic": "fractions",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.056159",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 7,
    "question": "Simplify: 4/4 + 9/8",
    "options": [
      "16/8",
      "15/8",
      "20/8",
      "17/8"
    ],
    "answer": "17/8"
  },
  {
    "id": 1211,
    "uuid": "0a495508-bc1b-4ff5-8973-ee8c197952d1",
    "topic": "fractions",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.056333",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 7,
    "question": "Simplify: 8/6 + 4/3",
    "options": [
      "9/3",
      "5/3",
      "8/3",
      "10/3"
    ],
    "answer": "8/3"
  },
  {
    "id": 1224,
    "uuid": "cd1bcc15-6a4d-4d7e-be14-adac83fd97ec",
    "topic": "fractions",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.056454",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 6,
    "question": "Simplify: 1/7 + 2/6",
    "options": [
      "10/21",
      "7/21",
      "13/21",
      "12/21"
    ],
    "answer": "10/21"
  },
  {
    "id": 1239,
    "uuid": "0ea44a15-b2ca-4c63-af69-b7fc7cffbecf",
    "topic": "fractions",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.056568",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 7,
    "question": "Simplify: 6/2 + 2/5",
    "options": [
      "18/5",
      "17/5",
      "19/5",
      "16/5"
    ],
    "answer": "17/5"
  },
  {
    "id": 1243,
    "uuid": "cf66d9e2-09ce-41ca-ba25-d95c125ac880",
    "topic": "fractions",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.056609",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 5,
    "question": "Simplify: 7/3 + 5/3",
    "options": [
      "3/1",
      "2/1",
      "7/1",
      "4/1"
    ],
    "answer": "4/1"
  },
  {
    "id": 1244,
    "uuid": "a7608d63-2943-4728-b2df-d37bb62dcae4",
    "topic": "operations",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.056621",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 5,
    "question": "What is 32 - 15?",
    "options": [
      "27",
      "21",
      "17",
      "14"
    ],
    "answer": "17"
  },
  {
    "id": 1251,
    "uuid": "09c2be1c-bcb7-4f19-a297-efc1d182b1d2",
    "topic": "fractions",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.056707",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 2,
    "question": "Simplify: 6/5 + 9/4",
    "options": [
      "69/20",
      "66/20",
      "72/20",
      "70/20"
    ],
    "answer": "69/20"
  },
  {
    "id": 1255,
    "uuid": "d6df7181-96f4-4e32-9f7d-e8965ee13050",
    "topic": "operations",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.056738",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 9,
    "question": "What is 30 \u00f7 16 (integer division)?",
    "options": [
      "4",
      "-7",
      "1",
      "9"
    ],
    "answer": "1"
  },
  {
    "id": 1256,
    "uuid": "76aadeb5-018d-480a-8c71-3087a05026bc",
    "topic": "operations",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.056749",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 10,
    "question": "What is 23 - 31?",
    "options": [
      "-16",
      "-8",
      "-10",
      "-7"
    ],
    "answer": "-8"
  },
  {
    "id": 1258,
    "uuid": "125d1fe8-0f88-4c9e-a16b-d67f81c3bce2",
    "topic": "fractions",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.056776",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 3,
    "question": "Simplify: 7/5 + 8/6",
    "options": [
      "40/15",
      "42/15",
      "41/15",
      "43/15"
    ],
    "answer": "41/15"
  },
  {
    "id": 1261,
    "uuid": "fb439410-da19-4c50-bd12-9f0ce57d4994",
    "topic": "operations",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.056804",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 3,
    "question": "What is 46 \u00d7 49?",
    "options": [
      "2246",
      "2262",
      "2247",
      "2254"
    ],
    "answer": "2254"
  },
  {
    "id": 1263,
    "uuid": "775d298f-5f3d-4549-a951-dc7254f75241",
    "topic": "fractions",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.056836",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 8,
    "question": "Simplify: 3/2 + 8/3",
    "options": [
      "25/6",
      "22/6",
      "24/6",
      "26/6"
    ],
    "answer": "25/6"
  },
  {
    "id": 1264,
    "uuid": "d08b1035-f7a0-4acb-8d99-b29f7fd6e781",
    "topic": "fractions",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.056853",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 2,
    "question": "Simplify: 6/4 + 2/6",
    "options": [
      "11/6",
      "9/6",
      "10/6",
      "13/6"
    ],
    "answer": "11/6"
  },
  {
    "id": 1265,
    "uuid": "f7224e3d-5b8d-4ce5-8803-4fac333c1dae",
    "topic": "fractions",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.056876",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 9,
    "question": "Simplify: 5/8 + 4/5",
    "options": [
      "54/40",
      "57/40",
      "56/40",
      "59/40"
    ],
    "answer": "57/40"
  },
  {
    "id": 1273,
    "uuid": "b03e969c-8129-470a-bc3a-95e19ead74ee",
    "topic": "fractions",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.056940",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 9,
    "question": "Simplify: 6/4 + 8/4",
    "options": [
      "8/2",
      "5/2",
      "7/2",
      "10/2"
    ],
    "answer": "7/2"
  },
  {
    "id": 1275,
    "uuid": "59b9a25b-9a3b-4ef9-9677-70b2acf6bfbe",
    "topic": "fractions",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.056973",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 8,
    "question": "Simplify: 9/4 + 2/9",
    "options": [
      "89/36",
      "87/36",
      "90/36",
      "88/36"
    ],
    "answer": "89/36"
  },
  {
    "id": 1285,
    "uuid": "e6cbf571-22c9-40d9-adae-288c2e1d63e7",
    "topic": "operations",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.057050",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 5,
    "question": "What is 32 \u00d7 7?",
    "options": [
      "224",
      "229",
      "231",
      "233"
    ],
    "answer": "224"
  },
  {
    "id": 1286,
    "uuid": "f7efbf68-e75f-4b17-a17c-ceaa75106639",
    "topic": "operations",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.057062",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "question": "What is 34 - 3?",
    "options": [
      "31",
      "39",
      "30",
      "23"
    ],
    "answer": "31"
  },
  {
    "id": 1288,
    "uuid": "ae4f8a82-6eaf-4658-857b-a58c394d7710",
    "topic": "operations",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.057079",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 9,
    "question": "What is 20 - 25?",
    "options": [
      "-4",
      "-5",
      "2",
      "-14"
    ],
    "answer": "-5"
  },
  {
    "id": 1293,
    "uuid": "65f6c232-44ee-45c9-8be3-be6951eb09d6",
    "topic": "fractions",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.057172",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 7,
    "question": "Simplify: 7/5 + 6/8",
    "options": [
      "43/20",
      "44/20",
      "41/20",
      "40/20"
    ],
    "answer": "43/20"
  },
  {
    "id": 1300,
    "uuid": "fee6008a-8a0b-40e0-8ba8-430ea459ae2c",
    "topic": "fractions",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.057241",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 7,
    "question": "Simplify: 5/8 + 5/6",
    "options": [
      "34/24",
      "36/24",
      "35/24",
      "38/24"
    ],
    "answer": "35/24"
  },
  {
    "id": 1303,
    "uuid": "ba1fa481-71f5-4de4-97a3-646f417c265a",
    "topic": "fractions",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.057281",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 2,
    "question": "Simplify: 9/2 + 8/9",
    "options": [
      "94/18",
      "95/18",
      "97/18",
      "100/18"
    ],
    "answer": "97/18"
  },
  {
    "id": 1306,
    "uuid": "4a77ae73-5f66-42de-8fd0-70a9d5a2591c",
    "topic": "fractions",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.057353",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 3,
    "question": "Simplify: 8/2 + 9/5",
    "options": [
      "32/5",
      "31/5",
      "29/5",
      "27/5"
    ],
    "answer": "29/5"
  },
  {
    "id": 1308,
    "uuid": "8fd68113-58a2-4fd4-83be-96e0f26b8a94",
    "topic": "fractions",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.057387",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 4,
    "question": "Simplify: 6/9 + 4/2",
    "options": [
      "6/3",
      "7/3",
      "9/3",
      "8/3"
    ],
    "answer": "8/3"
  },
  {
    "id": 1310,
    "uuid": "7e265b99-1e64-4f61-8c56-90022310f1df",
    "topic": "operations",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.057405",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "question": "What is 29 - 5?",
    "options": [
      "30",
      "23",
      "24",
      "33"
    ],
    "answer": "24"
  },
  {
    "id": 1313,
    "uuid": "cf47d43d-fe56-449a-8922-463915152000",
    "topic": "fractions",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.057437",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 10,
    "question": "Simplify: 6/7 + 1/4",
    "options": [
      "33/28",
      "29/28",
      "28/28",
      "31/28"
    ],
    "answer": "31/28"
  },
  {
    "id": 1314,
    "uuid": "7a7fe195-55d0-4722-a00b-69e368161a9f",
    "topic": "operations",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.057448",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 10,
    "question": "What is 25 + 50?",
    "options": [
      "85",
      "72",
      "66",
      "75"
    ],
    "answer": "75"
  },
  {
    "id": 1319,
    "uuid": "9c065093-0bdd-47b9-9a79-0881747b43de",
    "topic": "fractions",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.057503",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 3,
    "question": "Simplify: 5/4 + 7/6",
    "options": [
      "31/12",
      "28/12",
      "27/12",
      "29/12"
    ],
    "answer": "29/12"
  },
  {
    "id": 1320,
    "uuid": "98a10faa-f668-47d2-b181-73fcce2eceaf",
    "topic": "operations",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.057515",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 7,
    "question": "What is 30 - 27?",
    "options": [
      "13",
      "5",
      "3",
      "-3"
    ],
    "answer": "3"
  },
  {
    "id": 1336,
    "uuid": "8af6285c-ae89-49f7-ac2e-4295f9752f32",
    "topic": "fractions",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.057639",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 10,
    "question": "Simplify: 5/4 + 7/5",
    "options": [
      "53/20",
      "52/20",
      "56/20",
      "51/20"
    ],
    "answer": "53/20"
  },
  {
    "id": 1339,
    "uuid": "9683b381-5773-4f81-ac26-6bf9267a1730",
    "topic": "operations",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.057672",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 6,
    "question": "What is 22 \u00d7 6?",
    "options": [
      "128",
      "132",
      "126",
      "133"
    ],
    "answer": "132"
  },
  {
    "id": 1349,
    "uuid": "8a57214a-f8d9-4087-9ae1-08ff208a463b",
    "topic": "operations",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.057761",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 8,
    "question": "What is 9 \u00f7 13 (integer division)?",
    "options": [
      "-10",
      "0",
      "5",
      "-5"
    ],
    "answer": "0"
  },
  {
    "id": 1350,
    "uuid": "3ebb01c1-9886-48fc-b61e-6014a1233bc9",
    "topic": "operations",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.057775",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 7,
    "question": "What is 32 \u00d7 43?",
    "options": [
      "1376",
      "1371",
      "1377",
      "1368"
    ],
    "answer": "1376"
  },
  {
    "id": 1351,
    "uuid": "163ee83f-01a9-4be4-a2cf-79a23860f6cf",
    "topic": "fractions",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.057816",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "question": "Simplify: 2/5 + 6/6",
    "options": [
      "7/5",
      "9/5",
      "4/5",
      "10/5"
    ],
    "answer": "7/5"
  },
  {
    "id": 1356,
    "uuid": "be6c0195-c601-4f60-b425-f92ceac4da30",
    "topic": "fractions",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.057885",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 6,
    "question": "Simplify: 1/5 + 5/6",
    "options": [
      "30/30",
      "31/30",
      "28/30",
      "33/30"
    ],
    "answer": "31/30"
  },
  {
    "id": 1358,
    "uuid": "7cd4a07a-25dd-4f00-91c9-9828cea1d6c1",
    "topic": "fractions",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.057931",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 6,
    "question": "Simplify: 1/2 + 5/8",
    "options": [
      "9/8",
      "7/8",
      "11/8",
      "6/8"
    ],
    "answer": "9/8"
  },
  {
    "id": 1368,
    "uuid": "bf294056-8ce5-4e32-9f2c-a4811ee2882a",
    "topic": "operations",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.058017",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 2,
    "question": "What is 47 \u00d7 1?",
    "options": [
      "47",
      "56",
      "39",
      "41"
    ],
    "answer": "47"
  },
  {
    "id": 1374,
    "uuid": "0d367a3d-b23d-4e82-bada-c0b74983c2a4",
    "topic": "fractions",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.058102",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 5,
    "question": "Simplify: 8/6 + 1/9",
    "options": [
      "11/9",
      "14/9",
      "10/9",
      "13/9"
    ],
    "answer": "13/9"
  },
  {
    "id": 1375,
    "uuid": "9cfda2ec-0db7-4e65-956c-2d9b110f723a",
    "topic": "fractions",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.058122",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 10,
    "question": "Simplify: 9/5 + 2/3",
    "options": [
      "40/15",
      "36/15",
      "37/15",
      "35/15"
    ],
    "answer": "37/15"
  },
  {
    "id": 1392,
    "uuid": "bdaed550-80f6-4c46-a7a1-33e814072ce9",
    "topic": "fractions",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.058277",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "question": "Simplify: 7/8 + 1/4",
    "options": [
      "9/8",
      "8/8",
      "11/8",
      "12/8"
    ],
    "answer": "9/8"
  },
  {
    "id": 1401,
    "uuid": "20609c87-ba43-46fd-92e1-daaaad841f26",
    "topic": "operations",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.058383",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 10,
    "question": "What is 20 - 41?",
    "options": [
      "-11",
      "-21",
      "-22",
      "-12"
    ],
    "answer": "-21"
  },
  {
    "id": 1402,
    "uuid": "92097ff2-f0ac-4bbe-9d80-194f164f0c29",
    "topic": "fractions",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.058415",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 2,
    "question": "Simplify: 9/6 + 6/7",
    "options": [
      "33/14",
      "36/14",
      "31/14",
      "35/14"
    ],
    "answer": "33/14"
  },
  {
    "id": 1403,
    "uuid": "a5c0af99-82ee-4fb9-b383-5dde37544672",
    "topic": "operations",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.058428",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 10,
    "question": "What is 29 \u00f7 8 (integer division)?",
    "options": [
      "3",
      "0",
      "-1",
      "13"
    ],
    "answer": "3"
  },
  {
    "id": 1405,
    "uuid": "f0d0d147-abd0-416c-a5a5-d47a23ec1193",
    "topic": "fractions",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.058464",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 10,
    "question": "Simplify: 6/5 + 4/5",
    "options": [
      "-1/1",
      "1/1",
      "3/1",
      "2/1"
    ],
    "answer": "2/1"
  },
  {
    "id": 1415,
    "uuid": "83344578-c930-45ed-91cb-db6f49016dca",
    "topic": "fractions",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.058548",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 5,
    "question": "Simplify: 5/7 + 8/7",
    "options": [
      "16/7",
      "13/7",
      "11/7",
      "14/7"
    ],
    "answer": "13/7"
  },
  {
    "id": 1416,
    "uuid": "7a464ba0-8678-4082-8792-7cb43ff1c205",
    "topic": "operations",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.058560",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 4,
    "question": "What is 48 \u00d7 13?",
    "options": [
      "627",
      "626",
      "621",
      "624"
    ],
    "answer": "624"
  },
  {
    "id": 1417,
    "uuid": "c967bc6c-b866-4eaf-80dd-16e864288685",
    "topic": "fractions",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.058583",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 9,
    "question": "Simplify: 5/2 + 1/8",
    "options": [
      "21/8",
      "20/8",
      "24/8",
      "18/8"
    ],
    "answer": "21/8"
  },
  {
    "id": 1418,
    "uuid": "4b37f5e6-3306-48b6-a782-0bdd88746579",
    "topic": "fractions",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.058605",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 10,
    "question": "Simplify: 8/7 + 2/6",
    "options": [
      "29/21",
      "31/21",
      "30/21",
      "33/21"
    ],
    "answer": "31/21"
  },
  {
    "id": 1419,
    "uuid": "dbe4c4d1-3028-4178-b02b-b8921ef8755d",
    "topic": "fractions",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.058646",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 6,
    "question": "Simplify: 6/2 + 2/2",
    "options": [
      "3/1",
      "4/1",
      "7/1",
      "5/1"
    ],
    "answer": "4/1"
  },
  {
    "id": 1423,
    "uuid": "9bc5f6f0-323c-423c-878e-c5f2df1609f9",
    "topic": "operations",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.058693",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 4,
    "question": "What is 33 - 4?",
    "options": [
      "23",
      "21",
      "29",
      "34"
    ],
    "answer": "29"
  },
  {
    "id": 1432,
    "uuid": "b974862d-eef7-4eb1-9a54-7aedc75f61a0",
    "topic": "operations",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.058762",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 9,
    "question": "What is 42 - 45?",
    "options": [
      "-6",
      "-12",
      "-3",
      "2"
    ],
    "answer": "-3"
  },
  {
    "id": 1435,
    "uuid": "0a4b75fe-4ff4-4a5f-adad-ab62608b4dc0",
    "topic": "operations",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.058788",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 10,
    "question": "What is 43 \u00f7 18 (integer division)?",
    "options": [
      "-6",
      "-7",
      "-2",
      "2"
    ],
    "answer": "2"
  },
  {
    "id": 1439,
    "uuid": "ad15b6eb-ab5e-47f6-b52d-2fc2802e0d2e",
    "topic": "fractions",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.058834",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 9,
    "question": "Simplify: 7/5 + 3/2",
    "options": [
      "29/10",
      "31/10",
      "28/10",
      "30/10"
    ],
    "answer": "29/10"
  },
  {
    "id": 1443,
    "uuid": "7ec8c926-051f-4521-af15-b81579f6540a",
    "topic": "operations",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.058867",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 4,
    "question": "What is 29 \u00f7 7 (integer division)?",
    "options": [
      "-1",
      "-3",
      "4",
      "-5"
    ],
    "answer": "4"
  },
  {
    "id": 1449,
    "uuid": "cd6ae23d-79bd-42ad-a6b0-c484a7ab4d1a",
    "topic": "fractions",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.058924",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "question": "Simplify: 8/9 + 9/6",
    "options": [
      "46/18",
      "41/18",
      "45/18",
      "43/18"
    ],
    "answer": "43/18"
  },
  {
    "id": 1450,
    "uuid": "0e510625-ef5e-4cd3-aeca-f9090e0684dd",
    "topic": "operations",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.058935",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 2,
    "question": "What is 40 + 4?",
    "options": [
      "34",
      "44",
      "42",
      "43"
    ],
    "answer": "44"
  },
  {
    "id": 1451,
    "uuid": "52affacb-d5de-4dec-b3f0-c62ec7d23b9f",
    "topic": "operations",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.058945",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 5,
    "question": "What is 24 - 14?",
    "options": [
      "2",
      "10",
      "13",
      "11"
    ],
    "answer": "10"
  },
  {
    "id": 1452,
    "uuid": "ffabb8d0-b4d9-4617-a61e-6899d79b42e7",
    "topic": "operations",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.058957",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 8,
    "question": "What is 8 - 20?",
    "options": [
      "-14",
      "-16",
      "-8",
      "-12"
    ],
    "answer": "-12"
  },
  {
    "id": 1453,
    "uuid": "f7c984a0-4103-4c0d-87a0-57541b15ae40",
    "topic": "fractions",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.058983",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 10,
    "question": "Simplify: 1/3 + 2/5",
    "options": [
      "13/15",
      "11/15",
      "14/15",
      "12/15"
    ],
    "answer": "11/15"
  },
  {
    "id": 1455,
    "uuid": "7ed357ce-6888-44e8-a2a4-45a65cab0bb7",
    "topic": "fractions",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.059024",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 2,
    "question": "Simplify: 4/3 + 7/8",
    "options": [
      "50/24",
      "51/24",
      "56/24",
      "53/24"
    ],
    "answer": "53/24"
  },
  {
    "id": 1458,
    "uuid": "fbfadce8-aea9-4f51-8ec1-625bc7d9028d",
    "topic": "operations",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.059050",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 10,
    "question": "What is 42 \u00f7 18 (integer division)?",
    "options": [
      "-7",
      "2",
      "7",
      "-1"
    ],
    "answer": "2"
  },
  {
    "id": 1461,
    "uuid": "25551e75-5598-48ff-9e47-e6a9a3b758ec",
    "topic": "fractions",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.059098",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 6,
    "question": "Simplify: 6/7 + 9/4",
    "options": [
      "87/28",
      "89/28",
      "86/28",
      "85/28"
    ],
    "answer": "87/28"
  },
  {
    "id": 1465,
    "uuid": "8098f0b4-15fe-48f2-878c-ea5b8b0e0023",
    "topic": "operations",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.059133",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 4,
    "question": "What is 22 - 33?",
    "options": [
      "-1",
      "-11",
      "-4",
      "-2"
    ],
    "answer": "-11"
  },
  {
    "id": 1469,
    "uuid": "5f9bf8c7-948e-4e99-b804-51e48bed4c95",
    "topic": "operations",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.059164",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 9,
    "question": "What is 17 - 36?",
    "options": [
      "-19",
      "-22",
      "-26",
      "-14"
    ],
    "answer": "-19"
  },
  {
    "id": 1477,
    "uuid": "eabda8ac-48f5-4a7f-8f1e-a56fa653d82c",
    "topic": "operations",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.059242",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 6,
    "question": "What is 19 - 8?",
    "options": [
      "3",
      "6",
      "11",
      "9"
    ],
    "answer": "11"
  },
  {
    "id": 1481,
    "uuid": "3f08e0c1-45d4-468a-91e5-369454e6dbf2",
    "topic": "operations",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.059299",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 7,
    "question": "What is 44 + 32?",
    "options": [
      "76",
      "81",
      "66",
      "77"
    ],
    "answer": "76"
  },
  {
    "id": 1491,
    "uuid": "9f5bcfc4-1dd4-4a3f-aaab-3a16e6927c94",
    "topic": "operations",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.059391",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 9,
    "question": "What is 33 + 29?",
    "options": [
      "62",
      "68",
      "66",
      "57"
    ],
    "answer": "62"
  },
  {
    "id": 1492,
    "uuid": "d676ebf2-c13e-4f43-a955-106a0bd9693d",
    "topic": "operations",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.059403",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "question": "What is 17 + 38?",
    "options": [
      "60",
      "55",
      "61",
      "50"
    ],
    "answer": "55"
  },
  {
    "id": 1496,
    "uuid": "b6cc5e07-96d3-4f04-be30-b9831b824026",
    "topic": "fractions",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.059554",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 2,
    "question": "Simplify: 7/2 + 5/4",
    "options": [
      "18/4",
      "17/4",
      "19/4",
      "22/4"
    ],
    "answer": "19/4"
  },
  {
    "id": 1498,
    "uuid": "1a41a81b-8cfb-4e5e-9728-53c7543c61fb",
    "topic": "operations",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.059578",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 7,
    "question": "What is 29 \u00d7 32?",
    "options": [
      "931",
      "928",
      "934",
      "918"
    ],
    "answer": "928"
  },
  {
    "id": 1503,
    "uuid": "0584eee5-1b2d-4d72-8419-1aff85935790",
    "topic": "fractions",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.059639",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 2,
    "question": "Simplify: 4/9 + 9/7",
    "options": [
      "109/63",
      "106/63",
      "108/63",
      "110/63"
    ],
    "answer": "109/63"
  },
  {
    "id": 1507,
    "uuid": "98382adb-a02e-416c-88b2-8d8d07696033",
    "topic": "operations",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.059679",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 4,
    "question": "What is 8 \u00d7 34?",
    "options": [
      "262",
      "280",
      "272",
      "278"
    ],
    "answer": "272"
  },
  {
    "id": 1513,
    "uuid": "d1056b95-866f-4821-91b5-ec0f8a8e9842",
    "topic": "fractions",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.059744",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 4,
    "question": "Simplify: 2/9 + 9/3",
    "options": [
      "29/9",
      "30/9",
      "27/9",
      "31/9"
    ],
    "answer": "29/9"
  },
  {
    "id": 1515,
    "uuid": "f2e4ab8c-b534-4986-91df-c6309a062a91",
    "topic": "operations",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.059766",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 8,
    "question": "What is 13 \u00d7 43?",
    "options": [
      "568",
      "559",
      "563",
      "561"
    ],
    "answer": "559"
  },
  {
    "id": 1517,
    "uuid": "5011bd4d-182b-463e-b3eb-c47c99cdceec",
    "topic": "fractions",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.059812",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 6,
    "question": "Simplify: 4/6 + 8/3",
    "options": [
      "12/3",
      "10/3",
      "7/3",
      "11/3"
    ],
    "answer": "10/3"
  },
  {
    "id": 1524,
    "uuid": "083c7c43-3726-4b42-8f62-f2b37ca5ce45",
    "topic": "fractions",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.059887",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 5,
    "question": "Simplify: 8/7 + 2/9",
    "options": [
      "88/63",
      "87/63",
      "85/63",
      "86/63"
    ],
    "answer": "86/63"
  },
  {
    "id": 1529,
    "uuid": "a90bd386-6265-4a9b-8598-2f5de6ab4c46",
    "topic": "fractions",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.059940",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 4,
    "question": "Simplify: 5/5 + 6/7",
    "options": [
      "16/7",
      "14/7",
      "13/7",
      "11/7"
    ],
    "answer": "13/7"
  },
  {
    "id": 1531,
    "uuid": "1465a32f-f3fd-4554-a212-f3bb5a8c1bb1",
    "topic": "fractions",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.059974",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 3,
    "question": "Simplify: 8/7 + 4/8",
    "options": [
      "23/14",
      "25/14",
      "22/14",
      "24/14"
    ],
    "answer": "23/14"
  },
  {
    "id": 1539,
    "uuid": "c074b35c-01f5-48bb-a95d-95075d1ee56a",
    "topic": "fractions",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.060051",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 3,
    "question": "Simplify: 2/7 + 1/2",
    "options": [
      "10/14",
      "14/14",
      "8/14",
      "11/14"
    ],
    "answer": "11/14"
  },
  {
    "id": 1541,
    "uuid": "ab7d9b31-c2ce-478e-9117-5402d1f53e75",
    "topic": "operations",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.060074",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 4,
    "question": "What is 43 + 37?",
    "options": [
      "80",
      "89",
      "70",
      "73"
    ],
    "answer": "80"
  },
  {
    "id": 1545,
    "uuid": "353ed24c-80e0-4beb-a998-400d19b8d2c8",
    "topic": "fractions",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.060119",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 2,
    "question": "Simplify: 7/5 + 9/2",
    "options": [
      "60/10",
      "59/10",
      "57/10",
      "56/10"
    ],
    "answer": "59/10"
  },
  {
    "id": 1548,
    "uuid": "a83d938c-920e-4486-94ef-bbac7eda798b",
    "topic": "fractions",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.060157",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 8,
    "question": "Simplify: 3/5 + 5/3",
    "options": [
      "34/15",
      "36/15",
      "31/15",
      "32/15"
    ],
    "answer": "34/15"
  },
  {
    "id": 1551,
    "uuid": "25558389-d7b5-46d6-a29f-4266951e4e53",
    "topic": "fractions",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.060205",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 8,
    "question": "Simplify: 7/8 + 1/6",
    "options": [
      "28/24",
      "25/24",
      "23/24",
      "27/24"
    ],
    "answer": "25/24"
  },
  {
    "id": 1554,
    "uuid": "a8303abd-c8bd-409e-8035-af52e1ecbbf1",
    "topic": "fractions",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.060255",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 10,
    "question": "Simplify: 2/8 + 3/8",
    "options": [
      "7/8",
      "3/8",
      "5/8",
      "4/8"
    ],
    "answer": "5/8"
  },
  {
    "id": 1565,
    "uuid": "d28df9a9-dbd2-44db-9fdf-a3da072aafdc",
    "topic": "operations",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.060388",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 5,
    "question": "What is 25 + 24?",
    "options": [
      "46",
      "44",
      "41",
      "49"
    ],
    "answer": "49"
  },
  {
    "id": 1569,
    "uuid": "b5d6f933-d36e-4f87-a749-bf406c125dd7",
    "topic": "operations",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.060430",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "question": "What is 37 - 42?",
    "options": [
      "-6",
      "2",
      "-5",
      "0"
    ],
    "answer": "-5"
  },
  {
    "id": 1573,
    "uuid": "b50a570a-3e22-48c6-bc26-782bfa2aef3f",
    "topic": "fractions",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.060482",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 9,
    "question": "Simplify: 9/4 + 4/2",
    "options": [
      "16/4",
      "17/4",
      "15/4",
      "20/4"
    ],
    "answer": "17/4"
  },
  {
    "id": 1576,
    "uuid": "b12503d3-c5b2-491f-8f57-0f48b649d63e",
    "topic": "fractions",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.060552",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 2,
    "question": "Simplify: 3/5 + 6/6",
    "options": [
      "5/5",
      "10/5",
      "8/5",
      "6/5"
    ],
    "answer": "8/5"
  },
  {
    "id": 1583,
    "uuid": "b8e80a9e-acd6-45dd-aa9b-94b404fffee6",
    "topic": "fractions",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.060639",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 5,
    "question": "Simplify: 1/5 + 2/7",
    "options": [
      "17/35",
      "16/35",
      "20/35",
      "14/35"
    ],
    "answer": "17/35"
  },
  {
    "id": 1598,
    "uuid": "dae63fdb-95c0-4ddc-b77d-4b6b66fcee8a",
    "topic": "operations",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.060771",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 3,
    "question": "What is 31 \u00d7 5?",
    "options": [
      "161",
      "154",
      "155",
      "151"
    ],
    "answer": "155"
  },
  {
    "id": 1600,
    "uuid": "1fd42144-baec-49f5-83df-bf1676931313",
    "topic": "operations",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.060791",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 6,
    "question": "What is 2 - 33?",
    "options": [
      "-30",
      "-25",
      "-21",
      "-31"
    ],
    "answer": "-31"
  },
  {
    "id": 1606,
    "uuid": "8bfcca6f-afb8-47c7-a5a9-192f33ea1407",
    "topic": "operations",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.060844",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 4,
    "question": "What is 43 + 50?",
    "options": [
      "87",
      "97",
      "93",
      "95"
    ],
    "answer": "93"
  },
  {
    "id": 1610,
    "uuid": "69e9f456-dda5-4489-9d04-8bafed6ac8ee",
    "topic": "fractions",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.060894",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 2,
    "question": "Simplify: 7/6 + 4/2",
    "options": [
      "22/6",
      "17/6",
      "16/6",
      "19/6"
    ],
    "answer": "19/6"
  },
  {
    "id": 1616,
    "uuid": "9f09b4b0-3d48-4831-b263-6da2a308369d",
    "topic": "fractions",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.060980",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 8,
    "question": "Simplify: 9/6 + 4/5",
    "options": [
      "23/10",
      "26/10",
      "22/10",
      "20/10"
    ],
    "answer": "23/10"
  },
  {
    "id": 1632,
    "uuid": "56514837-9fce-4dd8-b291-bacaf5eacb63",
    "topic": "operations",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.061128",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 3,
    "question": "What is 10 \u00f7 16 (integer division)?",
    "options": [
      "10",
      "-8",
      "-6",
      "0"
    ],
    "answer": "0"
  },
  {
    "id": 1633,
    "uuid": "141b775b-214c-463f-bcfb-32279e605236",
    "topic": "operations",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.061141",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 6,
    "question": "What is 9 \u00d7 19?",
    "options": [
      "179",
      "172",
      "163",
      "171"
    ],
    "answer": "171"
  },
  {
    "id": 1635,
    "uuid": "bb01f013-2bb9-46ec-a59d-31ee4201b6a6",
    "topic": "operations",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.061164",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 10,
    "question": "What is 13 \u00f7 16 (integer division)?",
    "options": [
      "-7",
      "0",
      "8",
      "-2"
    ],
    "answer": "0"
  },
  {
    "id": 1640,
    "uuid": "405ae36f-d0f5-4f12-bd36-d03cb46c5f71",
    "topic": "operations",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.061211",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 7,
    "question": "What is 26 - 22?",
    "options": [
      "4",
      "5",
      "9",
      "8"
    ],
    "answer": "4"
  },
  {
    "id": 1643,
    "uuid": "52d90393-a83f-4f38-b8f9-d1a8aecd5e51",
    "topic": "fractions",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.061247",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 3,
    "question": "Simplify: 3/2 + 2/2",
    "options": [
      "2/2",
      "3/2",
      "6/2",
      "5/2"
    ],
    "answer": "5/2"
  },
  {
    "id": 1650,
    "uuid": "7d809457-ce3a-4c87-8c50-c6c9be13baf1",
    "topic": "operations",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.061310",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 6,
    "question": "What is 17 - 25?",
    "options": [
      "-6",
      "-8",
      "-3",
      "-4"
    ],
    "answer": "-8"
  },
  {
    "id": 1652,
    "uuid": "c6eeacd9-c79b-40a1-9c3d-c8e98dc76761",
    "topic": "fractions",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.061337",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 5,
    "question": "Simplify: 5/8 + 2/9",
    "options": [
      "59/72",
      "58/72",
      "61/72",
      "60/72"
    ],
    "answer": "61/72"
  },
  {
    "id": 1656,
    "uuid": "c924b7f9-981f-45d1-9f46-23a2afa2018e",
    "topic": "operations",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.061389",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 9,
    "question": "What is 7 - 31?",
    "options": [
      "-24",
      "-28",
      "-18",
      "-30"
    ],
    "answer": "-24"
  },
  {
    "id": 1661,
    "uuid": "1670e6a6-c6f6-445c-906c-4411f656c0ea",
    "topic": "operations",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.061444",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 8,
    "question": "What is 19 + 22?",
    "options": [
      "51",
      "49",
      "44",
      "41"
    ],
    "answer": "41"
  },
  {
    "id": 1666,
    "uuid": "b2202c68-4821-4aec-96d4-55694342acbd",
    "topic": "operations",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.061482",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 9,
    "question": "What is 15 - 29?",
    "options": [
      "-24",
      "-12",
      "-11",
      "-14"
    ],
    "answer": "-14"
  },
  {
    "id": 1668,
    "uuid": "cd367f67-6b8c-419a-bb9e-fdf219edc6d7",
    "topic": "operations",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.061500",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 2,
    "question": "What is 33 \u00d7 47?",
    "options": [
      "1551",
      "1556",
      "1542",
      "1560"
    ],
    "answer": "1551"
  },
  {
    "id": 1672,
    "uuid": "c22f83cb-6dd6-4e39-a750-7344817ec060",
    "topic": "operations",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.061532",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 5,
    "question": "What is 44 + 28?",
    "options": [
      "82",
      "69",
      "77",
      "72"
    ],
    "answer": "72"
  },
  {
    "id": 1673,
    "uuid": "e9e0ed1e-568b-46b4-962e-49ee6ec64d94",
    "topic": "fractions",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.061573",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 9,
    "question": "Simplify: 5/6 + 7/4",
    "options": [
      "30/12",
      "33/12",
      "29/12",
      "31/12"
    ],
    "answer": "31/12"
  },
  {
    "id": 1685,
    "uuid": "cde08341-f7ca-449f-a139-b3504d57dc32",
    "topic": "fractions",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.061682",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 9,
    "question": "Simplify: 9/5 + 8/7",
    "options": [
      "102/35",
      "103/35",
      "100/35",
      "106/35"
    ],
    "answer": "103/35"
  },
  {
    "id": 1693,
    "uuid": "3a095f6e-b456-4795-9b8b-e653385d671f",
    "topic": "operations",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.061741",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 2,
    "question": "What is 37 + 23?",
    "options": [
      "63",
      "70",
      "61",
      "60"
    ],
    "answer": "60"
  },
  {
    "id": 1694,
    "uuid": "dd788b0b-f5fd-486c-886f-4501ad8813f7",
    "topic": "fractions",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.061772",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 6,
    "question": "Simplify: 2/3 + 3/9",
    "options": [
      "2/1",
      "4/1",
      "1/1",
      "3/1"
    ],
    "answer": "1/1"
  },
  {
    "id": 1709,
    "uuid": "dd6ecfbe-6fdd-4c53-ace9-4c85c411347b",
    "topic": "operations",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.061886",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 6,
    "question": "What is 9 + 5?",
    "options": [
      "4",
      "22",
      "14",
      "7"
    ],
    "answer": "14"
  },
  {
    "id": 1714,
    "uuid": "f1a986f9-2738-40d0-95eb-54b970c78013",
    "topic": "fractions",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.061938",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "question": "Simplify: 3/5 + 7/2",
    "options": [
      "42/10",
      "41/10",
      "40/10",
      "43/10"
    ],
    "answer": "41/10"
  },
  {
    "id": 1722,
    "uuid": "4ee47f27-838c-450b-9b59-2732d90c1562",
    "topic": "fractions",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.062003",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 2,
    "question": "Simplify: 3/3 + 4/4",
    "options": [
      "0/1",
      "2/1",
      "-1/1",
      "4/1"
    ],
    "answer": "2/1"
  },
  {
    "id": 1724,
    "uuid": "c9340959-47f8-47a2-b516-8938f61694bc",
    "topic": "operations",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.062024",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 3,
    "question": "What is 42 + 14?",
    "options": [
      "49",
      "46",
      "56",
      "59"
    ],
    "answer": "56"
  },
  {
    "id": 1725,
    "uuid": "d414ce49-454b-4bd2-8b63-1021b9a0d334",
    "topic": "fractions",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.062048",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 3,
    "question": "Simplify: 2/7 + 6/8",
    "options": [
      "31/28",
      "29/28",
      "30/28",
      "28/28"
    ],
    "answer": "29/28"
  },
  {
    "id": 1730,
    "uuid": "661c8fcd-74e0-4f16-87d8-c74efb7c4d61",
    "topic": "fractions",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.062093",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 3,
    "question": "Simplify: 1/2 + 8/6",
    "options": [
      "11/6",
      "8/6",
      "10/6",
      "9/6"
    ],
    "answer": "11/6"
  },
  {
    "id": 1736,
    "uuid": "85f5a6d1-af4f-4819-908c-60b866290665",
    "topic": "operations",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.062142",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 6,
    "question": "What is 50 \u00f7 13 (integer division)?",
    "options": [
      "10",
      "9",
      "3",
      "0"
    ],
    "answer": "3"
  },
  {
    "id": 1739,
    "uuid": "d11aa11b-972a-4bed-8294-4802feba0fb0",
    "topic": "operations",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.062167",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 8,
    "question": "What is 5 + 37?",
    "options": [
      "40",
      "42",
      "41",
      "39"
    ],
    "answer": "42"
  },
  {
    "id": 1741,
    "uuid": "eedb3962-d80f-4da3-8032-b9e33f964a8f",
    "topic": "fractions",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.062188",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 2,
    "question": "Simplify: 1/7 + 9/8",
    "options": [
      "72/56",
      "70/56",
      "71/56",
      "68/56"
    ],
    "answer": "71/56"
  },
  {
    "id": 1751,
    "uuid": "6c600722-4ead-43e1-b04f-aee5b9da9e1c",
    "topic": "fractions",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.062272",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 3,
    "question": "Simplify: 4/8 + 1/5",
    "options": [
      "4/10",
      "8/10",
      "9/10",
      "7/10"
    ],
    "answer": "7/10"
  },
  {
    "id": 1754,
    "uuid": "23e9b8d9-0a34-44c3-ad5f-0aca8f125a15",
    "topic": "operations",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.062296",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 6,
    "question": "What is 17 \u00f7 4 (integer division)?",
    "options": [
      "2",
      "14",
      "4",
      "12"
    ],
    "answer": "4"
  },
  {
    "id": 1759,
    "uuid": "4cd9f864-614e-4184-8cc9-bc588020f056",
    "topic": "operations",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.062335",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "question": "What is 32 \u00f7 11 (integer division)?",
    "options": [
      "2",
      "8",
      "-6",
      "-5"
    ],
    "answer": "2"
  },
  {
    "id": 1761,
    "uuid": "76f6fb04-762c-4c57-8492-53f3c0eec91d",
    "topic": "fractions",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.062377",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 4,
    "question": "Simplify: 1/3 + 1/6",
    "options": [
      "-1/2",
      "3/2",
      "4/2",
      "1/2"
    ],
    "answer": "1/2"
  },
  {
    "id": 1766,
    "uuid": "99b51c9c-ce37-4bb6-bd04-33202e68dd52",
    "topic": "operations",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.062418",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 4,
    "question": "What is 11 + 24?",
    "options": [
      "42",
      "30",
      "38",
      "35"
    ],
    "answer": "35"
  },
  {
    "id": 1772,
    "uuid": "b2651b12-b1d0-4550-8668-a7896d0b2006",
    "topic": "fractions",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.062472",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 5,
    "question": "Simplify: 8/6 + 6/6",
    "options": [
      "5/3",
      "8/3",
      "9/3",
      "7/3"
    ],
    "answer": "7/3"
  },
  {
    "id": 1774,
    "uuid": "e87703fd-c4cb-4477-9418-040ed42ce626",
    "topic": "operations",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.062518",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 9,
    "question": "What is 15 + 48?",
    "options": [
      "65",
      "68",
      "63",
      "70"
    ],
    "answer": "63"
  },
  {
    "id": 1776,
    "uuid": "eb20ce7f-0516-4caf-85e4-3abf1a2759ad",
    "topic": "operations",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.062536",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 5,
    "question": "What is 33 + 39?",
    "options": [
      "69",
      "72",
      "64",
      "79"
    ],
    "answer": "72"
  },
  {
    "id": 1779,
    "uuid": "9484ec22-9e99-4a16-aca6-ad5fc84baa44",
    "topic": "fractions",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.062586",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 8,
    "question": "Simplify: 4/3 + 9/4",
    "options": [
      "45/12",
      "44/12",
      "40/12",
      "43/12"
    ],
    "answer": "43/12"
  },
  {
    "id": 1780,
    "uuid": "88b1059b-9818-4f64-b5f0-2cb19c9fc8ea",
    "topic": "fractions",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.062613",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 2,
    "question": "Simplify: 5/7 + 1/2",
    "options": [
      "20/14",
      "19/14",
      "14/14",
      "17/14"
    ],
    "answer": "17/14"
  },
  {
    "id": 1784,
    "uuid": "c498eabb-8cfc-4674-8ddf-76e0b290f60e",
    "topic": "operations",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.062685",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 3,
    "question": "What is 47 \u00d7 10?",
    "options": [
      "470",
      "476",
      "472",
      "463"
    ],
    "answer": "470"
  },
  {
    "id": 1788,
    "uuid": "75795fac-0eb8-4f86-a2be-23fa41744d7d",
    "topic": "operations",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.062718",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "question": "What is 21 \u00f7 2 (integer division)?",
    "options": [
      "16",
      "13",
      "14",
      "10"
    ],
    "answer": "10"
  },
  {
    "id": 1795,
    "uuid": "c0b5aa5c-d3c1-48f0-bba5-46bcaa945e59",
    "topic": "fractions",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.062796",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 10,
    "question": "Simplify: 7/2 + 9/2",
    "options": [
      "8/1",
      "5/1",
      "6/1",
      "10/1"
    ],
    "answer": "8/1"
  },
  {
    "id": 1798,
    "uuid": "5acea6c4-f4ee-43e9-ba1b-79481ac09a55",
    "topic": "fractions",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.062829",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 5,
    "question": "Simplify: 2/2 + 5/2",
    "options": [
      "4/2",
      "6/2",
      "10/2",
      "7/2"
    ],
    "answer": "7/2"
  },
  {
    "id": 1803,
    "uuid": "de138d7f-6bd3-46a6-910f-1f47e9bc67c9",
    "topic": "fractions",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.062880",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 6,
    "question": "Simplify: 7/6 + 3/6",
    "options": [
      "3/3",
      "5/3",
      "2/3",
      "4/3"
    ],
    "answer": "5/3"
  },
  {
    "id": 1807,
    "uuid": "ddb3ec37-ab64-4715-a61e-768bc8680d1a",
    "topic": "fractions",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.062921",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 5,
    "question": "Simplify: 6/7 + 5/2",
    "options": [
      "49/14",
      "47/14",
      "45/14",
      "50/14"
    ],
    "answer": "47/14"
  },
  {
    "id": 1814,
    "uuid": "e3a93f3f-842a-4eb1-8613-3a84c7256a71",
    "topic": "operations",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.062976",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 4,
    "question": "What is 19 + 44?",
    "options": [
      "60",
      "59",
      "63",
      "62"
    ],
    "answer": "63"
  },
  {
    "id": 1825,
    "uuid": "5354fd5a-577a-4c5d-89e7-8d16957406da",
    "topic": "operations",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.063052",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 2,
    "question": "What is 27 + 3?",
    "options": [
      "30",
      "39",
      "22",
      "36"
    ],
    "answer": "30"
  },
  {
    "id": 1828,
    "uuid": "9b7d3797-5ef0-426d-b9b4-fb53cfd1d269",
    "topic": "operations",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.063076",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 4,
    "question": "What is 2 + 38?",
    "options": [
      "47",
      "40",
      "33",
      "43"
    ],
    "answer": "40"
  },
  {
    "id": 1833,
    "uuid": "063f8dc3-daf1-4033-8864-960e16d1d6c5",
    "topic": "operations",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.063116",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 4,
    "question": "What is 5 + 20?",
    "options": [
      "35",
      "18",
      "25",
      "31"
    ],
    "answer": "25"
  },
  {
    "id": 1836,
    "uuid": "395934e9-a377-4cda-8e55-d8aa69fecec1",
    "topic": "operations",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.063143",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 8,
    "question": "What is 38 \u00f7 7 (integer division)?",
    "options": [
      "14",
      "1",
      "5",
      "0"
    ],
    "answer": "5"
  },
  {
    "id": 1838,
    "uuid": "894e3b29-c60d-43c9-a405-4de4ee7d9415",
    "topic": "operations",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.063162",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 6,
    "question": "What is 45 \u00d7 48?",
    "options": [
      "2154",
      "2160",
      "2166",
      "2167"
    ],
    "answer": "2160"
  },
  {
    "id": 1839,
    "uuid": "34a380c4-756a-4a6c-8a58-4fceeb8a6351",
    "topic": "operations",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.063173",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 9,
    "question": "What is 50 - 22?",
    "options": [
      "33",
      "28",
      "30",
      "31"
    ],
    "answer": "28"
  },
  {
    "id": 1841,
    "uuid": "9450a53c-f406-4328-8b05-301d464603fe",
    "topic": "operations",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.063191",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "question": "What is 3 + 13?",
    "options": [
      "12",
      "16",
      "22",
      "17"
    ],
    "answer": "16"
  },
  {
    "id": 1857,
    "uuid": "80ce78d6-e6ce-4c03-9755-0fe3e69f0794",
    "topic": "operations",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.063356",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "question": "What is 39 \u00d7 4?",
    "options": [
      "164",
      "156",
      "155",
      "148"
    ],
    "answer": "156"
  },
  {
    "id": 1859,
    "uuid": "76719e5f-eef5-4a97-945e-611664bd5fde",
    "topic": "fractions",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.063398",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 3,
    "question": "Simplify: 7/8 + 7/6",
    "options": [
      "50/24",
      "52/24",
      "49/24",
      "51/24"
    ],
    "answer": "49/24"
  },
  {
    "id": 1866,
    "uuid": "52aed415-d96a-4e45-ad82-95cce0177c30",
    "topic": "operations",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.063453",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 8,
    "question": "What is 36 - 31?",
    "options": [
      "15",
      "5",
      "7",
      "-2"
    ],
    "answer": "5"
  },
  {
    "id": 1867,
    "uuid": "f9c61f37-b19b-41af-b186-1a5ab84d88fe",
    "topic": "fractions",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.063474",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 9,
    "question": "Simplify: 4/6 + 9/5",
    "options": [
      "38/15",
      "37/15",
      "36/15",
      "35/15"
    ],
    "answer": "37/15"
  },
  {
    "id": 1868,
    "uuid": "95e473f8-a00c-4c0b-b376-e1a3f8b34a47",
    "topic": "fractions",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.063494",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 6,
    "question": "Simplify: 9/2 + 5/2",
    "options": [
      "7/1",
      "4/1",
      "9/1",
      "6/1"
    ],
    "answer": "7/1"
  },
  {
    "id": 1869,
    "uuid": "8f4addbd-142f-4d30-a7c1-958e353cf6f8",
    "topic": "operations",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.063506",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 2,
    "question": "What is 36 \u00f7 19 (integer division)?",
    "options": [
      "1",
      "2",
      "8",
      "-5"
    ],
    "answer": "1"
  },
  {
    "id": 1872,
    "uuid": "326721e6-e1dc-42d7-b8ef-cb1184a14595",
    "topic": "operations",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.063535",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 2,
    "question": "What is 36 \u00f7 4 (integer division)?",
    "options": [
      "9",
      "3",
      "15",
      "5"
    ],
    "answer": "9"
  },
  {
    "id": 1880,
    "uuid": "2b2a6917-054f-49b7-8f9e-19eb2e613e58",
    "topic": "operations",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.063630",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 6,
    "question": "What is 5 + 25?",
    "options": [
      "40",
      "28",
      "39",
      "30"
    ],
    "answer": "30"
  },
  {
    "id": 1882,
    "uuid": "573153b0-5194-4f75-8247-825620d418fd",
    "topic": "operations",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.063651",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 10,
    "question": "What is 47 - 24?",
    "options": [
      "23",
      "21",
      "33",
      "13"
    ],
    "answer": "23"
  },
  {
    "id": 1885,
    "uuid": "9e1eb8da-f41d-470f-a986-97b2880c8ab1",
    "topic": "fractions",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.063705",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 5,
    "question": "Simplify: 6/2 + 9/3",
    "options": [
      "3/1",
      "6/1",
      "9/1",
      "8/1"
    ],
    "answer": "6/1"
  },
  {
    "id": 1886,
    "uuid": "eb25d4ce-bbae-4bda-bf11-956f0b064bac",
    "topic": "operations",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.063747",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 6,
    "question": "What is 26 \u00d7 34?",
    "options": [
      "888",
      "880",
      "884",
      "876"
    ],
    "answer": "884"
  },
  {
    "id": 1890,
    "uuid": "31e16a5a-991c-4522-bedf-236c40b8dd24",
    "topic": "operations",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.063779",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 4,
    "question": "What is 14 + 11?",
    "options": [
      "34",
      "20",
      "17",
      "25"
    ],
    "answer": "25"
  },
  {
    "id": 1899,
    "uuid": "31c21e44-fe15-414a-97d3-fbe134c8e5ce",
    "topic": "fractions",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.063867",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 8,
    "question": "Simplify: 7/6 + 9/2",
    "options": [
      "20/3",
      "16/3",
      "17/3",
      "14/3"
    ],
    "answer": "17/3"
  },
  {
    "id": 1904,
    "uuid": "3f978e8b-0c26-4abd-97a4-7756321309fe",
    "topic": "fractions",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.063922",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 5,
    "question": "Simplify: 2/2 + 3/3",
    "options": [
      "5/1",
      "0/1",
      "3/1",
      "2/1"
    ],
    "answer": "2/1"
  },
  {
    "id": 1906,
    "uuid": "98d8ecbf-b7dd-4c0a-97fa-68e298a5184e",
    "topic": "fractions",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.063957",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 9,
    "question": "Simplify: 9/7 + 8/9",
    "options": [
      "138/63",
      "140/63",
      "137/63",
      "135/63"
    ],
    "answer": "137/63"
  },
  {
    "id": 1908,
    "uuid": "6df5a1c6-0a28-49ce-8e56-e04abafea150",
    "topic": "operations",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.063978",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 8,
    "question": "What is 22 \u00f7 1 (integer division)?",
    "options": [
      "30",
      "22",
      "27",
      "29"
    ],
    "answer": "22"
  },
  {
    "id": 1911,
    "uuid": "1be8773b-5f7e-4604-9ddf-4428b43fbb08",
    "topic": "fractions",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.064032",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 6,
    "question": "Simplify: 1/7 + 1/8",
    "options": [
      "12/56",
      "13/56",
      "15/56",
      "16/56"
    ],
    "answer": "15/56"
  },
  {
    "id": 1917,
    "uuid": "88b4a15a-8f4a-472f-bf9a-74ee9b741761",
    "topic": "fractions",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.064089",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 10,
    "question": "Simplify: 2/4 + 6/8",
    "options": [
      "2/4",
      "8/4",
      "5/4",
      "6/4"
    ],
    "answer": "5/4"
  },
  {
    "id": 1920,
    "uuid": "d152506c-8ba5-4174-bda1-004757eae0b4",
    "topic": "fractions",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.064118",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 9,
    "question": "Simplify: 3/2 + 6/2",
    "options": [
      "9/2",
      "10/2",
      "11/2",
      "7/2"
    ],
    "answer": "9/2"
  },
  {
    "id": 1928,
    "uuid": "bd92492b-7a1f-4aa3-9167-b846b056d267",
    "topic": "operations",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.064180",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 8,
    "question": "What is 40 \u00d7 29?",
    "options": [
      "1169",
      "1162",
      "1152",
      "1160"
    ],
    "answer": "1160"
  },
  {
    "id": 1932,
    "uuid": "e2f87fcc-6912-44cc-b8e1-3e16add9ec32",
    "topic": "fractions",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.064215",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 7,
    "question": "Simplify: 6/5 + 8/2",
    "options": [
      "29/5",
      "26/5",
      "27/5",
      "28/5"
    ],
    "answer": "26/5"
  },
  {
    "id": 1933,
    "uuid": "17716215-4ab6-4115-8578-0a5f082556f8",
    "topic": "fractions",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.064231",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 10,
    "question": "Simplify: 4/7 + 1/6",
    "options": [
      "31/42",
      "34/42",
      "28/42",
      "33/42"
    ],
    "answer": "31/42"
  },
  {
    "id": 1935,
    "uuid": "08814381-9e0d-47ea-b10c-79d579d07cf8",
    "topic": "operations",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.064249",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 6,
    "question": "What is 2 + 44?",
    "options": [
      "46",
      "53",
      "44",
      "41"
    ],
    "answer": "46"
  },
  {
    "id": 1937,
    "uuid": "f9faea97-bd9f-4bbf-bdc8-b598f015355e",
    "topic": "fractions",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.064275",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 4,
    "question": "Simplify: 6/6 + 3/5",
    "options": [
      "9/5",
      "8/5",
      "10/5",
      "6/5"
    ],
    "answer": "8/5"
  },
  {
    "id": 1944,
    "uuid": "6aab7b85-4368-4685-92f6-40b0b2f9383e",
    "topic": "fractions",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.064330",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 9,
    "question": "Simplify: 3/8 + 4/5",
    "options": [
      "46/40",
      "50/40",
      "47/40",
      "48/40"
    ],
    "answer": "47/40"
  },
  {
    "id": 1953,
    "uuid": "87a109f4-b661-4a2e-89b6-027c18861192",
    "topic": "operations",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.064399",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 4,
    "question": "What is 13 \u00d7 34?",
    "options": [
      "439",
      "450",
      "440",
      "442"
    ],
    "answer": "442"
  },
  {
    "id": 1958,
    "uuid": "6d249036-16e7-4276-b335-c8c318fed3f1",
    "topic": "fractions",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.064441",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 8,
    "question": "Simplify: 6/5 + 7/9",
    "options": [
      "92/45",
      "91/45",
      "90/45",
      "89/45"
    ],
    "answer": "89/45"
  },
  {
    "id": 1960,
    "uuid": "cd8fb082-2980-4aec-980c-9647d21fcd6f",
    "topic": "operations",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.064457",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 3,
    "question": "What is 40 - 18?",
    "options": [
      "15",
      "32",
      "21",
      "22"
    ],
    "answer": "22"
  },
  {
    "id": 1965,
    "uuid": "d174803c-4784-4b26-ab23-52b05e8ad1b0",
    "topic": "fractions",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.064501",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 3,
    "question": "Simplify: 8/2 + 5/7",
    "options": [
      "34/7",
      "33/7",
      "31/7",
      "36/7"
    ],
    "answer": "33/7"
  },
  {
    "id": 1977,
    "uuid": "61f6fa95-baa1-4c74-9b78-7fb2f9d16fc3",
    "topic": "operations",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.064586",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 10,
    "question": "What is 9 + 1?",
    "options": [
      "1",
      "10",
      "9",
      "4"
    ],
    "answer": "10"
  },
  {
    "id": 1979,
    "uuid": "00dff508-2ded-4495-9fd9-2c6cb5bf85bc",
    "topic": "fractions",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.064609",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 9,
    "question": "Simplify: 2/7 + 6/3",
    "options": [
      "15/7",
      "16/7",
      "14/7",
      "13/7"
    ],
    "answer": "16/7"
  },
  {
    "id": 1989,
    "uuid": "2f82f696-f716-4849-af2e-fe21c3eade9c",
    "topic": "fractions",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.064721",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 3,
    "question": "Simplify: 6/6 + 4/3",
    "options": [
      "10/3",
      "7/3",
      "5/3",
      "8/3"
    ],
    "answer": "7/3"
  },
  {
    "id": 1992,
    "uuid": "835b83f8-20fa-4095-919b-e29d3af38bdd",
    "topic": "operations",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.064750",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 7,
    "question": "What is 41 + 20?",
    "options": [
      "52",
      "51",
      "63",
      "61"
    ],
    "answer": "61"
  },
  {
    "id": 1994,
    "uuid": "e61d91cc-a24a-466b-a8dc-a65b72075f97",
    "topic": "operations",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.064809",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 8,
    "question": "What is 35 \u00f7 13 (integer division)?",
    "options": [
      "-6",
      "6",
      "2",
      "8"
    ],
    "answer": "2"
  },
  {
    "id": 1997,
    "uuid": "a9caafed-10d1-40ec-9acb-1329c97dce3a",
    "topic": "fractions",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.064860",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 2,
    "question": "Simplify: 1/7 + 3/3",
    "options": [
      "11/7",
      "8/7",
      "9/7",
      "10/7"
    ],
    "answer": "8/7"
  },
  {
    "id": 2002,
    "uuid": "98792f57-40e3-4467-a16c-b814e5832922",
    "topic": "fractions",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.064929",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 7,
    "question": "Simplify: 1/7 + 3/4",
    "options": [
      "23/28",
      "26/28",
      "25/28",
      "27/28"
    ],
    "answer": "25/28"
  },
  {
    "id": 2015,
    "uuid": "881a6a30-7c53-42ef-a66e-3fd65f9b1cb3",
    "topic": "fractions",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.065047",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 2,
    "question": "Simplify: 3/9 + 2/4",
    "options": [
      "5/6",
      "2/6",
      "4/6",
      "3/6"
    ],
    "answer": "5/6"
  },
  {
    "id": 2017,
    "uuid": "6aff55a6-149e-4ddf-8a98-56fe2ceced59",
    "topic": "fractions",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.065074",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 7,
    "question": "Simplify: 9/5 + 3/4",
    "options": [
      "54/20",
      "48/20",
      "53/20",
      "51/20"
    ],
    "answer": "51/20"
  },
  {
    "id": 2018,
    "uuid": "2a6f92c3-45cb-4ee9-a5a9-1d75b9f6670e",
    "topic": "operations",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.065090",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 9,
    "question": "What is 36 - 13?",
    "options": [
      "23",
      "14",
      "21",
      "30"
    ],
    "answer": "23"
  },
  {
    "id": 2023,
    "uuid": "79852b3c-34a6-4530-a4fd-5b21ef8f2bed",
    "topic": "fractions",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.065139",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 2,
    "question": "Simplify: 4/8 + 1/2",
    "options": [
      "0/1",
      "-1/1",
      "1/1",
      "-2/1"
    ],
    "answer": "1/1"
  },
  {
    "id": 2032,
    "uuid": "d7502cf1-3ce1-4177-98d8-5fff906104fe",
    "topic": "operations",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.065216",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 2,
    "question": "What is 40 + 13?",
    "options": [
      "56",
      "61",
      "58",
      "53"
    ],
    "answer": "53"
  },
  {
    "id": 2034,
    "uuid": "8f9d1a56-5054-45bd-837c-c1d56afe882e",
    "topic": "fractions",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.065266",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 2,
    "question": "Simplify: 2/5 + 3/3",
    "options": [
      "10/5",
      "9/5",
      "5/5",
      "7/5"
    ],
    "answer": "7/5"
  },
  {
    "id": 2036,
    "uuid": "3c9daa1f-d27a-46f5-a84e-e069fb0215d8",
    "topic": "fractions",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.065292",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 10,
    "question": "Simplify: 1/3 + 1/9",
    "options": [
      "2/9",
      "6/9",
      "4/9",
      "3/9"
    ],
    "answer": "4/9"
  },
  {
    "id": 2041,
    "uuid": "d91e4ac4-79d6-4cbe-b308-2e2aadb3d104",
    "topic": "fractions",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.065342",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 5,
    "question": "Simplify: 8/6 + 9/3",
    "options": [
      "12/3",
      "16/3",
      "13/3",
      "11/3"
    ],
    "answer": "13/3"
  },
  {
    "id": 2042,
    "uuid": "0b66f166-d154-4efc-8d33-ff2cdfba6e78",
    "topic": "operations",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.065356",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 10,
    "question": "What is 36 \u00f7 17 (integer division)?",
    "options": [
      "-4",
      "10",
      "2",
      "-8"
    ],
    "answer": "2"
  },
  {
    "id": 2052,
    "uuid": "02965f0f-0e74-44e4-8f9c-14c223d5c93f",
    "topic": "operations",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.065451",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 9,
    "question": "What is 10 + 31?",
    "options": [
      "34",
      "41",
      "42",
      "44"
    ],
    "answer": "41"
  },
  {
    "id": 2054,
    "uuid": "9201279c-0622-430f-a217-8973198a4f14",
    "topic": "operations",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.065470",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 7,
    "question": "What is 11 + 39?",
    "options": [
      "54",
      "50",
      "42",
      "53"
    ],
    "answer": "50"
  },
  {
    "id": 2057,
    "uuid": "cfc4e6b6-6544-496c-b08f-54d03ace9222",
    "topic": "operations",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.065500",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 7,
    "question": "What is 15 \u00d7 45?",
    "options": [
      "668",
      "666",
      "672",
      "675"
    ],
    "answer": "675"
  },
  {
    "id": 2064,
    "uuid": "f0386079-1752-44c3-8980-ce6b134ed8d0",
    "topic": "fractions",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.065576",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "question": "Simplify: 5/9 + 7/2",
    "options": [
      "70/18",
      "76/18",
      "74/18",
      "73/18"
    ],
    "answer": "73/18"
  },
  {
    "id": 2078,
    "uuid": "05ccc7ff-49ac-4277-adcd-643894e1ca86",
    "topic": "operations",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.065715",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 4,
    "question": "What is 19 \u00d7 24?",
    "options": [
      "461",
      "455",
      "456",
      "452"
    ],
    "answer": "456"
  },
  {
    "id": 2079,
    "uuid": "607a5a6d-0aeb-4d00-b044-81420ef32f8f",
    "topic": "operations",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.065729",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 7,
    "question": "What is 2 \u00f7 6 (integer division)?",
    "options": [
      "0",
      "6",
      "1",
      "7"
    ],
    "answer": "0"
  },
  {
    "id": 2085,
    "uuid": "f44c5e17-fce5-4eeb-b0b3-2211002a61c0",
    "topic": "operations",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.065788",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 2,
    "question": "What is 3 \u00d7 4?",
    "options": [
      "5",
      "12",
      "14",
      "15"
    ],
    "answer": "12"
  },
  {
    "id": 2090,
    "uuid": "372d60ce-cfff-487f-ae01-54e8cc5b87f7",
    "topic": "operations",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.065841",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 10,
    "question": "What is 21 + 16?",
    "options": [
      "35",
      "32",
      "28",
      "37"
    ],
    "answer": "37"
  },
  {
    "id": 2099,
    "uuid": "b2922cce-1432-4c1e-acb5-0f5ea970ab21",
    "topic": "operations",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.065927",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 10,
    "question": "What is 32 \u00d7 31?",
    "options": [
      "987",
      "995",
      "992",
      "989"
    ],
    "answer": "992"
  },
  {
    "id": 2102,
    "uuid": "65990b68-7203-498b-bf30-23190f300288",
    "topic": "operations",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.065960",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 5,
    "question": "What is 33 - 30?",
    "options": [
      "-4",
      "-5",
      "6",
      "3"
    ],
    "answer": "3"
  },
  {
    "id": 2116,
    "uuid": "d8f3328c-5373-46c4-a1d9-a328a9d5e684",
    "topic": "operations",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.066083",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 10,
    "question": "What is 2 + 17?",
    "options": [
      "24",
      "11",
      "19",
      "22"
    ],
    "answer": "19"
  },
  {
    "id": 2121,
    "uuid": "2a16e53c-0b8a-4bd5-9fb2-6db3532f7f80",
    "topic": "operations",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.066131",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 7,
    "question": "What is 38 - 23?",
    "options": [
      "13",
      "8",
      "15",
      "7"
    ],
    "answer": "15"
  },
  {
    "id": 2122,
    "uuid": "05afa20f-24db-4895-8ef7-63cd009b18a4",
    "topic": "operations",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.066143",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 6,
    "question": "What is 32 - 36?",
    "options": [
      "-4",
      "1",
      "-5",
      "-9"
    ],
    "answer": "-4"
  },
  {
    "id": 2136,
    "uuid": "4fd600d0-fe2e-4a0e-a5aa-25a50fa77e88",
    "topic": "fractions",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.066303",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 2,
    "question": "Simplify: 9/9 + 2/8",
    "options": [
      "6/4",
      "2/4",
      "8/4",
      "5/4"
    ],
    "answer": "5/4"
  },
  {
    "id": 2139,
    "uuid": "715e594e-bb52-4579-a23b-578045a26dfa",
    "topic": "fractions",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.066345",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "question": "Simplify: 4/8 + 2/5",
    "options": [
      "7/10",
      "6/10",
      "9/10",
      "11/10"
    ],
    "answer": "9/10"
  },
  {
    "id": 2141,
    "uuid": "67fa4f96-2b93-4049-b025-b48b9c0110ea",
    "topic": "fractions",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.066374",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "question": "Simplify: 6/6 + 5/9",
    "options": [
      "11/9",
      "13/9",
      "12/9",
      "14/9"
    ],
    "answer": "14/9"
  },
  {
    "id": 2148,
    "uuid": "e7b3ad78-d836-4ec4-aa66-53b4420f6500",
    "topic": "fractions",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.066450",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 10,
    "question": "Simplify: 2/6 + 2/9",
    "options": [
      "6/9",
      "4/9",
      "8/9",
      "5/9"
    ],
    "answer": "5/9"
  },
  {
    "id": 2149,
    "uuid": "7379ae7c-9320-4461-a167-a7891e52e726",
    "topic": "fractions",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.066473",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 10,
    "question": "Simplify: 7/8 + 5/8",
    "options": [
      "3/2",
      "6/2",
      "5/2",
      "4/2"
    ],
    "answer": "3/2"
  },
  {
    "id": 2154,
    "uuid": "03904b8e-8a26-463c-93bb-bd9eddf57268",
    "topic": "fractions",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.066544",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 2,
    "question": "Simplify: 1/9 + 6/5",
    "options": [
      "56/45",
      "61/45",
      "58/45",
      "59/45"
    ],
    "answer": "59/45"
  },
  {
    "id": 2159,
    "uuid": "aeaa8d90-cbcd-4acc-ad61-bc2cdc8b07fe",
    "topic": "operations",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.066594",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 9,
    "question": "What is 25 + 32?",
    "options": [
      "66",
      "48",
      "57",
      "47"
    ],
    "answer": "57"
  },
  {
    "id": 2167,
    "uuid": "d92f74aa-f627-4a40-b34a-353cebb9d912",
    "topic": "operations",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.066696",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 4,
    "question": "What is 37 \u00d7 29?",
    "options": [
      "1069",
      "1079",
      "1070",
      "1073"
    ],
    "answer": "1073"
  },
  {
    "id": 2171,
    "uuid": "5a182d77-6f5b-45ed-849b-e18d0a4b65f8",
    "topic": "operations",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.066733",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 3,
    "question": "What is 7 \u00d7 26?",
    "options": [
      "183",
      "191",
      "179",
      "182"
    ],
    "answer": "182"
  },
  {
    "id": 2172,
    "uuid": "9f050a99-41e0-47b6-a4dd-16624154a21f",
    "topic": "fractions",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.066763",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 3,
    "question": "Simplify: 2/4 + 3/6",
    "options": [
      "1/1",
      "4/1",
      "-1/1",
      "3/1"
    ],
    "answer": "1/1"
  },
  {
    "id": 2175,
    "uuid": "a11c5e0b-c0a8-4cf7-ba67-9aea88a9c5d2",
    "topic": "fractions",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.066824",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 9,
    "question": "Simplify: 5/3 + 2/7",
    "options": [
      "44/21",
      "42/21",
      "41/21",
      "40/21"
    ],
    "answer": "41/21"
  },
  {
    "id": 2176,
    "uuid": "5a73b456-5c6d-447b-b2fd-53f862c77d46",
    "topic": "operations",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.066836",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 10,
    "question": "What is 7 \u00f7 16 (integer division)?",
    "options": [
      "-6",
      "7",
      "0",
      "5"
    ],
    "answer": "0"
  },
  {
    "id": 2178,
    "uuid": "e05ada79-a769-4daa-930d-5d57b96e7fbb",
    "topic": "operations",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.066854",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 2,
    "question": "What is 18 - 29?",
    "options": [
      "-8",
      "-13",
      "-11",
      "-16"
    ],
    "answer": "-11"
  },
  {
    "id": 2179,
    "uuid": "d814039e-8a6e-4894-b9c5-04ea4098a624",
    "topic": "fractions",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.066870",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 7,
    "question": "Simplify: 1/5 + 9/6",
    "options": [
      "19/10",
      "17/10",
      "15/10",
      "20/10"
    ],
    "answer": "17/10"
  },
  {
    "id": 2187,
    "uuid": "4782c35e-4088-4e13-89ff-ddbdd12eb46f",
    "topic": "fractions",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.066980",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 8,
    "question": "Simplify: 4/3 + 2/4",
    "options": [
      "9/6",
      "11/6",
      "13/6",
      "10/6"
    ],
    "answer": "11/6"
  },
  {
    "id": 2190,
    "uuid": "96520d74-e05d-443b-be10-d6644ec554cc",
    "topic": "fractions",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.067022",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 6,
    "question": "Simplify: 8/4 + 1/5",
    "options": [
      "12/5",
      "13/5",
      "11/5",
      "14/5"
    ],
    "answer": "11/5"
  },
  {
    "id": 2191,
    "uuid": "9da556c7-d2a1-4fc8-b1bf-bd37f8898593",
    "topic": "operations",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.067033",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 6,
    "question": "What is 42 + 35?",
    "options": [
      "86",
      "79",
      "77",
      "69"
    ],
    "answer": "77"
  },
  {
    "id": 2196,
    "uuid": "45ed916f-017d-47a1-9184-4b0fdbc89861",
    "topic": "operations",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.067072",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 9,
    "question": "What is 45 + 41?",
    "options": [
      "86",
      "78",
      "92",
      "88"
    ],
    "answer": "86"
  },
  {
    "id": 2203,
    "uuid": "53291ae7-3f11-4ba7-8aa8-c8459de73af4",
    "topic": "operations",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.067180",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 9,
    "question": "What is 42 \u00d7 44?",
    "options": [
      "1858",
      "1845",
      "1857",
      "1848"
    ],
    "answer": "1848"
  },
  {
    "id": 2214,
    "uuid": "07336361-a2f3-4aab-8d66-df40e48ad6ba",
    "topic": "fractions",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.067280",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 10,
    "question": "Simplify: 2/9 + 1/8",
    "options": [
      "26/72",
      "23/72",
      "25/72",
      "28/72"
    ],
    "answer": "25/72"
  },
  {
    "id": 2216,
    "uuid": "172c9da6-c2c5-4a5a-8599-8704315d010a",
    "topic": "fractions",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.067314",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 7,
    "question": "Simplify: 3/3 + 1/3",
    "options": [
      "4/3",
      "2/3",
      "1/3",
      "6/3"
    ],
    "answer": "4/3"
  },
  {
    "id": 2224,
    "uuid": "efa086c3-82c2-4386-891c-3ab62c249359",
    "topic": "operations",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.067379",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 6,
    "question": "What is 13 + 47?",
    "options": [
      "55",
      "62",
      "64",
      "60"
    ],
    "answer": "60"
  },
  {
    "id": 2226,
    "uuid": "89c60dfe-589b-4ea6-bedc-8959d334814e",
    "topic": "operations",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.067398",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 2,
    "question": "What is 28 \u00f7 14 (integer division)?",
    "options": [
      "2",
      "-6",
      "0",
      "-8"
    ],
    "answer": "2"
  },
  {
    "id": 2232,
    "uuid": "07d7325a-1d28-40f5-a807-6c373579c8fc",
    "topic": "operations",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.067445",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 7,
    "question": "What is 24 - 50?",
    "options": [
      "-23",
      "-26",
      "-30",
      "-19"
    ],
    "answer": "-26"
  },
  {
    "id": 2243,
    "uuid": "60b9378f-fdc9-4a6b-a380-fb5af02f07f5",
    "topic": "operations",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.067522",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 8,
    "question": "What is 45 - 39?",
    "options": [
      "6",
      "-4",
      "-2",
      "0"
    ],
    "answer": "6"
  },
  {
    "id": 2247,
    "uuid": "2b4c431e-4319-4c7a-8406-a79c9456882c",
    "topic": "operations",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.067553",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 2,
    "question": "What is 49 \u00d7 37?",
    "options": [
      "1813",
      "1817",
      "1807",
      "1805"
    ],
    "answer": "1813"
  },
  {
    "id": 2254,
    "uuid": "b881ce51-502e-4057-be69-94db1117ed98",
    "topic": "fractions",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.067625",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 5,
    "question": "Simplify: 3/4 + 8/7",
    "options": [
      "53/28",
      "54/28",
      "56/28",
      "50/28"
    ],
    "answer": "53/28"
  },
  {
    "id": 2255,
    "uuid": "7238c353-df8f-4639-b306-7c5b3edc0fb6",
    "topic": "fractions",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.067651",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "question": "Simplify: 2/7 + 5/7",
    "options": [
      "4/1",
      "1/1",
      "-2/1",
      "0/1"
    ],
    "answer": "1/1"
  },
  {
    "id": 2256,
    "uuid": "d86e2266-2762-4f9f-a000-e1010e3e17fd",
    "topic": "fractions",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.067667",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 4,
    "question": "Simplify: 3/7 + 8/2",
    "options": [
      "32/7",
      "33/7",
      "28/7",
      "31/7"
    ],
    "answer": "31/7"
  },
  {
    "id": 2263,
    "uuid": "8eb562b2-f58c-4d2e-a5a4-457c3e5a03c7",
    "topic": "operations",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.067718",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 8,
    "question": "What is 4 \u00f7 17 (integer division)?",
    "options": [
      "0",
      "-5",
      "6",
      "10"
    ],
    "answer": "0"
  },
  {
    "id": 2267,
    "uuid": "02cb3ae2-b58a-4008-9baf-1d6b89d920cf",
    "topic": "operations",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.067750",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 8,
    "question": "What is 23 + 36?",
    "options": [
      "51",
      "67",
      "59",
      "52"
    ],
    "answer": "59"
  },
  {
    "id": 2271,
    "uuid": "637e6d15-e974-4914-a32c-a2cdec545455",
    "topic": "fractions",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.067798",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "question": "Simplify: 4/2 + 1/9",
    "options": [
      "16/9",
      "19/9",
      "20/9",
      "22/9"
    ],
    "answer": "19/9"
  },
  {
    "id": 2283,
    "uuid": "9721566f-61eb-4822-88fc-3e9f4c9afacc",
    "topic": "fractions",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.067963",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 6,
    "question": "Simplify: 2/9 + 5/5",
    "options": [
      "13/9",
      "11/9",
      "14/9",
      "10/9"
    ],
    "answer": "11/9"
  },
  {
    "id": 2284,
    "uuid": "3b4d7647-a219-4044-9787-5081bb04e638",
    "topic": "fractions",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.068006",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 10,
    "question": "Simplify: 7/2 + 7/6",
    "options": [
      "11/3",
      "14/3",
      "15/3",
      "16/3"
    ],
    "answer": "14/3"
  },
  {
    "id": 2289,
    "uuid": "9c72fa3a-e5f1-4f6c-bb68-8d7313479e0a",
    "topic": "operations",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.068054",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 10,
    "question": "What is 22 + 22?",
    "options": [
      "44",
      "42",
      "48",
      "35"
    ],
    "answer": "44"
  },
  {
    "id": 2292,
    "uuid": "6a88e1eb-f6b8-469a-a0e3-806ebdc9e08d",
    "topic": "fractions",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.068091",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "question": "Simplify: 1/2 + 9/7",
    "options": [
      "22/14",
      "24/14",
      "28/14",
      "25/14"
    ],
    "answer": "25/14"
  },
  {
    "id": 2298,
    "uuid": "c6cc3738-9dee-42a9-bac2-eab71fd91bff",
    "topic": "operations",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.068144",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 4,
    "question": "What is 44 - 45?",
    "options": [
      "-1",
      "-6",
      "9",
      "-11"
    ],
    "answer": "-1"
  },
  {
    "id": 2301,
    "uuid": "a7706c41-9e76-4d95-9106-9ad5be31365e",
    "topic": "fractions",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.068191",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 2,
    "question": "Simplify: 3/9 + 6/7",
    "options": [
      "28/21",
      "25/21",
      "22/21",
      "23/21"
    ],
    "answer": "25/21"
  },
  {
    "id": 2304,
    "uuid": "a21263b1-2606-44b6-ac4b-020456352562",
    "topic": "fractions",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.068230",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 4,
    "question": "Simplify: 6/6 + 8/7",
    "options": [
      "14/7",
      "12/7",
      "15/7",
      "18/7"
    ],
    "answer": "15/7"
  },
  {
    "id": 2305,
    "uuid": "8e75fbec-5626-4178-8c61-42cf36569458",
    "topic": "fractions",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.068249",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 7,
    "question": "Simplify: 8/2 + 6/7",
    "options": [
      "36/7",
      "31/7",
      "32/7",
      "34/7"
    ],
    "answer": "34/7"
  },
  {
    "id": 2308,
    "uuid": "e5baaefe-dd90-4a9d-bcd2-523fb5dc8183",
    "topic": "operations",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.068286",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 10,
    "question": "What is 14 + 28?",
    "options": [
      "51",
      "48",
      "41",
      "42"
    ],
    "answer": "42"
  },
  {
    "id": 2310,
    "uuid": "f9c2f866-b191-4928-9cf9-5d5f29545f1c",
    "topic": "fractions",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.068319",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 6,
    "question": "Simplify: 9/7 + 6/5",
    "options": [
      "86/35",
      "88/35",
      "87/35",
      "89/35"
    ],
    "answer": "87/35"
  },
  {
    "id": 2313,
    "uuid": "6565523e-897d-4ae5-8e2a-fd5afdd0b062",
    "topic": "operations",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.068348",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 8,
    "question": "What is 42 \u00f7 19 (integer division)?",
    "options": [
      "-7",
      "5",
      "9",
      "2"
    ],
    "answer": "2"
  },
  {
    "id": 2315,
    "uuid": "846f3bc8-e4f1-41bd-a903-20bf3ed72cd9",
    "topic": "operations",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.068367",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 4,
    "question": "What is 50 - 45?",
    "options": [
      "3",
      "5",
      "11",
      "10"
    ],
    "answer": "5"
  },
  {
    "id": 2319,
    "uuid": "0373a6d9-d2a3-4b0c-b482-fc7246ed7116",
    "topic": "operations",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.068405",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 5,
    "question": "What is 14 \u00d7 11?",
    "options": [
      "154",
      "146",
      "159",
      "144"
    ],
    "answer": "154"
  },
  {
    "id": 2320,
    "uuid": "5584b4e5-e191-4e4e-89af-e061c49f21bd",
    "topic": "fractions",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.068429",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 10,
    "question": "Simplify: 7/4 + 5/3",
    "options": [
      "42/12",
      "39/12",
      "40/12",
      "41/12"
    ],
    "answer": "41/12"
  },
  {
    "id": 2321,
    "uuid": "ad12b37a-a0c9-45a0-a09f-e0fd868e1dfd",
    "topic": "fractions",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.068453",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 7,
    "question": "Simplify: 4/5 + 5/7",
    "options": [
      "56/35",
      "55/35",
      "50/35",
      "53/35"
    ],
    "answer": "53/35"
  },
  {
    "id": 2322,
    "uuid": "8195b21c-2527-4cfc-baa7-473a8780e88a",
    "topic": "operations",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.068466",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 3,
    "question": "What is 23 + 16?",
    "options": [
      "49",
      "42",
      "39",
      "46"
    ],
    "answer": "39"
  },
  {
    "id": 2325,
    "uuid": "cb89fce8-7029-44ec-9e70-0627824099f2",
    "topic": "operations",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.068496",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 2,
    "question": "What is 19 \u00d7 44?",
    "options": [
      "844",
      "836",
      "840",
      "843"
    ],
    "answer": "836"
  },
  {
    "id": 2326,
    "uuid": "37505ab8-62da-4e21-bd35-edcae132568d",
    "topic": "fractions",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.068515",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "question": "Simplify: 7/6 + 3/8",
    "options": [
      "35/24",
      "37/24",
      "40/24",
      "34/24"
    ],
    "answer": "37/24"
  },
  {
    "id": 2327,
    "uuid": "dc6669b5-ad8f-4712-8aaf-0f60804f4b6f",
    "topic": "fractions",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.068546",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 2,
    "question": "Simplify: 8/7 + 6/4",
    "options": [
      "36/14",
      "39/14",
      "37/14",
      "34/14"
    ],
    "answer": "37/14"
  },
  {
    "id": 2329,
    "uuid": "cb8b8a75-fa67-47f1-9ad3-6e6a7e1ee086",
    "topic": "operations",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.068567",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 9,
    "question": "What is 12 \u00f7 6 (integer division)?",
    "options": [
      "12",
      "11",
      "2",
      "-5"
    ],
    "answer": "2"
  },
  {
    "id": 2337,
    "uuid": "678cbcb0-6402-4361-913d-30cf80fe9a70",
    "topic": "fractions",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.068648",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 9,
    "question": "Simplify: 2/8 + 9/2",
    "options": [
      "22/4",
      "21/4",
      "19/4",
      "16/4"
    ],
    "answer": "19/4"
  },
  {
    "id": 2342,
    "uuid": "cc3b849f-4e62-4cc5-8ee2-8113e9f0c5e0",
    "topic": "operations",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.068696",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 10,
    "question": "What is 43 - 7?",
    "options": [
      "31",
      "41",
      "26",
      "36"
    ],
    "answer": "36"
  },
  {
    "id": 2345,
    "uuid": "9944b54a-ba62-4eaa-9723-b8fe561186ed",
    "topic": "fractions",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.068739",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 3,
    "question": "Simplify: 9/3 + 2/8",
    "options": [
      "15/4",
      "13/4",
      "14/4",
      "12/4"
    ],
    "answer": "13/4"
  },
  {
    "id": 2346,
    "uuid": "a61c4e5d-d5d6-434d-ad41-4ab7c48762c6",
    "topic": "operations",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.068752",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 8,
    "question": "What is 9 - 3?",
    "options": [
      "0",
      "4",
      "6",
      "-3"
    ],
    "answer": "6"
  },
  {
    "id": 2348,
    "uuid": "0ddc3a52-6830-4df9-a295-8c110fedd531",
    "topic": "fractions",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.068788",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "question": "Simplify: 2/5 + 6/5",
    "options": [
      "6/5",
      "11/5",
      "5/5",
      "8/5"
    ],
    "answer": "8/5"
  },
  {
    "id": 2350,
    "uuid": "947f952d-084c-4eb6-b0de-1da77d13b2f2",
    "topic": "operations",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.068811",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 3,
    "question": "What is 23 - 46?",
    "options": [
      "-19",
      "-21",
      "-22",
      "-23"
    ],
    "answer": "-23"
  },
  {
    "id": 2354,
    "uuid": "3b2a8997-f4d3-4da1-b80c-0d7b573264d2",
    "topic": "operations",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.068853",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 10,
    "question": "What is 17 \u00d7 16?",
    "options": [
      "264",
      "281",
      "272",
      "274"
    ],
    "answer": "272"
  },
  {
    "id": 2356,
    "uuid": "789e9728-8089-4839-9b43-8a9e267771b4",
    "topic": "operations",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.068875",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "question": "What is 33 \u00d7 4?",
    "options": [
      "132",
      "139",
      "134",
      "133"
    ],
    "answer": "132"
  },
  {
    "id": 2365,
    "uuid": "35f252f7-dae7-4e21-8254-e35067662dd3",
    "topic": "fractions",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.069023",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 3,
    "question": "Simplify: 7/4 + 7/3",
    "options": [
      "47/12",
      "46/12",
      "49/12",
      "48/12"
    ],
    "answer": "49/12"
  },
  {
    "id": 2368,
    "uuid": "63016a84-87ad-40d4-9431-013752fc3d54",
    "topic": "fractions",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.069080",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 5,
    "question": "Simplify: 2/2 + 9/9",
    "options": [
      "3/1",
      "4/1",
      "2/1",
      "-1/1"
    ],
    "answer": "2/1"
  },
  {
    "id": 2372,
    "uuid": "7b0fcd12-9a6e-40c2-9fa8-e73f79330b28",
    "topic": "fractions",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.069124",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 5,
    "question": "Simplify: 5/9 + 3/7",
    "options": [
      "61/63",
      "59/63",
      "62/63",
      "64/63"
    ],
    "answer": "62/63"
  },
  {
    "id": 2376,
    "uuid": "1e329a0d-4323-4155-9d87-276f652bb61e",
    "topic": "operations",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.069163",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 8,
    "question": "What is 24 \u00d7 47?",
    "options": [
      "1128",
      "1130",
      "1129",
      "1132"
    ],
    "answer": "1128"
  },
  {
    "id": 2382,
    "uuid": "70bba81b-40cf-4355-a930-445e9422c18d",
    "topic": "fractions",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.069222",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 9,
    "question": "Simplify: 6/6 + 6/2",
    "options": [
      "4/1",
      "5/1",
      "1/1",
      "6/1"
    ],
    "answer": "4/1"
  },
  {
    "id": 2384,
    "uuid": "4d048f6c-cf8b-4370-b9d5-be304fefa546",
    "topic": "fractions",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.069249",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 8,
    "question": "Simplify: 6/7 + 7/8",
    "options": [
      "96/56",
      "100/56",
      "95/56",
      "97/56"
    ],
    "answer": "97/56"
  },
  {
    "id": 2386,
    "uuid": "7e3f6eb2-c71f-4424-b488-30bd9b62461f",
    "topic": "fractions",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.069283",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 7,
    "question": "Simplify: 7/3 + 5/2",
    "options": [
      "30/6",
      "28/6",
      "29/6",
      "31/6"
    ],
    "answer": "29/6"
  },
  {
    "id": 2390,
    "uuid": "01e5b5fa-c0ee-4359-afe2-a6ef4138168a",
    "topic": "fractions",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.069332",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 4,
    "question": "Simplify: 3/3 + 2/7",
    "options": [
      "6/7",
      "9/7",
      "11/7",
      "10/7"
    ],
    "answer": "9/7"
  },
  {
    "id": 2392,
    "uuid": "55b3acf4-71a2-4716-b637-28fb634d5497",
    "topic": "fractions",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.069374",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 3,
    "question": "Simplify: 7/9 + 5/6",
    "options": [
      "31/18",
      "26/18",
      "32/18",
      "29/18"
    ],
    "answer": "29/18"
  },
  {
    "id": 2393,
    "uuid": "71d13ee5-6887-4a76-89cc-e4b1b1d9e825",
    "topic": "operations",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.069388",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 10,
    "question": "What is 45 \u00f7 11 (integer division)?",
    "options": [
      "1",
      "4",
      "-2",
      "8"
    ],
    "answer": "4"
  },
  {
    "id": 2396,
    "uuid": "90f98461-d0a7-449b-99f4-eafda5f58140",
    "topic": "operations",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.069418",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "question": "What is 8 + 18?",
    "options": [
      "17",
      "26",
      "27",
      "36"
    ],
    "answer": "26"
  },
  {
    "id": 2402,
    "uuid": "5054f4ca-5106-4df2-b4b4-f919cb878e09",
    "topic": "fractions",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.069497",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 3,
    "question": "Simplify: 1/5 + 2/5",
    "options": [
      "3/5",
      "5/5",
      "2/5",
      "4/5"
    ],
    "answer": "3/5"
  },
  {
    "id": 2403,
    "uuid": "3a7da114-a6a6-43c1-a933-134f13d93b51",
    "topic": "operations",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.069511",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 6,
    "question": "What is 39 - 42?",
    "options": [
      "7",
      "-3",
      "2",
      "5"
    ],
    "answer": "-3"
  },
  {
    "id": 2406,
    "uuid": "d2960d7d-6022-4921-a7df-6b3b51a7d0fa",
    "topic": "fractions",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.069557",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 6,
    "question": "Simplify: 8/5 + 4/4",
    "options": [
      "10/5",
      "13/5",
      "12/5",
      "16/5"
    ],
    "answer": "13/5"
  },
  {
    "id": 2417,
    "uuid": "619d9e0a-4b4d-45cd-bc99-7b016fcca94b",
    "topic": "fractions",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.069671",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 6,
    "question": "Simplify: 2/9 + 7/6",
    "options": [
      "28/18",
      "25/18",
      "26/18",
      "24/18"
    ],
    "answer": "25/18"
  },
  {
    "id": 2419,
    "uuid": "5ec81adc-315c-476d-92a7-d4c388b9ad84",
    "topic": "fractions",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.069698",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 10,
    "question": "Simplify: 3/5 + 4/4",
    "options": [
      "6/5",
      "9/5",
      "10/5",
      "8/5"
    ],
    "answer": "8/5"
  },
  {
    "id": 2421,
    "uuid": "5270bd85-0773-4d43-a84a-93ef3ce8fa52",
    "topic": "fractions",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.069731",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "question": "Simplify: 6/8 + 1/8",
    "options": [
      "8/8",
      "5/8",
      "7/8",
      "10/8"
    ],
    "answer": "7/8"
  },
  {
    "id": 2426,
    "uuid": "382c7076-4828-4db6-9761-3401fe9f9197",
    "topic": "operations",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.069798",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 4,
    "question": "What is 43 - 5?",
    "options": [
      "38",
      "40",
      "29",
      "33"
    ],
    "answer": "38"
  },
  {
    "id": 2429,
    "uuid": "f65a24df-7d0d-430e-b93b-7b30a602158c",
    "topic": "operations",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.069827",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 7,
    "question": "What is 24 \u00d7 21?",
    "options": [
      "496",
      "499",
      "512",
      "504"
    ],
    "answer": "504"
  },
  {
    "id": 2431,
    "uuid": "80262fee-2a10-47ce-a827-196ea3a00999",
    "topic": "operations",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.069852",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 6,
    "question": "What is 37 + 43?",
    "options": [
      "80",
      "76",
      "88",
      "82"
    ],
    "answer": "80"
  },
  {
    "id": 2432,
    "uuid": "e974afcc-bc4f-4af1-9ae0-ae0fa99ea324",
    "topic": "fractions",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.069873",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 2,
    "question": "Simplify: 1/9 + 1/4",
    "options": [
      "10/36",
      "12/36",
      "13/36",
      "11/36"
    ],
    "answer": "13/36"
  },
  {
    "id": 2434,
    "uuid": "b2a64fd5-0a5b-4b98-bb83-94baf5325e9f",
    "topic": "fractions",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.069901",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 8,
    "question": "Simplify: 2/4 + 5/3",
    "options": [
      "13/6",
      "11/6",
      "14/6",
      "16/6"
    ],
    "answer": "13/6"
  },
  {
    "id": 2437,
    "uuid": "17a49aa6-355a-46b4-91b5-982093e8351a",
    "topic": "operations",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.069926",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 2,
    "question": "What is 37 \u00f7 7 (integer division)?",
    "options": [
      "0",
      "5",
      "-3",
      "8"
    ],
    "answer": "5"
  },
  {
    "id": 2438,
    "uuid": "a224a148-043f-4a8d-a4ac-b69a1a8ced36",
    "topic": "fractions",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.069942",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 6,
    "question": "Simplify: 3/9 + 7/2",
    "options": [
      "23/6",
      "22/6",
      "25/6",
      "24/6"
    ],
    "answer": "23/6"
  },
  {
    "id": 2442,
    "uuid": "82559b02-8eaf-436e-b985-75d5443073fb",
    "topic": "fractions",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.070004",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 5,
    "question": "Simplify: 1/4 + 2/3",
    "options": [
      "11/12",
      "8/12",
      "10/12",
      "14/12"
    ],
    "answer": "11/12"
  },
  {
    "id": 2449,
    "uuid": "1596a808-d2e3-440c-a77e-9dd22b2483a1",
    "topic": "operations",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.070063",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 5,
    "question": "What is 27 \u00d7 16?",
    "options": [
      "428",
      "429",
      "437",
      "432"
    ],
    "answer": "432"
  },
  {
    "id": 2455,
    "uuid": "f7f5f8f6-1a6f-4287-9bfa-41e024acac1d",
    "topic": "fractions",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.070127",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 4,
    "question": "Simplify: 6/7 + 2/4",
    "options": [
      "19/14",
      "17/14",
      "21/14",
      "20/14"
    ],
    "answer": "19/14"
  },
  {
    "id": 2471,
    "uuid": "27016954-e886-4d95-b341-c373c688f864",
    "topic": "operations",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.070696",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 7,
    "question": "What is 45 + 12?",
    "options": [
      "56",
      "62",
      "57",
      "48"
    ],
    "answer": "57"
  },
  {
    "id": 2474,
    "uuid": "ff16f233-780b-481d-83a9-9fd025883104",
    "topic": "fractions",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.070748",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 2,
    "question": "Simplify: 3/2 + 4/2",
    "options": [
      "7/2",
      "6/2",
      "4/2",
      "8/2"
    ],
    "answer": "7/2"
  },
  {
    "id": 2475,
    "uuid": "160f501b-8f8e-49b2-a071-28b5911772bc",
    "topic": "fractions",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.070783",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 4,
    "question": "Simplify: 4/2 + 1/4",
    "options": [
      "11/4",
      "12/4",
      "8/4",
      "9/4"
    ],
    "answer": "9/4"
  },
  {
    "id": 2480,
    "uuid": "83c6f063-7255-4044-8741-cbeedfee9d9b",
    "topic": "operations",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.070839",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 9,
    "question": "What is 36 + 28?",
    "options": [
      "60",
      "73",
      "72",
      "64"
    ],
    "answer": "64"
  },
  {
    "id": 2485,
    "uuid": "55bd8764-e205-462e-9a73-7981d2e86f9b",
    "topic": "fractions",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.070909",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 4,
    "question": "Simplify: 1/5 + 4/6",
    "options": [
      "11/15",
      "12/15",
      "15/15",
      "13/15"
    ],
    "answer": "13/15"
  },
  {
    "id": 2489,
    "uuid": "2515120b-e967-4429-8809-ee6fd8235706",
    "topic": "fractions",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.070975",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 2,
    "question": "Simplify: 5/8 + 1/4",
    "options": [
      "7/8",
      "9/8",
      "10/8",
      "4/8"
    ],
    "answer": "7/8"
  },
  {
    "id": 2493,
    "uuid": "a133dc25-ce3e-460d-9dd2-e9ad93b360ce",
    "topic": "fractions",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.071042",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 6,
    "question": "Simplify: 4/7 + 1/4",
    "options": [
      "23/28",
      "24/28",
      "21/28",
      "26/28"
    ],
    "answer": "23/28"
  },
  {
    "id": 2494,
    "uuid": "881911c0-cbcb-4f58-b8b4-85f599b9c6bd",
    "topic": "fractions",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.071071",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "question": "Simplify: 8/7 + 3/5",
    "options": [
      "64/35",
      "62/35",
      "61/35",
      "59/35"
    ],
    "answer": "61/35"
  },
  {
    "id": 2495,
    "uuid": "04ad0def-6a70-43a7-acf3-7ac7670b0c2f",
    "topic": "fractions",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.071099",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 2,
    "question": "Simplify: 6/8 + 2/5",
    "options": [
      "23/20",
      "20/20",
      "21/20",
      "22/20"
    ],
    "answer": "23/20"
  },
  {
    "id": 2497,
    "uuid": "c650eec4-3b61-482c-81f6-884d74726b70",
    "topic": "operations",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.071122",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 3,
    "question": "What is 29 - 28?",
    "options": [
      "6",
      "2",
      "1",
      "10"
    ],
    "answer": "1"
  },
  {
    "id": 2505,
    "uuid": "4c52b1c2-d530-4107-9314-27620f68b391",
    "topic": "fractions",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.071211",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 2,
    "question": "Simplify: 3/6 + 1/7",
    "options": [
      "9/14",
      "12/14",
      "6/14",
      "11/14"
    ],
    "answer": "9/14"
  },
  {
    "id": 2509,
    "uuid": "7899607c-53d8-4057-894c-6bb2150be879",
    "topic": "operations",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.071243",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 6,
    "question": "What is 25 - 24?",
    "options": [
      "8",
      "1",
      "5",
      "-5"
    ],
    "answer": "1"
  },
  {
    "id": 2511,
    "uuid": "bab7c468-0c32-4ee5-9205-361e9a72c045",
    "topic": "fractions",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.071292",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 4,
    "question": "Simplify: 3/7 + 1/7",
    "options": [
      "7/7",
      "4/7",
      "3/7",
      "5/7"
    ],
    "answer": "4/7"
  },
  {
    "id": 2516,
    "uuid": "698ef77d-74c3-46f0-8092-90cf11edd26e",
    "topic": "operations",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.071343",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 8,
    "question": "What is 16 \u00d7 45?",
    "options": [
      "727",
      "729",
      "723",
      "720"
    ],
    "answer": "720"
  },
  {
    "id": 2517,
    "uuid": "4c8f31a4-12cd-4815-bf33-cb27ce862408",
    "topic": "operations",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.071355",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 10,
    "question": "What is 32 + 19?",
    "options": [
      "48",
      "51",
      "60",
      "61"
    ],
    "answer": "51"
  },
  {
    "id": 2522,
    "uuid": "6a45cb41-33df-4e9f-8aa0-03ef8106a1c2",
    "topic": "fractions",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.071449",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 10,
    "question": "Simplify: 1/7 + 5/4",
    "options": [
      "39/28",
      "37/28",
      "41/28",
      "36/28"
    ],
    "answer": "39/28"
  },
  {
    "id": 2535,
    "uuid": "ab2b5bc4-5c59-4d12-a5a0-a049d41fc342",
    "topic": "fractions",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.071577",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "question": "Simplify: 3/7 + 3/2",
    "options": [
      "24/14",
      "26/14",
      "28/14",
      "27/14"
    ],
    "answer": "27/14"
  },
  {
    "id": 2537,
    "uuid": "44914490-776a-4fb4-8099-a5ff4ac2c8fc",
    "topic": "fractions",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.071612",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 6,
    "question": "Simplify: 3/6 + 2/3",
    "options": [
      "10/6",
      "6/6",
      "5/6",
      "7/6"
    ],
    "answer": "7/6"
  },
  {
    "id": 2539,
    "uuid": "8762a322-cb7a-4136-bb6f-58527b28dd42",
    "topic": "fractions",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.071650",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 9,
    "question": "Simplify: 7/4 + 5/4",
    "options": [
      "0/1",
      "3/1",
      "5/1",
      "2/1"
    ],
    "answer": "3/1"
  },
  {
    "id": 2543,
    "uuid": "21f01805-ee9b-4bd1-b02e-ba5b75afe752",
    "topic": "operations",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.071682",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 2,
    "question": "What is 3 - 18?",
    "options": [
      "-20",
      "-23",
      "-5",
      "-15"
    ],
    "answer": "-15"
  },
  {
    "id": 2544,
    "uuid": "b4e0a9c1-0400-43e7-a898-344af0a6303c",
    "topic": "fractions",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.071699",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 9,
    "question": "Simplify: 2/7 + 5/3",
    "options": [
      "41/21",
      "40/21",
      "42/21",
      "43/21"
    ],
    "answer": "41/21"
  },
  {
    "id": 2548,
    "uuid": "4eba11b8-8e23-41e0-b867-234e02990e93",
    "topic": "operations",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.071756",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 8,
    "question": "What is 25 \u00d7 20?",
    "options": [
      "490",
      "494",
      "500",
      "491"
    ],
    "answer": "500"
  },
  {
    "id": 2555,
    "uuid": "1399a224-e547-4467-b59c-bb0a0cbe1d20",
    "topic": "fractions",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.071875",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 10,
    "question": "Simplify: 2/5 + 3/2",
    "options": [
      "21/10",
      "16/10",
      "18/10",
      "19/10"
    ],
    "answer": "19/10"
  },
  {
    "id": 2563,
    "uuid": "b4f70985-2395-4d3c-87b4-882249b6d975",
    "topic": "operations",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.071947",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "question": "What is 1 - 23?",
    "options": [
      "-27",
      "-15",
      "-22",
      "-26"
    ],
    "answer": "-22"
  },
  {
    "id": 2571,
    "uuid": "de6346d0-8558-4475-8bb4-5b0f53bbd2fd",
    "topic": "fractions",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.072039",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 4,
    "question": "Simplify: 8/8 + 4/5",
    "options": [
      "9/5",
      "10/5",
      "12/5",
      "7/5"
    ],
    "answer": "9/5"
  },
  {
    "id": 2577,
    "uuid": "ff51208e-2097-4767-a399-1cc51c5f41bf",
    "topic": "fractions",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.072121",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 8,
    "question": "Simplify: 4/5 + 3/3",
    "options": [
      "10/5",
      "9/5",
      "12/5",
      "11/5"
    ],
    "answer": "9/5"
  },
  {
    "id": 2580,
    "uuid": "645cd2f0-84b1-4199-80fa-64023641f196",
    "topic": "operations",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.072152",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 4,
    "question": "What is 28 \u00d7 49?",
    "options": [
      "1362",
      "1380",
      "1367",
      "1372"
    ],
    "answer": "1372"
  },
  {
    "id": 2586,
    "uuid": "116ba130-59b8-4ba4-847c-1a7d5645126f",
    "topic": "operations",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.072198",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 10,
    "question": "What is 46 - 47?",
    "options": [
      "0",
      "1",
      "-1",
      "6"
    ],
    "answer": "-1"
  },
  {
    "id": 2590,
    "uuid": "27cdd3a1-51c5-418c-9298-900c87d82668",
    "topic": "operations",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.072234",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 10,
    "question": "What is 29 \u00f7 5 (integer division)?",
    "options": [
      "13",
      "14",
      "5",
      "8"
    ],
    "answer": "5"
  },
  {
    "id": 2604,
    "uuid": "a0ddbdbf-6d26-4f97-9667-cdc04120dbd9",
    "topic": "operations",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.072355",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "question": "What is 11 - 26?",
    "options": [
      "-24",
      "-15",
      "-11",
      "-13"
    ],
    "answer": "-15"
  },
  {
    "id": 2607,
    "uuid": "f5eff578-43a7-40f3-996b-baaa9d629ab4",
    "topic": "operations",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.072382",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 5,
    "question": "What is 36 - 35?",
    "options": [
      "1",
      "0",
      "6",
      "-8"
    ],
    "answer": "1"
  },
  {
    "id": 2609,
    "uuid": "bbdb96d2-49ab-4d2e-948d-0d804ff40049",
    "topic": "operations",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.072401",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 7,
    "question": "What is 10 \u00d7 29?",
    "options": [
      "286",
      "280",
      "281",
      "290"
    ],
    "answer": "290"
  },
  {
    "id": 2611,
    "uuid": "758216e4-8cbf-4217-8105-63be1976b38e",
    "topic": "operations",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.072419",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 7,
    "question": "What is 23 \u00d7 25?",
    "options": [
      "575",
      "582",
      "573",
      "568"
    ],
    "answer": "575"
  },
  {
    "id": 2613,
    "uuid": "f490e1ee-7f02-4dcc-96d2-19ee2b4e3fef",
    "topic": "operations",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.072451",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "question": "What is 33 \u00f7 1 (integer division)?",
    "options": [
      "26",
      "43",
      "33",
      "39"
    ],
    "answer": "33"
  },
  {
    "id": 2614,
    "uuid": "39f733ec-f960-4c39-b087-a1f1e7d4351e",
    "topic": "operations",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.072464",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 5,
    "question": "What is 8 - 41?",
    "options": [
      "-32",
      "-30",
      "-40",
      "-33"
    ],
    "answer": "-33"
  },
  {
    "id": 2622,
    "uuid": "c8ac008e-1b60-4a2f-aece-f70dee58b6cd",
    "topic": "fractions",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.072550",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 5,
    "question": "Simplify: 3/4 + 2/2",
    "options": [
      "9/4",
      "7/4",
      "6/4",
      "5/4"
    ],
    "answer": "7/4"
  },
  {
    "id": 2630,
    "uuid": "6a963965-248d-4c15-97ad-2f15b6a0972e",
    "topic": "fractions",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.072612",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 7,
    "question": "Simplify: 5/7 + 6/5",
    "options": [
      "64/35",
      "65/35",
      "69/35",
      "67/35"
    ],
    "answer": "67/35"
  },
  {
    "id": 2631,
    "uuid": "9cda715c-a97b-4801-952d-687d818e8da7",
    "topic": "fractions",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.072628",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 8,
    "question": "Simplify: 3/3 + 2/9",
    "options": [
      "11/9",
      "13/9",
      "14/9",
      "9/9"
    ],
    "answer": "11/9"
  },
  {
    "id": 2632,
    "uuid": "a1067ef7-b535-4362-a845-2b60118fb652",
    "topic": "fractions",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.072648",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 3,
    "question": "Simplify: 7/6 + 9/5",
    "options": [
      "89/30",
      "90/30",
      "91/30",
      "88/30"
    ],
    "answer": "89/30"
  },
  {
    "id": 2633,
    "uuid": "99a44580-0918-45e1-bd39-28c4c549424d",
    "topic": "fractions",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.072663",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 9,
    "question": "Simplify: 5/4 + 6/4",
    "options": [
      "14/4",
      "10/4",
      "13/4",
      "11/4"
    ],
    "answer": "11/4"
  },
  {
    "id": 2637,
    "uuid": "1bc9a8b2-33c0-4cce-88e7-1c91eb3d89ee",
    "topic": "operations",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.072698",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 8,
    "question": "What is 34 + 41?",
    "options": [
      "84",
      "74",
      "76",
      "75"
    ],
    "answer": "75"
  },
  {
    "id": 2639,
    "uuid": "ab392e1c-84ed-4e58-a7dd-04769a395f4f",
    "topic": "fractions",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.072729",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 4,
    "question": "Simplify: 5/9 + 9/6",
    "options": [
      "37/18",
      "34/18",
      "36/18",
      "40/18"
    ],
    "answer": "37/18"
  },
  {
    "id": 2647,
    "uuid": "586b67af-a5e1-4456-8e4d-142cd62941e4",
    "topic": "fractions",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.072808",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 8,
    "question": "Simplify: 7/2 + 9/9",
    "options": [
      "7/2",
      "12/2",
      "10/2",
      "9/2"
    ],
    "answer": "9/2"
  },
  {
    "id": 2651,
    "uuid": "457c19cb-d04b-4f05-ab40-ec6c106be4eb",
    "topic": "fractions",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.072867",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 6,
    "question": "Simplify: 6/3 + 6/4",
    "options": [
      "9/2",
      "7/2",
      "4/2",
      "6/2"
    ],
    "answer": "7/2"
  },
  {
    "id": 2653,
    "uuid": "4a6386bc-f4e3-4abc-84ae-205024551697",
    "topic": "operations",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.072886",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 7,
    "question": "What is 7 + 33?",
    "options": [
      "40",
      "43",
      "45",
      "41"
    ],
    "answer": "40"
  },
  {
    "id": 2658,
    "uuid": "8f8c5b22-c183-4bc9-bdd6-3f9c6a8c9502",
    "topic": "fractions",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.072961",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 2,
    "question": "Simplify: 5/8 + 7/6",
    "options": [
      "42/24",
      "44/24",
      "40/24",
      "43/24"
    ],
    "answer": "43/24"
  },
  {
    "id": 2659,
    "uuid": "1b3ded09-b47d-4fe4-89d6-485c86726eed",
    "topic": "operations",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.072972",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 6,
    "question": "What is 35 \u00d7 39?",
    "options": [
      "1370",
      "1373",
      "1362",
      "1365"
    ],
    "answer": "1365"
  },
  {
    "id": 2660,
    "uuid": "fb0dce91-8bf0-45d1-baf6-6ea10a951c0a",
    "topic": "fractions",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.072989",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 7,
    "question": "Simplify: 2/3 + 9/8",
    "options": [
      "42/24",
      "45/24",
      "43/24",
      "44/24"
    ],
    "answer": "43/24"
  },
  {
    "id": 2663,
    "uuid": "51c184de-93be-43f1-993b-27bf178dbd75",
    "topic": "fractions",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.073022",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 10,
    "question": "Simplify: 9/7 + 8/7",
    "options": [
      "16/7",
      "17/7",
      "18/7",
      "19/7"
    ],
    "answer": "17/7"
  },
  {
    "id": 2664,
    "uuid": "7a964103-5498-4f7a-8d1e-d79ef343e192",
    "topic": "operations",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.073033",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 9,
    "question": "What is 12 + 10?",
    "options": [
      "30",
      "26",
      "29",
      "22"
    ],
    "answer": "22"
  },
  {
    "id": 2671,
    "uuid": "d7982614-4521-4657-a40e-e42b7b3cc394",
    "topic": "fractions",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.073112",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 4,
    "question": "Simplify: 9/8 + 9/3",
    "options": [
      "35/8",
      "33/8",
      "31/8",
      "30/8"
    ],
    "answer": "33/8"
  },
  {
    "id": 2677,
    "uuid": "0c58faed-cd90-4bb6-bbe6-31bc9a37821c",
    "topic": "fractions",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.073185",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 4,
    "question": "Simplify: 2/9 + 8/2",
    "options": [
      "36/9",
      "38/9",
      "37/9",
      "39/9"
    ],
    "answer": "38/9"
  },
  {
    "id": 2683,
    "uuid": "5e0bb23e-e81d-42a5-ba5e-796c7c51cf45",
    "topic": "fractions",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.073243",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 9,
    "question": "Simplify: 7/2 + 2/3",
    "options": [
      "26/6",
      "23/6",
      "28/6",
      "25/6"
    ],
    "answer": "25/6"
  },
  {
    "id": 2684,
    "uuid": "5737d9ef-0b3c-4fd9-9271-0a09ac3d4d4c",
    "topic": "fractions",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.073259",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 9,
    "question": "Simplify: 8/6 + 3/7",
    "options": [
      "36/21",
      "34/21",
      "37/21",
      "35/21"
    ],
    "answer": "37/21"
  },
  {
    "id": 2695,
    "uuid": "92158f83-ad85-4de1-9772-75763505baba",
    "topic": "operations",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.073341",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 8,
    "question": "What is 46 \u00d7 1?",
    "options": [
      "46",
      "53",
      "38",
      "49"
    ],
    "answer": "46"
  },
  {
    "id": 2698,
    "uuid": "a5b0b839-f8f0-4c5b-81ca-a6cbc9994220",
    "topic": "fractions",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.073376",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 9,
    "question": "Simplify: 6/7 + 2/3",
    "options": [
      "31/21",
      "34/21",
      "30/21",
      "32/21"
    ],
    "answer": "32/21"
  },
  {
    "id": 2700,
    "uuid": "4d002faf-6eed-4159-bfcc-bbb357df04df",
    "topic": "fractions",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.073404",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 3,
    "question": "Simplify: 8/2 + 3/8",
    "options": [
      "32/8",
      "38/8",
      "35/8",
      "37/8"
    ],
    "answer": "35/8"
  },
  {
    "id": 2708,
    "uuid": "e1ee58be-2b07-4269-8739-24d331080dc1",
    "topic": "fractions",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.073500",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 5,
    "question": "Simplify: 8/5 + 1/6",
    "options": [
      "54/30",
      "56/30",
      "51/30",
      "53/30"
    ],
    "answer": "53/30"
  },
  {
    "id": 2718,
    "uuid": "6fb1606b-a446-4895-aa31-7b6e32bc0d18",
    "topic": "fractions",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.073620",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 2,
    "question": "Simplify: 8/3 + 8/6",
    "options": [
      "2/1",
      "4/1",
      "1/1",
      "6/1"
    ],
    "answer": "4/1"
  },
  {
    "id": 2726,
    "uuid": "502625af-d017-4841-b673-8d3406ebc8b5",
    "topic": "operations",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.073683",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 9,
    "question": "What is 39 + 1?",
    "options": [
      "41",
      "36",
      "40",
      "46"
    ],
    "answer": "40"
  },
  {
    "id": 2727,
    "uuid": "d43e0904-8442-4047-8bf0-413e31e4e929",
    "topic": "fractions",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.073699",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 4,
    "question": "Simplify: 7/4 + 6/6",
    "options": [
      "14/4",
      "8/4",
      "11/4",
      "9/4"
    ],
    "answer": "11/4"
  },
  {
    "id": 2730,
    "uuid": "7865c435-f78f-46b4-8b64-55c1cefcb8a4",
    "topic": "operations",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.073724",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 2,
    "question": "What is 18 \u00d7 49?",
    "options": [
      "882",
      "874",
      "872",
      "873"
    ],
    "answer": "882"
  },
  {
    "id": 2734,
    "uuid": "18420704-04b9-40e8-8d30-6dd58f2287fa",
    "topic": "operations",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.073759",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "question": "What is 40 \u00d7 31?",
    "options": [
      "1240",
      "1250",
      "1234",
      "1233"
    ],
    "answer": "1240"
  },
  {
    "id": 2736,
    "uuid": "59edee92-4db1-4daf-bb3b-4d4b158709d5",
    "topic": "fractions",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.073783",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 3,
    "question": "Simplify: 7/6 + 7/5",
    "options": [
      "76/30",
      "77/30",
      "75/30",
      "74/30"
    ],
    "answer": "77/30"
  },
  {
    "id": 2743,
    "uuid": "15dcce13-b1f7-4f8e-bc67-95ce9d98b199",
    "topic": "fractions",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.073842",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 4,
    "question": "Simplify: 9/8 + 8/4",
    "options": [
      "23/8",
      "22/8",
      "28/8",
      "25/8"
    ],
    "answer": "25/8"
  },
  {
    "id": 2749,
    "uuid": "c387918e-2f99-452f-a564-d77b14869b8c",
    "topic": "operations",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.073897",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 10,
    "question": "What is 7 - 32?",
    "options": [
      "-17",
      "-35",
      "-31",
      "-25"
    ],
    "answer": "-25"
  },
  {
    "id": 2752,
    "uuid": "d65db475-815b-4410-81ed-f72c2a38f18a",
    "topic": "fractions",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.073933",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 8,
    "question": "Simplify: 3/3 + 2/5",
    "options": [
      "10/5",
      "8/5",
      "7/5",
      "4/5"
    ],
    "answer": "7/5"
  },
  {
    "id": 2753,
    "uuid": "7d2dbb10-37ad-4b1d-9817-c8e69458aad7",
    "topic": "fractions",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.073950",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 2,
    "question": "Simplify: 3/3 + 1/6",
    "options": [
      "7/6",
      "6/6",
      "9/6",
      "10/6"
    ],
    "answer": "7/6"
  },
  {
    "id": 2755,
    "uuid": "d5c1a7bc-9def-4079-a030-db9f547b056d",
    "topic": "fractions",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.073977",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 5,
    "question": "Simplify: 9/3 + 8/2",
    "options": [
      "5/1",
      "4/1",
      "7/1",
      "6/1"
    ],
    "answer": "7/1"
  },
  {
    "id": 2756,
    "uuid": "8fcb5bf7-8e29-42c8-8d10-7ddd6f25a6d8",
    "topic": "fractions",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.073997",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 10,
    "question": "Simplify: 3/7 + 3/3",
    "options": [
      "12/7",
      "8/7",
      "10/7",
      "7/7"
    ],
    "answer": "10/7"
  },
  {
    "id": 2759,
    "uuid": "5ef5d4ed-c031-4b77-9132-9973862b51ea",
    "topic": "fractions",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.074034",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 7,
    "question": "Simplify: 7/2 + 4/4",
    "options": [
      "8/2",
      "6/2",
      "9/2",
      "11/2"
    ],
    "answer": "9/2"
  },
  {
    "id": 2761,
    "uuid": "4fdc478c-1ebb-4f97-91a8-5e0e6868cef7",
    "topic": "operations",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.074053",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "question": "What is 44 \u00d7 9?",
    "options": [
      "403",
      "397",
      "396",
      "404"
    ],
    "answer": "396"
  },
  {
    "id": 2762,
    "uuid": "cfc34d2b-2ca0-44a8-819c-eb5899bc6f0b",
    "topic": "fractions",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.074069",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 5,
    "question": "Simplify: 2/3 + 2/7",
    "options": [
      "20/21",
      "23/21",
      "17/21",
      "21/21"
    ],
    "answer": "20/21"
  },
  {
    "id": 2766,
    "uuid": "3b6d0f6c-6c90-43ba-b3cc-5354d283e0a2",
    "topic": "operations",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.074104",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 8,
    "question": "What is 1 \u00d7 33?",
    "options": [
      "32",
      "31",
      "37",
      "33"
    ],
    "answer": "33"
  },
  {
    "id": 2769,
    "uuid": "c1a6c13f-d982-4a1f-8051-7661d243383c",
    "topic": "fractions",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.074164",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 4,
    "question": "Simplify: 2/8 + 5/2",
    "options": [
      "12/4",
      "11/4",
      "13/4",
      "8/4"
    ],
    "answer": "11/4"
  },
  {
    "id": 2776,
    "uuid": "62ee36e8-02d4-49f6-b423-6fa98c2f4c7c",
    "topic": "operations",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.074230",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 4,
    "question": "What is 23 + 22?",
    "options": [
      "35",
      "41",
      "36",
      "45"
    ],
    "answer": "45"
  },
  {
    "id": 2778,
    "uuid": "d16eeee0-b318-4c63-b802-2edf9a9a7d89",
    "topic": "operations",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.074280",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 7,
    "question": "What is 1 + 34?",
    "options": [
      "28",
      "33",
      "37",
      "35"
    ],
    "answer": "35"
  },
  {
    "id": 2779,
    "uuid": "d32996f2-3123-4e4d-a769-54619b3e5738",
    "topic": "fractions",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.074309",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 7,
    "question": "Simplify: 4/4 + 8/5",
    "options": [
      "15/5",
      "13/5",
      "16/5",
      "14/5"
    ],
    "answer": "13/5"
  },
  {
    "id": 2780,
    "uuid": "4dbbb2bf-c20a-4c55-8ea4-54e28f767030",
    "topic": "operations",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.074322",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 7,
    "question": "What is 35 \u00d7 47?",
    "options": [
      "1645",
      "1652",
      "1644",
      "1637"
    ],
    "answer": "1645"
  },
  {
    "id": 2782,
    "uuid": "305f34d4-59a6-4a83-9ce7-9f82d4d45124",
    "topic": "operations",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.074345",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 8,
    "question": "What is 39 \u00d7 38?",
    "options": [
      "1479",
      "1475",
      "1485",
      "1482"
    ],
    "answer": "1482"
  },
  {
    "id": 2786,
    "uuid": "fc33e4a4-619d-4c29-82bb-28d923247cb9",
    "topic": "fractions",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.074389",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 4,
    "question": "Simplify: 5/4 + 1/5",
    "options": [
      "28/20",
      "31/20",
      "32/20",
      "29/20"
    ],
    "answer": "29/20"
  },
  {
    "id": 2790,
    "uuid": "46b22117-c674-4fa3-82e3-d3da4b2c6f06",
    "topic": "fractions",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.074450",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 9,
    "question": "Simplify: 1/3 + 1/4",
    "options": [
      "4/12",
      "7/12",
      "9/12",
      "6/12"
    ],
    "answer": "7/12"
  },
  {
    "id": 2791,
    "uuid": "a0b20428-5ea5-403c-9359-b1dae27a511d",
    "topic": "fractions",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.074468",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 3,
    "question": "Simplify: 3/5 + 9/9",
    "options": [
      "11/5",
      "9/5",
      "7/5",
      "8/5"
    ],
    "answer": "8/5"
  },
  {
    "id": 2792,
    "uuid": "8c8125e0-7556-46d2-ba61-3aca4299132e",
    "topic": "operations",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.074481",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 4,
    "question": "What is 34 + 23?",
    "options": [
      "55",
      "62",
      "57",
      "51"
    ],
    "answer": "57"
  },
  {
    "id": 2795,
    "uuid": "badcfe65-3745-4850-94ce-aebe8ff91575",
    "topic": "operations",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.074515",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 2,
    "question": "What is 19 - 6?",
    "options": [
      "13",
      "20",
      "6",
      "22"
    ],
    "answer": "13"
  },
  {
    "id": 2801,
    "uuid": "e978e711-3e76-4030-9962-fe5abb51e1ca",
    "topic": "fractions",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.074610",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 2,
    "question": "Simplify: 9/5 + 9/4",
    "options": [
      "83/20",
      "79/20",
      "81/20",
      "78/20"
    ],
    "answer": "81/20"
  },
  {
    "id": 2803,
    "uuid": "c1892d0f-7c58-4a60-8a89-dbf29b78947f",
    "topic": "fractions",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.074676",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 5,
    "question": "Simplify: 1/6 + 9/7",
    "options": [
      "64/42",
      "58/42",
      "61/42",
      "63/42"
    ],
    "answer": "61/42"
  },
  {
    "id": 2812,
    "uuid": "2ebb3403-712b-4b0c-b9a5-7dbcc263aae8",
    "topic": "fractions",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.074760",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 9,
    "question": "Simplify: 3/7 + 2/4",
    "options": [
      "15/14",
      "13/14",
      "16/14",
      "11/14"
    ],
    "answer": "13/14"
  },
  {
    "id": 2819,
    "uuid": "2c462c95-5d91-4b4f-890c-31aee15b4c68",
    "topic": "operations",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.074817",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 9,
    "question": "What is 41 \u00d7 14?",
    "options": [
      "577",
      "564",
      "565",
      "574"
    ],
    "answer": "574"
  },
  {
    "id": 2825,
    "uuid": "5f424289-eb77-4f6b-ae77-be271a6be68a",
    "topic": "fractions",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.074890",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 4,
    "question": "Simplify: 1/8 + 5/6",
    "options": [
      "26/24",
      "25/24",
      "20/24",
      "23/24"
    ],
    "answer": "23/24"
  },
  {
    "id": 2828,
    "uuid": "65015b61-19ea-4236-bbd3-b83b0cad6919",
    "topic": "operations",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.074917",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 2,
    "question": "What is 43 - 28?",
    "options": [
      "14",
      "15",
      "23",
      "12"
    ],
    "answer": "15"
  },
  {
    "id": 2831,
    "uuid": "81c3f780-7452-485c-98fc-56bc1064d971",
    "topic": "operations",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.074960",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 4,
    "question": "What is 23 + 7?",
    "options": [
      "30",
      "25",
      "22",
      "21"
    ],
    "answer": "30"
  },
  {
    "id": 2833,
    "uuid": "3e105a9d-50bb-4637-88a1-eead67f3e03a",
    "topic": "operations",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.074983",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "question": "What is 20 \u00f7 1 (integer division)?",
    "options": [
      "14",
      "17",
      "25",
      "20"
    ],
    "answer": "20"
  },
  {
    "id": 2834,
    "uuid": "05da13d0-81ec-43e4-bbe6-5621f8b86c2b",
    "topic": "operations",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.074995",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 2,
    "question": "What is 13 + 11?",
    "options": [
      "20",
      "24",
      "17",
      "33"
    ],
    "answer": "24"
  },
  {
    "id": 2839,
    "uuid": "8afb76fc-f802-4fd7-a3d6-f7c21e13bb5b",
    "topic": "fractions",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.075051",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 9,
    "question": "Simplify: 6/2 + 9/6",
    "options": [
      "9/2",
      "6/2",
      "11/2",
      "10/2"
    ],
    "answer": "9/2"
  },
  {
    "id": 2841,
    "uuid": "77375d2f-8c93-49f5-b14f-f26dd3d71ef1",
    "topic": "operations",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.075069",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 2,
    "question": "What is 41 + 8?",
    "options": [
      "45",
      "49",
      "46",
      "53"
    ],
    "answer": "49"
  },
  {
    "id": 2842,
    "uuid": "8a64bb35-65c3-499f-addf-c1440a4cc18d",
    "topic": "operations",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.075080",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 4,
    "question": "What is 31 \u00f7 17 (integer division)?",
    "options": [
      "-9",
      "1",
      "6",
      "-5"
    ],
    "answer": "1"
  },
  {
    "id": 2847,
    "uuid": "52733917-20fa-4ef8-8307-a6c22eaa316e",
    "topic": "fractions",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.075129",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 4,
    "question": "Simplify: 4/8 + 5/9",
    "options": [
      "19/18",
      "16/18",
      "20/18",
      "22/18"
    ],
    "answer": "19/18"
  },
  {
    "id": 2848,
    "uuid": "602b777f-b411-40a5-babc-658054e0bd94",
    "topic": "operations",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.075141",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 6,
    "question": "What is 29 + 27?",
    "options": [
      "55",
      "46",
      "51",
      "56"
    ],
    "answer": "56"
  },
  {
    "id": 2850,
    "uuid": "ac67df31-6175-4c80-b013-c299d9323848",
    "topic": "operations",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.075159",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 3,
    "question": "What is 1 \u00d7 11?",
    "options": [
      "7",
      "11",
      "5",
      "10"
    ],
    "answer": "11"
  },
  {
    "id": 2859,
    "uuid": "cf949e94-b37d-4dfd-b74a-bac781f23c12",
    "topic": "operations",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.075259",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 10,
    "question": "What is 42 \u00d7 34?",
    "options": [
      "1423",
      "1424",
      "1427",
      "1428"
    ],
    "answer": "1428"
  },
  {
    "id": 2860,
    "uuid": "93af786a-6d88-4453-914b-d8b7835e4f0f",
    "topic": "fractions",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.075280",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 10,
    "question": "Simplify: 5/6 + 9/3",
    "options": [
      "22/6",
      "21/6",
      "20/6",
      "23/6"
    ],
    "answer": "23/6"
  },
  {
    "id": 2862,
    "uuid": "f9e6c01a-5ed4-4bfb-afbb-cd19ff735175",
    "topic": "fractions",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.075328",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 7,
    "question": "Simplify: 2/7 + 2/8",
    "options": [
      "15/28",
      "17/28",
      "14/28",
      "18/28"
    ],
    "answer": "15/28"
  },
  {
    "id": 2867,
    "uuid": "01ec4e34-a554-429f-a354-c25e93dce04c",
    "topic": "fractions",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.075375",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 3,
    "question": "Simplify: 8/8 + 2/7",
    "options": [
      "7/7",
      "9/7",
      "8/7",
      "10/7"
    ],
    "answer": "9/7"
  },
  {
    "id": 2871,
    "uuid": "50cad550-420f-4e27-a2d2-b9da731b27e2",
    "topic": "fractions",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.075424",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 3,
    "question": "Simplify: 4/7 + 8/3",
    "options": [
      "71/21",
      "67/21",
      "66/21",
      "68/21"
    ],
    "answer": "68/21"
  },
  {
    "id": 2873,
    "uuid": "cf146d58-49ba-41d9-a308-f128701f8120",
    "topic": "operations",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.075442",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 3,
    "question": "What is 10 \u00d7 19?",
    "options": [
      "190",
      "191",
      "193",
      "188"
    ],
    "answer": "190"
  },
  {
    "id": 2874,
    "uuid": "d60822af-d902-4229-82ff-4294fd1cac04",
    "topic": "operations",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.075453",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 2,
    "question": "What is 23 \u00f7 4 (integer division)?",
    "options": [
      "1",
      "-5",
      "9",
      "5"
    ],
    "answer": "5"
  },
  {
    "id": 2879,
    "uuid": "c6bf50ff-5eea-4b2f-b7c5-f8303f4f065a",
    "topic": "fractions",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.075497",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 7,
    "question": "Simplify: 8/6 + 2/6",
    "options": [
      "6/3",
      "5/3",
      "8/3",
      "4/3"
    ],
    "answer": "5/3"
  },
  {
    "id": 2880,
    "uuid": "2256aeb4-d4b7-412b-9ee5-a0b3879fbe8b",
    "topic": "operations",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.075509",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 3,
    "question": "What is 11 - 37?",
    "options": [
      "-24",
      "-28",
      "-26",
      "-20"
    ],
    "answer": "-26"
  },
  {
    "id": 2891,
    "uuid": "febf9e4b-8f11-4724-8d28-3c908c7c0a31",
    "topic": "fractions",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.075662",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "question": "Simplify: 8/5 + 7/3",
    "options": [
      "59/15",
      "60/15",
      "58/15",
      "62/15"
    ],
    "answer": "59/15"
  },
  {
    "id": 2900,
    "uuid": "476c3135-db79-4976-b1ab-58e600a4c7a2",
    "topic": "fractions",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.075737",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 3,
    "question": "Simplify: 3/9 + 4/8",
    "options": [
      "7/6",
      "5/6",
      "8/6",
      "3/6"
    ],
    "answer": "5/6"
  },
  {
    "id": 2901,
    "uuid": "edf838fa-b987-495e-bc1b-4df32bdb41b4",
    "topic": "operations",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.075748",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 8,
    "question": "What is 46 - 12?",
    "options": [
      "44",
      "28",
      "39",
      "34"
    ],
    "answer": "34"
  },
  {
    "id": 2904,
    "uuid": "012558f3-7a48-470d-96dc-731a62d6d72e",
    "topic": "fractions",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.075781",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "question": "Simplify: 1/6 + 3/7",
    "options": [
      "22/42",
      "25/42",
      "24/42",
      "28/42"
    ],
    "answer": "25/42"
  },
  {
    "id": 2907,
    "uuid": "2e901a45-9ff9-4c4e-b569-2a71775543c5",
    "topic": "fractions",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.075869",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 7,
    "question": "Simplify: 3/2 + 3/8",
    "options": [
      "18/8",
      "12/8",
      "16/8",
      "15/8"
    ],
    "answer": "15/8"
  },
  {
    "id": 2910,
    "uuid": "1ca95782-01b9-4f2f-8ec5-0135f31640ac",
    "topic": "operations",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.075899",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 4,
    "question": "What is 14 \u00f7 7 (integer division)?",
    "options": [
      "-7",
      "-8",
      "6",
      "2"
    ],
    "answer": "2"
  },
  {
    "id": 2911,
    "uuid": "237778bc-ceb9-400a-be81-0234e76d15e9",
    "topic": "fractions",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.075924",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 10,
    "question": "Simplify: 7/9 + 3/6",
    "options": [
      "24/18",
      "21/18",
      "22/18",
      "23/18"
    ],
    "answer": "23/18"
  },
  {
    "id": 2919,
    "uuid": "d5056cde-ba65-4521-a233-970c4b5432b5",
    "topic": "fractions",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.075993",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "question": "Simplify: 8/4 + 9/3",
    "options": [
      "6/1",
      "3/1",
      "5/1",
      "2/1"
    ],
    "answer": "5/1"
  },
  {
    "id": 2932,
    "uuid": "e7116e63-17b0-46e1-ae81-85822b6510e8",
    "topic": "operations",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.076096",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 2,
    "question": "What is 11 + 3?",
    "options": [
      "7",
      "22",
      "9",
      "14"
    ],
    "answer": "14"
  },
  {
    "id": 2938,
    "uuid": "54bd391a-e0d9-430a-9f1e-21cdebabcf65",
    "topic": "operations",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.076184",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 4,
    "question": "What is 8 - 40?",
    "options": [
      "-32",
      "-33",
      "-41",
      "-35"
    ],
    "answer": "-32"
  },
  {
    "id": 2940,
    "uuid": "bae9a60d-6476-4ebe-9a5e-33ea4174ad20",
    "topic": "fractions",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.076217",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 2,
    "question": "Simplify: 5/5 + 7/4",
    "options": [
      "9/4",
      "8/4",
      "12/4",
      "11/4"
    ],
    "answer": "11/4"
  },
  {
    "id": 2941,
    "uuid": "d22661a3-da85-4b9b-b946-7d447a58ddd8",
    "topic": "fractions",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.076241",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 6,
    "question": "Simplify: 5/6 + 2/4",
    "options": [
      "4/3",
      "5/3",
      "7/3",
      "1/3"
    ],
    "answer": "4/3"
  },
  {
    "id": 2942,
    "uuid": "125d1f6f-1036-4f51-af9c-4d783f5b7234",
    "topic": "fractions",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.076283",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 2,
    "question": "Simplify: 1/3 + 3/5",
    "options": [
      "13/15",
      "14/15",
      "12/15",
      "11/15"
    ],
    "answer": "14/15"
  },
  {
    "id": 2943,
    "uuid": "6d6821e2-af78-48c9-909a-e40be6521d30",
    "topic": "operations",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.076295",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 10,
    "question": "What is 25 \u00d7 12?",
    "options": [
      "300",
      "292",
      "308",
      "310"
    ],
    "answer": "300"
  },
  {
    "id": 2953,
    "uuid": "0e5367f0-67a0-44e7-9807-7f2a6607cf78",
    "topic": "operations",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.076381",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 3,
    "question": "What is 37 - 38?",
    "options": [
      "6",
      "-7",
      "-1",
      "-3"
    ],
    "answer": "-1"
  },
  {
    "id": 2963,
    "uuid": "4f2ab87e-5625-491e-ade5-26e221acaf7c",
    "topic": "fractions",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.076470",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "question": "Simplify: 2/5 + 5/7",
    "options": [
      "41/35",
      "42/35",
      "40/35",
      "39/35"
    ],
    "answer": "39/35"
  },
  {
    "id": 2969,
    "uuid": "cbb31d36-3a39-4c0e-8f2d-806efa36fdf9",
    "topic": "operations",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.076515",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 9,
    "question": "What is 11 \u00f7 18 (integer division)?",
    "options": [
      "-2",
      "-1",
      "3",
      "0"
    ],
    "answer": "0"
  },
  {
    "id": 2977,
    "uuid": "8faece82-5769-44ac-b6d7-d934455007cc",
    "topic": "fractions",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.076577",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 3,
    "question": "Simplify: 6/6 + 4/7",
    "options": [
      "13/7",
      "10/7",
      "11/7",
      "8/7"
    ],
    "answer": "11/7"
  },
  {
    "id": 2978,
    "uuid": "77a2cd19-61a2-43c4-ae1c-1544a596d2c4",
    "topic": "fractions",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.076593",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 8,
    "question": "Simplify: 6/2 + 2/4",
    "options": [
      "9/2",
      "6/2",
      "7/2",
      "10/2"
    ],
    "answer": "7/2"
  },
  {
    "id": 2985,
    "uuid": "a1916ca6-7e1b-498d-8bcc-33bcdc25cabd",
    "topic": "operations",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.076689",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 3,
    "question": "What is 48 + 49?",
    "options": [
      "98",
      "97",
      "94",
      "105"
    ],
    "answer": "97"
  },
  {
    "id": 2986,
    "uuid": "21435087-77f4-42e5-878c-fe6c816b0641",
    "topic": "fractions",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.076710",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 7,
    "question": "Simplify: 5/9 + 2/3",
    "options": [
      "12/9",
      "14/9",
      "9/9",
      "11/9"
    ],
    "answer": "11/9"
  },
  {
    "id": 2987,
    "uuid": "653e408e-dd9b-4aa8-9670-4f742ca97064",
    "topic": "operations",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.076734",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "question": "What is 34 \u00f7 16 (integer division)?",
    "options": [
      "4",
      "-7",
      "2",
      "0"
    ],
    "answer": "2"
  },
  {
    "id": 2989,
    "uuid": "cb48736f-6b62-4cbf-b244-5cc14fe100cb",
    "topic": "fractions",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.076765",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 4,
    "question": "Simplify: 7/6 + 4/7",
    "options": [
      "74/42",
      "73/42",
      "72/42",
      "70/42"
    ],
    "answer": "73/42"
  },
  {
    "id": 2992,
    "uuid": "c6f08a79-171f-4952-a159-5fa0d352a676",
    "topic": "operations",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.076804",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 2,
    "question": "What is 42 \u00d7 40?",
    "options": [
      "1679",
      "1683",
      "1680",
      "1672"
    ],
    "answer": "1680"
  },
  {
    "id": 2998,
    "uuid": "484f7ee5-fd42-4647-9736-a50a0d232e2a",
    "topic": "operations",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.076854",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 8,
    "question": "What is 18 + 28?",
    "options": [
      "51",
      "39",
      "46",
      "52"
    ],
    "answer": "46"
  },
  {
    "id": 3000,
    "uuid": "739d5c70-b7cd-4644-a534-a0eac0bf4b81",
    "topic": "fractions",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.076884",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 5,
    "question": "Simplify: 1/4 + 5/5",
    "options": [
      "4/4",
      "8/4",
      "5/4",
      "2/4"
    ],
    "answer": "5/4"
  },
  {
    "id": 3014,
    "uuid": "bff3d60c-75ad-4ed9-a8ed-5e453c1f400c",
    "topic": "operations",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.077001",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "question": "What is 3 - 38?",
    "options": [
      "-35",
      "-30",
      "-43",
      "-28"
    ],
    "answer": "-35"
  },
  {
    "id": 3023,
    "uuid": "d9d61d6c-715b-4c1f-97ea-9e17dac91b12",
    "topic": "operations",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.077088",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 6,
    "question": "What is 4 \u00f7 16 (integer division)?",
    "options": [
      "-7",
      "-5",
      "8",
      "0"
    ],
    "answer": "0"
  },
  {
    "id": 3024,
    "uuid": "8f65df76-2a63-4c56-af2b-74ff13d3847f",
    "topic": "operations",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.077110",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 6,
    "question": "What is 45 \u00f7 1 (integer division)?",
    "options": [
      "42",
      "45",
      "44",
      "46"
    ],
    "answer": "45"
  },
  {
    "id": 3025,
    "uuid": "2fc96709-ca6e-4305-92f6-3103e96bb164",
    "topic": "operations",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.077131",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 7,
    "question": "What is 15 - 46?",
    "options": [
      "-28",
      "-33",
      "-31",
      "-27"
    ],
    "answer": "-31"
  },
  {
    "id": 3030,
    "uuid": "9682fb84-f964-4ac1-aa0c-661dc70235ea",
    "topic": "fractions",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.077233",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 9,
    "question": "Simplify: 3/8 + 7/9",
    "options": [
      "84/72",
      "82/72",
      "85/72",
      "83/72"
    ],
    "answer": "83/72"
  },
  {
    "id": 3035,
    "uuid": "ec67a5b2-a233-49e5-9a80-859911cb94ad",
    "topic": "operations",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.077271",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 9,
    "question": "What is 25 - 31?",
    "options": [
      "2",
      "-6",
      "-10",
      "-3"
    ],
    "answer": "-6"
  },
  {
    "id": 3038,
    "uuid": "31619f93-753e-4654-815f-04f4d69c001a",
    "topic": "operations",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.077300",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 9,
    "question": "What is 43 \u00d7 41?",
    "options": [
      "1757",
      "1771",
      "1763",
      "1756"
    ],
    "answer": "1763"
  },
  {
    "id": 3040,
    "uuid": "3c9c9d14-95b2-46f8-9099-5fb95fe4898e",
    "topic": "operations",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.077322",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 8,
    "question": "What is 27 - 26?",
    "options": [
      "-4",
      "-8",
      "1",
      "-7"
    ],
    "answer": "1"
  },
  {
    "id": 3042,
    "uuid": "cbb4180a-fca9-44cf-83ed-fe4b0a0b7988",
    "topic": "fractions",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.077373",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 4,
    "question": "Simplify: 9/3 + 9/4",
    "options": [
      "21/4",
      "18/4",
      "22/4",
      "19/4"
    ],
    "answer": "21/4"
  },
  {
    "id": 3047,
    "uuid": "e93e48e4-c4a2-43bc-9196-ec7a9699d381",
    "topic": "operations",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.077426",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 6,
    "question": "What is 14 - 46?",
    "options": [
      "-35",
      "-40",
      "-33",
      "-32"
    ],
    "answer": "-32"
  },
  {
    "id": 3049,
    "uuid": "c8b59daf-34ef-49bc-a702-59d673290d32",
    "topic": "fractions",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.077488",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 5,
    "question": "Simplify: 2/7 + 9/9",
    "options": [
      "7/7",
      "9/7",
      "8/7",
      "6/7"
    ],
    "answer": "9/7"
  },
  {
    "id": 3056,
    "uuid": "5c3bf25d-694e-47f0-b63d-42b74a39c91b",
    "topic": "operations",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.077580",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 4,
    "question": "What is 7 \u00d7 25?",
    "options": [
      "169",
      "185",
      "183",
      "175"
    ],
    "answer": "175"
  },
  {
    "id": 3066,
    "uuid": "b9cce698-bf3b-43fa-87ae-346697a5746d",
    "topic": "operations",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.077672",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 2,
    "question": "What is 43 \u00f7 5 (integer division)?",
    "options": [
      "8",
      "14",
      "16",
      "3"
    ],
    "answer": "8"
  },
  {
    "id": 3069,
    "uuid": "77b46255-af22-4a3d-89e3-7a51bf527bae",
    "topic": "fractions",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.077727",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 8,
    "question": "Simplify: 8/8 + 7/4",
    "options": [
      "8/4",
      "12/4",
      "9/4",
      "11/4"
    ],
    "answer": "11/4"
  },
  {
    "id": 3070,
    "uuid": "038eb877-0340-48eb-a435-13cc3319d98e",
    "topic": "operations",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.077741",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 6,
    "question": "What is 41 - 49?",
    "options": [
      "-10",
      "-8",
      "-5",
      "-12"
    ],
    "answer": "-8"
  },
  {
    "id": 3073,
    "uuid": "d25b5062-322d-459d-b235-b09f80bd8f2f",
    "topic": "operations",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.077816",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 10,
    "question": "What is 6 + 12?",
    "options": [
      "13",
      "17",
      "18",
      "12"
    ],
    "answer": "18"
  },
  {
    "id": 3074,
    "uuid": "db2b8a92-3a83-4746-a684-a0a63797a47d",
    "topic": "operations",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.077830",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 9,
    "question": "What is 38 - 6?",
    "options": [
      "33",
      "36",
      "32",
      "29"
    ],
    "answer": "32"
  },
  {
    "id": 3078,
    "uuid": "c10a69d5-5e37-4e63-a715-8b79a886ea4f",
    "topic": "fractions",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.077883",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 9,
    "question": "Simplify: 5/2 + 6/7",
    "options": [
      "49/14",
      "47/14",
      "45/14",
      "50/14"
    ],
    "answer": "47/14"
  },
  {
    "id": 3089,
    "uuid": "fb0725fc-7e1d-4f01-a4c0-66eddb42e28b",
    "topic": "fractions",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.078053",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 2,
    "question": "Simplify: 1/6 + 3/8",
    "options": [
      "13/24",
      "14/24",
      "11/24",
      "10/24"
    ],
    "answer": "13/24"
  },
  {
    "id": 3092,
    "uuid": "1e7b2d22-6135-4797-aa42-b0ba8647bb93",
    "topic": "fractions",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.078091",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 8,
    "question": "Simplify: 9/5 + 4/7",
    "options": [
      "83/35",
      "84/35",
      "86/35",
      "85/35"
    ],
    "answer": "83/35"
  },
  {
    "id": 3094,
    "uuid": "8f2e3dac-e206-49de-92a5-6ea20a2b9a2c",
    "topic": "fractions",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.078149",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 10,
    "question": "Simplify: 6/8 + 1/6",
    "options": [
      "9/12",
      "10/12",
      "11/12",
      "8/12"
    ],
    "answer": "11/12"
  },
  {
    "id": 3098,
    "uuid": "d879706f-c712-493d-b787-3314a2e896fd",
    "topic": "fractions",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.078236",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 10,
    "question": "Simplify: 3/8 + 1/2",
    "options": [
      "6/8",
      "7/8",
      "4/8",
      "9/8"
    ],
    "answer": "7/8"
  },
  {
    "id": 3103,
    "uuid": "03f42905-c4ee-440f-bbf8-09529661f910",
    "topic": "fractions",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.078325",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 3,
    "question": "Simplify: 9/9 + 3/2",
    "options": [
      "7/2",
      "5/2",
      "6/2",
      "4/2"
    ],
    "answer": "5/2"
  },
  {
    "id": 3106,
    "uuid": "d3cb1f77-1a58-45c2-9345-db679aef3ea0",
    "topic": "operations",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.078360",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 6,
    "question": "What is 37 \u00f7 14 (integer division)?",
    "options": [
      "11",
      "-5",
      "2",
      "0"
    ],
    "answer": "2"
  },
  {
    "id": 3109,
    "uuid": "22a2cfea-b45b-4d8c-a3a7-59f84a8f4bc8",
    "topic": "operations",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.078393",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 5,
    "question": "What is 29 \u00f7 14 (integer division)?",
    "options": [
      "5",
      "2",
      "-5",
      "8"
    ],
    "answer": "2"
  },
  {
    "id": 3110,
    "uuid": "3f605e88-8b25-49d1-83c7-b396ceaee0f8",
    "topic": "operations",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.078434",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 2,
    "question": "What is 20 \u00d7 16?",
    "options": [
      "318",
      "320",
      "313",
      "325"
    ],
    "answer": "320"
  },
  {
    "id": 3115,
    "uuid": "c544454e-4655-4bd0-bb39-10b41f904d7c",
    "topic": "fractions",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.078506",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 6,
    "question": "Simplify: 2/9 + 6/2",
    "options": [
      "32/9",
      "26/9",
      "29/9",
      "27/9"
    ],
    "answer": "29/9"
  },
  {
    "id": 3125,
    "uuid": "02a05513-be9a-4a14-95af-258654ccfd8e",
    "topic": "fractions",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.078609",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 9,
    "question": "Simplify: 9/7 + 2/6",
    "options": [
      "31/21",
      "33/21",
      "32/21",
      "34/21"
    ],
    "answer": "34/21"
  },
  {
    "id": 3126,
    "uuid": "937e7f33-bdc5-4c6c-9113-18d24873e067",
    "topic": "operations",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.078634",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 6,
    "question": "What is 23 + 23?",
    "options": [
      "46",
      "39",
      "44",
      "50"
    ],
    "answer": "46"
  },
  {
    "id": 3129,
    "uuid": "341b177f-0642-4990-a212-0030499200f2",
    "topic": "operations",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.078680",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 2,
    "question": "What is 4 + 19?",
    "options": [
      "23",
      "13",
      "31",
      "20"
    ],
    "answer": "23"
  },
  {
    "id": 3131,
    "uuid": "dce8be21-707f-4bb0-9fff-46618d0ed327",
    "topic": "operations",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.078700",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 10,
    "question": "What is 49 - 16?",
    "options": [
      "28",
      "40",
      "25",
      "33"
    ],
    "answer": "33"
  },
  {
    "id": 3137,
    "uuid": "3549ae65-e98c-4205-9abc-d0d52ca58f11",
    "topic": "operations",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.078757",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 10,
    "question": "What is 10 \u00d7 26?",
    "options": [
      "260",
      "269",
      "255",
      "252"
    ],
    "answer": "260"
  },
  {
    "id": 3140,
    "uuid": "9f6b3cf7-390f-4cae-9bc9-a4d20c48b8f5",
    "topic": "fractions",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.078815",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "question": "Simplify: 4/2 + 4/9",
    "options": [
      "19/9",
      "25/9",
      "21/9",
      "22/9"
    ],
    "answer": "22/9"
  },
  {
    "id": 3143,
    "uuid": "5f248791-595d-4ed7-b0b7-be65d7fafa7f",
    "topic": "operations",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.078847",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 2,
    "question": "What is 39 + 11?",
    "options": [
      "43",
      "42",
      "50",
      "59"
    ],
    "answer": "50"
  },
  {
    "id": 3152,
    "uuid": "e4fc2a5c-5f32-424a-8c2b-6456c6233de1",
    "topic": "fractions",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.078985",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 5,
    "question": "Simplify: 1/7 + 4/9",
    "options": [
      "37/63",
      "39/63",
      "36/63",
      "34/63"
    ],
    "answer": "37/63"
  },
  {
    "id": 3159,
    "uuid": "697f6c16-6c2c-4259-ac69-dedc6326ec82",
    "topic": "fractions",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.079085",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 2,
    "question": "Simplify: 4/7 + 7/2",
    "options": [
      "57/14",
      "54/14",
      "55/14",
      "56/14"
    ],
    "answer": "57/14"
  },
  {
    "id": 3166,
    "uuid": "c9806e03-b526-4023-b517-c31a8fe90a57",
    "topic": "fractions",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.079160",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 10,
    "question": "Simplify: 9/3 + 7/6",
    "options": [
      "28/6",
      "22/6",
      "26/6",
      "25/6"
    ],
    "answer": "25/6"
  },
  {
    "id": 3167,
    "uuid": "b12b3622-e401-4cb1-a2d0-c857fb3b3958",
    "topic": "operations",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.079174",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 3,
    "question": "What is 38 - 8?",
    "options": [
      "27",
      "21",
      "40",
      "30"
    ],
    "answer": "30"
  },
  {
    "id": 3168,
    "uuid": "2515b279-dbec-4d6b-8e64-57a38efe7f2d",
    "topic": "operations",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.079188",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 10,
    "question": "What is 39 \u00d7 17?",
    "options": [
      "663",
      "658",
      "667",
      "659"
    ],
    "answer": "663"
  },
  {
    "id": 3171,
    "uuid": "07a05db7-967a-4326-81cf-ba46540c531a",
    "topic": "operations",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.079218",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 5,
    "question": "What is 4 \u00f7 2 (integer division)?",
    "options": [
      "2",
      "6",
      "-4",
      "3"
    ],
    "answer": "2"
  },
  {
    "id": 3194,
    "uuid": "8153fdca-d1c8-4d85-af52-6726b4529573",
    "topic": "operations",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.079432",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 5,
    "question": "What is 24 - 9?",
    "options": [
      "14",
      "7",
      "15",
      "13"
    ],
    "answer": "15"
  },
  {
    "id": 3198,
    "uuid": "f56ac6e7-5528-4613-a9df-0d39bdbdaced",
    "topic": "operations",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.079507",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 7,
    "question": "What is 21 \u00f7 4 (integer division)?",
    "options": [
      "5",
      "-3",
      "13",
      "15"
    ],
    "answer": "5"
  },
  {
    "id": 3205,
    "uuid": "5becd0fb-6d70-4c3e-b140-b9e79cd1e3fe",
    "topic": "fractions",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.079605",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 10,
    "question": "Simplify: 4/9 + 8/3",
    "options": [
      "29/9",
      "26/9",
      "27/9",
      "28/9"
    ],
    "answer": "28/9"
  },
  {
    "id": 3206,
    "uuid": "c31c1e5e-27de-4301-8728-97d197789123",
    "topic": "fractions",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.079647",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 4,
    "question": "Simplify: 3/2 + 6/8",
    "options": [
      "7/4",
      "12/4",
      "9/4",
      "11/4"
    ],
    "answer": "9/4"
  },
  {
    "id": 3210,
    "uuid": "ac9c5cef-6a9d-45fa-a782-b291c041623a",
    "topic": "fractions",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.079706",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 3,
    "question": "Simplify: 7/9 + 7/4",
    "options": [
      "89/36",
      "92/36",
      "91/36",
      "90/36"
    ],
    "answer": "91/36"
  },
  {
    "id": 3211,
    "uuid": "df803fa0-ffc7-4d17-87aa-9fc6a5de72da",
    "topic": "operations",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.079719",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 2,
    "question": "What is 9 - 16?",
    "options": [
      "-17",
      "-7",
      "-14",
      "1"
    ],
    "answer": "-7"
  },
  {
    "id": 3215,
    "uuid": "e08ad788-1694-4d25-8dca-b0a86804bae5",
    "topic": "operations",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.079759",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 6,
    "question": "What is 44 \u00d7 31?",
    "options": [
      "1362",
      "1356",
      "1364",
      "1358"
    ],
    "answer": "1364"
  },
  {
    "id": 3217,
    "uuid": "524aa7a9-597a-4fde-8bbf-549dddf20d0d",
    "topic": "operations",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.079782",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 3,
    "question": "What is 1 \u00f7 10 (integer division)?",
    "options": [
      "-4",
      "0",
      "-6",
      "-3"
    ],
    "answer": "0"
  },
  {
    "id": 3225,
    "uuid": "c13e074e-22d4-496b-929c-56471dc1add0",
    "topic": "operations",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.079873",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 2,
    "question": "What is 16 + 25?",
    "options": [
      "47",
      "50",
      "41",
      "36"
    ],
    "answer": "41"
  },
  {
    "id": 3226,
    "uuid": "4d4ee675-f155-4571-8623-cef324edc668",
    "topic": "operations",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.079905",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 8,
    "question": "What is 41 \u00d7 31?",
    "options": [
      "1276",
      "1262",
      "1271",
      "1265"
    ],
    "answer": "1271"
  },
  {
    "id": 3241,
    "uuid": "cd576ef8-14f4-477e-895d-00640ecc6729",
    "topic": "operations",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.080059",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 4,
    "question": "What is 19 - 39?",
    "options": [
      "-21",
      "-17",
      "-20",
      "-26"
    ],
    "answer": "-20"
  },
  {
    "id": 3247,
    "uuid": "218901de-6889-48fd-b1dc-bc651f3966f3",
    "topic": "fractions",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.080142",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 8,
    "question": "Simplify: 3/5 + 9/6",
    "options": [
      "21/10",
      "19/10",
      "24/10",
      "20/10"
    ],
    "answer": "21/10"
  },
  {
    "id": 3252,
    "uuid": "56cf32f8-690e-4ac8-b526-7bef6ec7fa8d",
    "topic": "operations",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.080194",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 4,
    "question": "What is 22 \u00d7 43?",
    "options": [
      "948",
      "952",
      "938",
      "946"
    ],
    "answer": "946"
  },
  {
    "id": 3260,
    "uuid": "3cc4bb9d-b996-4e60-8ff9-94b75bba386a",
    "topic": "operations",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.080997",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 2,
    "question": "What is 35 - 4?",
    "options": [
      "34",
      "23",
      "31",
      "33"
    ],
    "answer": "31"
  },
  {
    "id": 3278,
    "uuid": "04311464-1332-4bda-9b92-f07f5146eed4",
    "topic": "fractions",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.081323",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 4,
    "question": "Simplify: 1/7 + 1/5",
    "options": [
      "9/35",
      "12/35",
      "15/35",
      "13/35"
    ],
    "answer": "12/35"
  },
  {
    "id": 3292,
    "uuid": "12ac401a-7d26-478f-9a13-c5079bcd46b4",
    "topic": "operations",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.081492",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 5,
    "question": "What is 22 + 38?",
    "options": [
      "60",
      "50",
      "63",
      "54"
    ],
    "answer": "60"
  },
  {
    "id": 3294,
    "uuid": "fecc5793-698d-42cb-a436-61fa43e7ba3a",
    "topic": "operations",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.081546",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 8,
    "question": "What is 30 \u00d7 13?",
    "options": [
      "387",
      "384",
      "381",
      "390"
    ],
    "answer": "390"
  },
  {
    "id": 3300,
    "uuid": "3972d36d-5202-4d0b-af39-2e19f53cb8bd",
    "topic": "fractions",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.081634",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 2,
    "question": "Simplify: 4/2 + 9/4",
    "options": [
      "17/4",
      "20/4",
      "18/4",
      "16/4"
    ],
    "answer": "17/4"
  },
  {
    "id": 3314,
    "uuid": "db3745fb-4fa0-4bd6-9d41-7493ad78c185",
    "topic": "operations",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.081784",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 10,
    "question": "What is 27 - 10?",
    "options": [
      "21",
      "11",
      "17",
      "14"
    ],
    "answer": "17"
  },
  {
    "id": 3316,
    "uuid": "b29ee353-17cf-42a8-a810-4d115148e22e",
    "topic": "operations",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.081821",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 6,
    "question": "What is 10 - 11?",
    "options": [
      "-10",
      "4",
      "7",
      "-1"
    ],
    "answer": "-1"
  },
  {
    "id": 3327,
    "uuid": "1929ea52-cd95-40be-bc6c-ce19a0c67be2",
    "topic": "operations",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.081974",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 9,
    "question": "What is 36 \u00d7 38?",
    "options": [
      "1374",
      "1369",
      "1368",
      "1377"
    ],
    "answer": "1368"
  },
  {
    "id": 3332,
    "uuid": "723b1d81-4357-404f-b85e-68265754f1e6",
    "topic": "fractions",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.082059",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 10,
    "question": "Simplify: 1/9 + 7/3",
    "options": [
      "20/9",
      "23/9",
      "24/9",
      "22/9"
    ],
    "answer": "22/9"
  },
  {
    "id": 3333,
    "uuid": "c90e1de1-bf32-4cfb-8dcd-b374af35b74a",
    "topic": "operations",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.082089",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 9,
    "question": "What is 41 + 22?",
    "options": [
      "70",
      "63",
      "56",
      "57"
    ],
    "answer": "63"
  },
  {
    "id": 3334,
    "uuid": "835a3fc7-9316-45fe-83ad-749ade086abe",
    "topic": "fractions",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.082141",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 8,
    "question": "Simplify: 1/9 + 1/8",
    "options": [
      "19/72",
      "20/72",
      "18/72",
      "17/72"
    ],
    "answer": "17/72"
  },
  {
    "id": 3335,
    "uuid": "20afb063-687e-4fd7-bac5-e7800f8161d7",
    "topic": "fractions",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.082181",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 10,
    "question": "Simplify: 4/9 + 3/4",
    "options": [
      "43/36",
      "44/36",
      "41/36",
      "42/36"
    ],
    "answer": "43/36"
  },
  {
    "id": 3338,
    "uuid": "5e413802-8350-4526-a46f-b28b8766516b",
    "topic": "operations",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.082232",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 4,
    "question": "What is 27 \u00d7 32?",
    "options": [
      "868",
      "864",
      "870",
      "873"
    ],
    "answer": "864"
  },
  {
    "id": 3343,
    "uuid": "183887aa-9967-46f3-bfe3-a238a587c920",
    "topic": "fractions",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.082319",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 6,
    "question": "Simplify: 4/3 + 6/7",
    "options": [
      "43/21",
      "46/21",
      "45/21",
      "48/21"
    ],
    "answer": "46/21"
  },
  {
    "id": 3344,
    "uuid": "fd6a318b-69e6-44ee-8a4b-0d2316b8528e",
    "topic": "fractions",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.082365",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 6,
    "question": "Simplify: 2/9 + 4/6",
    "options": [
      "7/9",
      "10/9",
      "8/9",
      "11/9"
    ],
    "answer": "8/9"
  },
  {
    "id": 3349,
    "uuid": "d475298f-53c1-4639-991a-4e8779216da2",
    "topic": "operations",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.082419",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 10,
    "question": "What is 13 \u00f7 4 (integer division)?",
    "options": [
      "13",
      "10",
      "5",
      "3"
    ],
    "answer": "3"
  },
  {
    "id": 3352,
    "uuid": "75300aaa-4b6f-4267-b2cc-cb9e4e968938",
    "topic": "operations",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.082461",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 5,
    "question": "What is 10 \u00d7 15?",
    "options": [
      "150",
      "160",
      "148",
      "151"
    ],
    "answer": "150"
  },
  {
    "id": 3361,
    "uuid": "6eeac12a-982c-4d2c-b427-b92a4244cbeb",
    "topic": "fractions",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.082558",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 3,
    "question": "Simplify: 8/5 + 2/8",
    "options": [
      "39/20",
      "37/20",
      "40/20",
      "38/20"
    ],
    "answer": "37/20"
  },
  {
    "id": 3363,
    "uuid": "47719abf-1c94-4e27-ab60-b874023139a1",
    "topic": "fractions",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.082584",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 5,
    "question": "Simplify: 4/5 + 3/6",
    "options": [
      "15/10",
      "10/10",
      "13/10",
      "16/10"
    ],
    "answer": "13/10"
  },
  {
    "id": 3367,
    "uuid": "3b2b443a-d3e0-498f-a39d-9c51cd8eaf87",
    "topic": "fractions",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.082652",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 8,
    "question": "Simplify: 2/7 + 6/6",
    "options": [
      "6/7",
      "8/7",
      "11/7",
      "9/7"
    ],
    "answer": "9/7"
  },
  {
    "id": 3368,
    "uuid": "cadd03d3-60fd-4d30-a730-c4b3ce5d55da",
    "topic": "operations",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.082678",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 5,
    "question": "What is 22 - 1?",
    "options": [
      "13",
      "27",
      "16",
      "21"
    ],
    "answer": "21"
  },
  {
    "id": 3373,
    "uuid": "1393363e-23bb-4f5b-b41b-655aabc8b15a",
    "topic": "operations",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.082724",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 3,
    "question": "What is 48 - 9?",
    "options": [
      "38",
      "41",
      "39",
      "46"
    ],
    "answer": "39"
  },
  {
    "id": 3378,
    "uuid": "8335649c-a677-40d7-9062-cba8c821ba09",
    "topic": "operations",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.082768",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 4,
    "question": "What is 9 \u00f7 8 (integer division)?",
    "options": [
      "-8",
      "-4",
      "1",
      "-1"
    ],
    "answer": "1"
  },
  {
    "id": 3381,
    "uuid": "47dda49f-b33f-4b80-9925-bf26a54305c6",
    "topic": "operations",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.082801",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 2,
    "question": "What is 7 \u00f7 20 (integer division)?",
    "options": [
      "0",
      "10",
      "-8",
      "-6"
    ],
    "answer": "0"
  },
  {
    "id": 3386,
    "uuid": "d4768b02-4362-4758-a055-4d325d18f67d",
    "topic": "fractions",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.082871",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 3,
    "question": "Simplify: 7/5 + 2/7",
    "options": [
      "61/35",
      "59/35",
      "58/35",
      "60/35"
    ],
    "answer": "59/35"
  },
  {
    "id": 3389,
    "uuid": "2ae30233-73a7-4109-92a1-51003537636a",
    "topic": "operations",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.082898",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 5,
    "question": "What is 2 \u00d7 14?",
    "options": [
      "28",
      "23",
      "20",
      "18"
    ],
    "answer": "28"
  },
  {
    "id": 3392,
    "uuid": "d3bb8571-15e5-46df-beeb-7f3ac5471242",
    "topic": "fractions",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.082930",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 7,
    "question": "Simplify: 9/5 + 1/6",
    "options": [
      "59/30",
      "56/30",
      "62/30",
      "57/30"
    ],
    "answer": "59/30"
  },
  {
    "id": 3399,
    "uuid": "280cdf56-0439-44f2-977e-247218876a0b",
    "topic": "operations",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.082982",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 9,
    "question": "What is 38 \u00d7 21?",
    "options": [
      "802",
      "798",
      "795",
      "803"
    ],
    "answer": "798"
  },
  {
    "id": 3402,
    "uuid": "03e639e7-69ea-4b1b-8c85-ed3eb6bd543f",
    "topic": "operations",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.083007",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 2,
    "question": "What is 4 \u00f7 8 (integer division)?",
    "options": [
      "-1",
      "-4",
      "-8",
      "0"
    ],
    "answer": "0"
  },
  {
    "id": 3406,
    "uuid": "8c1ebdd0-8eb6-48d4-b227-5cd465424722",
    "topic": "operations",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.083046",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 7,
    "question": "What is 40 \u00f7 17 (integer division)?",
    "options": [
      "-4",
      "2",
      "5",
      "1"
    ],
    "answer": "2"
  },
  {
    "id": 3408,
    "uuid": "7eaed86a-2d00-4032-a1de-c0b58f91dd12",
    "topic": "fractions",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.083084",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "question": "Simplify: 7/5 + 4/3",
    "options": [
      "39/15",
      "43/15",
      "41/15",
      "40/15"
    ],
    "answer": "41/15"
  },
  {
    "id": 3409,
    "uuid": "05ba4299-80ad-46ba-bde1-4c2d358755d1",
    "topic": "operations",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.083096",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "question": "What is 12 + 13?",
    "options": [
      "25",
      "20",
      "28",
      "31"
    ],
    "answer": "25"
  },
  {
    "id": 3411,
    "uuid": "14e5d90d-f875-42d0-bcf1-6163959899e8",
    "topic": "fractions",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.083119",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "question": "Simplify: 5/3 + 2/6",
    "options": [
      "2/1",
      "0/1",
      "5/1",
      "-1/1"
    ],
    "answer": "2/1"
  },
  {
    "id": 3413,
    "uuid": "7e916ebe-9567-4d9e-97ec-0be4cdd98bc8",
    "topic": "fractions",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.083148",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 3,
    "question": "Simplify: 1/3 + 7/8",
    "options": [
      "31/24",
      "32/24",
      "29/24",
      "27/24"
    ],
    "answer": "29/24"
  },
  {
    "id": 3415,
    "uuid": "e40a52d1-316c-43be-960f-a60200431abf",
    "topic": "fractions",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.083178",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 4,
    "question": "Simplify: 1/7 + 7/4",
    "options": [
      "55/28",
      "50/28",
      "54/28",
      "53/28"
    ],
    "answer": "53/28"
  },
  {
    "id": 3424,
    "uuid": "8c1c7e50-66fb-467b-b5b5-410ac5848a20",
    "topic": "operations",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.083248",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 4,
    "question": "What is 12 \u00f7 14 (integer division)?",
    "options": [
      "-5",
      "-4",
      "-2",
      "0"
    ],
    "answer": "0"
  },
  {
    "id": 3431,
    "uuid": "f7d359a9-fef3-4e6c-8cd9-e5fb4611da8e",
    "topic": "fractions",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.083313",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 4,
    "question": "Simplify: 6/5 + 9/2",
    "options": [
      "57/10",
      "54/10",
      "58/10",
      "56/10"
    ],
    "answer": "57/10"
  },
  {
    "id": 3438,
    "uuid": "fa7d007a-9d01-4301-a403-4d8a1c40b4b1",
    "topic": "fractions",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.083372",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 2,
    "question": "Simplify: 5/5 + 7/9",
    "options": [
      "15/9",
      "14/9",
      "17/9",
      "16/9"
    ],
    "answer": "16/9"
  },
  {
    "id": 3454,
    "uuid": "e9fce2d7-e878-4649-b844-d087f53a7197",
    "topic": "fractions",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.083524",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 6,
    "question": "Simplify: 2/6 + 7/5",
    "options": [
      "29/15",
      "26/15",
      "27/15",
      "25/15"
    ],
    "answer": "26/15"
  },
  {
    "id": 3457,
    "uuid": "ed6d424b-a35b-499f-a5b3-cd00876d7640",
    "topic": "fractions",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.083561",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 3,
    "question": "Simplify: 5/2 + 4/8",
    "options": [
      "6/1",
      "2/1",
      "4/1",
      "3/1"
    ],
    "answer": "3/1"
  },
  {
    "id": 3464,
    "uuid": "c2faa7ea-dccf-40f6-a272-ebaeb5ef4bae",
    "topic": "fractions",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.083618",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 2,
    "question": "Simplify: 6/2 + 2/8",
    "options": [
      "16/4",
      "13/4",
      "11/4",
      "15/4"
    ],
    "answer": "13/4"
  },
  {
    "id": 3473,
    "uuid": "e9001f6f-af42-4288-b68e-211ab53116d9",
    "topic": "operations",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.083688",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 7,
    "question": "What is 20 - 42?",
    "options": [
      "-28",
      "-22",
      "-31",
      "-16"
    ],
    "answer": "-22"
  },
  {
    "id": 3478,
    "uuid": "cc5f68b7-cae0-4d63-a679-fe94a6523961",
    "topic": "fractions",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.083762",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 4,
    "question": "Simplify: 1/5 + 6/5",
    "options": [
      "9/5",
      "8/5",
      "4/5",
      "7/5"
    ],
    "answer": "7/5"
  },
  {
    "id": 3480,
    "uuid": "8a922fe7-914c-484d-8f1b-28b1dde57efa",
    "topic": "operations",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.083796",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 10,
    "question": "What is 6 \u00f7 4 (integer division)?",
    "options": [
      "-6",
      "6",
      "1",
      "-7"
    ],
    "answer": "1"
  },
  {
    "id": 3493,
    "uuid": "f505e9a9-821e-4fb1-a0b0-2a0a358d31eb",
    "topic": "operations",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.083897",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 3,
    "question": "What is 5 - 46?",
    "options": [
      "-41",
      "-49",
      "-45",
      "-50"
    ],
    "answer": "-41"
  },
  {
    "id": 3508,
    "uuid": "e6ac78bf-0bfe-4700-8f23-a9c608515d66",
    "topic": "fractions",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.084036",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "question": "Simplify: 7/8 + 3/7",
    "options": [
      "70/56",
      "76/56",
      "72/56",
      "73/56"
    ],
    "answer": "73/56"
  },
  {
    "id": 3512,
    "uuid": "3c7176de-df19-4c80-880a-ea0edb825d9c",
    "topic": "fractions",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.084089",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 5,
    "question": "Simplify: 5/2 + 9/9",
    "options": [
      "4/2",
      "7/2",
      "10/2",
      "9/2"
    ],
    "answer": "7/2"
  },
  {
    "id": 3515,
    "uuid": "0b9baf30-3182-4f7e-8b7c-cb08ce890ce2",
    "topic": "fractions",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.084125",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 9,
    "question": "Simplify: 4/3 + 2/7",
    "options": [
      "32/21",
      "36/21",
      "34/21",
      "37/21"
    ],
    "answer": "34/21"
  },
  {
    "id": 3516,
    "uuid": "028cc844-b479-4f35-be1e-e008c3cdd60c",
    "topic": "fractions",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.084141",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 3,
    "question": "Simplify: 3/4 + 9/4",
    "options": [
      "3/1",
      "4/1",
      "2/1",
      "0/1"
    ],
    "answer": "3/1"
  },
  {
    "id": 3523,
    "uuid": "19057f90-f6b7-4a13-9be1-de98a494329f",
    "topic": "fractions",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.084206",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 10,
    "question": "Simplify: 3/4 + 1/8",
    "options": [
      "9/8",
      "7/8",
      "6/8",
      "4/8"
    ],
    "answer": "7/8"
  },
  {
    "id": 3532,
    "uuid": "b2a59150-5f5b-47ee-9302-cc41d46a2958",
    "topic": "fractions",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.084278",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 4,
    "question": "Simplify: 2/5 + 1/8",
    "options": [
      "19/40",
      "21/40",
      "24/40",
      "20/40"
    ],
    "answer": "21/40"
  },
  {
    "id": 3537,
    "uuid": "845b1982-ae9b-4fab-8a6e-2e435d9c850d",
    "topic": "operations",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.084316",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 9,
    "question": "What is 21 \u00d7 22?",
    "options": [
      "463",
      "462",
      "470",
      "467"
    ],
    "answer": "462"
  },
  {
    "id": 3539,
    "uuid": "c4f582da-042b-4fe7-b82f-9c8246a26abb",
    "topic": "operations",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.084336",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 2,
    "question": "What is 45 \u00d7 20?",
    "options": [
      "906",
      "894",
      "900",
      "909"
    ],
    "answer": "900"
  },
  {
    "id": 3540,
    "uuid": "896b342c-427e-471d-bbd4-91d74c42c092",
    "topic": "operations",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.084348",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 2,
    "question": "What is 25 \u00f7 15 (integer division)?",
    "options": [
      "-1",
      "1",
      "-2",
      "5"
    ],
    "answer": "1"
  },
  {
    "id": 3544,
    "uuid": "ac7beaa0-7f67-4eb2-8d05-495b0dca4757",
    "topic": "fractions",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.084394",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 5,
    "question": "Simplify: 6/5 + 1/6",
    "options": [
      "41/30",
      "42/30",
      "43/30",
      "39/30"
    ],
    "answer": "41/30"
  },
  {
    "id": 3547,
    "uuid": "5d944a70-9fd6-4e47-8888-e5af8c9902d3",
    "topic": "fractions",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.084424",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 2,
    "question": "Simplify: 4/4 + 5/4",
    "options": [
      "8/4",
      "7/4",
      "10/4",
      "9/4"
    ],
    "answer": "9/4"
  },
  {
    "id": 3552,
    "uuid": "4393a2b5-34fa-4d0d-bf86-f03c547e31b9",
    "topic": "operations",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.084464",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 8,
    "question": "What is 25 \u00f7 19 (integer division)?",
    "options": [
      "-4",
      "3",
      "1",
      "-9"
    ],
    "answer": "1"
  },
  {
    "id": 3553,
    "uuid": "9ed987d3-2d5f-46b0-9d59-2615a31d2eff",
    "topic": "operations",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.084475",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 6,
    "question": "What is 16 - 49?",
    "options": [
      "-33",
      "-36",
      "-24",
      "-39"
    ],
    "answer": "-33"
  },
  {
    "id": 3554,
    "uuid": "dc742bb9-b7df-4a4f-adb6-46839390f6c6",
    "topic": "fractions",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.084491",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 10,
    "question": "Simplify: 4/3 + 6/4",
    "options": [
      "18/6",
      "14/6",
      "17/6",
      "15/6"
    ],
    "answer": "17/6"
  },
  {
    "id": 3556,
    "uuid": "52546f7d-eff5-46a5-a95b-ff5ce3e07204",
    "topic": "fractions",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.084514",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 2,
    "question": "Simplify: 2/9 + 5/4",
    "options": [
      "51/36",
      "56/36",
      "53/36",
      "54/36"
    ],
    "answer": "53/36"
  },
  {
    "id": 3559,
    "uuid": "7e4f6e6f-6052-491c-9e5f-388856e041cf",
    "topic": "fractions",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.084553",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 4,
    "question": "Simplify: 7/8 + 4/9",
    "options": [
      "92/72",
      "95/72",
      "93/72",
      "98/72"
    ],
    "answer": "95/72"
  },
  {
    "id": 3561,
    "uuid": "c061cd05-20f1-4293-a46d-3758709d19a0",
    "topic": "operations",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.084572",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 10,
    "question": "What is 20 \u00d7 35?",
    "options": [
      "695",
      "694",
      "690",
      "700"
    ],
    "answer": "700"
  },
  {
    "id": 3562,
    "uuid": "aaeeb851-0f72-43db-9a31-59584e8e00e8",
    "topic": "operations",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.084582",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 8,
    "question": "What is 7 - 37?",
    "options": [
      "-20",
      "-30",
      "-34",
      "-33"
    ],
    "answer": "-30"
  },
  {
    "id": 3564,
    "uuid": "1b08d3d2-3170-4d7c-930d-36c3b06acd40",
    "topic": "operations",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.084599",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 7,
    "question": "What is 1 + 4?",
    "options": [
      "15",
      "5",
      "0",
      "13"
    ],
    "answer": "5"
  },
  {
    "id": 3565,
    "uuid": "eeeb1e02-2289-4cb3-a517-5b8524ebbb04",
    "topic": "fractions",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.084615",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "question": "Simplify: 3/7 + 7/6",
    "options": [
      "67/42",
      "68/42",
      "69/42",
      "64/42"
    ],
    "answer": "67/42"
  },
  {
    "id": 3567,
    "uuid": "c0078352-44a9-4312-a11d-1966551262a4",
    "topic": "fractions",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.084638",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 2,
    "question": "Simplify: 4/2 + 5/7",
    "options": [
      "17/7",
      "19/7",
      "22/7",
      "21/7"
    ],
    "answer": "19/7"
  },
  {
    "id": 3573,
    "uuid": "cdbe599a-9c06-43d2-924c-5407ebffdfa4",
    "topic": "operations",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.084689",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 6,
    "question": "What is 23 \u00f7 14 (integer division)?",
    "options": [
      "-9",
      "1",
      "-5",
      "-7"
    ],
    "answer": "1"
  },
  {
    "id": 3575,
    "uuid": "50629ba6-a88f-4a3f-9d77-f4ce529af697",
    "topic": "operations",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.084706",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 2,
    "question": "What is 27 + 43?",
    "options": [
      "64",
      "61",
      "70",
      "79"
    ],
    "answer": "70"
  },
  {
    "id": 3579,
    "uuid": "fb80c24b-438f-414e-8f52-c7230c663069",
    "topic": "fractions",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.084743",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 9,
    "question": "Simplify: 3/5 + 8/3",
    "options": [
      "48/15",
      "50/15",
      "47/15",
      "49/15"
    ],
    "answer": "49/15"
  },
  {
    "id": 3582,
    "uuid": "4d8c1aee-d09b-4af3-a1bf-9ac906d48fc4",
    "topic": "operations",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.084771",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 4,
    "question": "What is 3 - 2?",
    "options": [
      "9",
      "-2",
      "1",
      "5"
    ],
    "answer": "1"
  },
  {
    "id": 3583,
    "uuid": "6fa06d7b-0686-41a7-b999-fe60341d22a5",
    "topic": "fractions",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.084797",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 9,
    "question": "Simplify: 5/8 + 6/8",
    "options": [
      "14/8",
      "12/8",
      "11/8",
      "9/8"
    ],
    "answer": "11/8"
  },
  {
    "id": 3587,
    "uuid": "85ec7191-5ce2-415c-a5ab-d0eb447bf439",
    "topic": "operations",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.084829",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 7,
    "question": "What is 7 \u00d7 7?",
    "options": [
      "49",
      "50",
      "51",
      "39"
    ],
    "answer": "49"
  },
  {
    "id": 3589,
    "uuid": "573a0b7e-8431-4033-913d-2828f0067ffa",
    "topic": "fractions",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.084872",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 7,
    "question": "Simplify: 8/4 + 5/7",
    "options": [
      "19/7",
      "17/7",
      "22/7",
      "18/7"
    ],
    "answer": "19/7"
  },
  {
    "id": 3594,
    "uuid": "f31382af-22fc-4635-a093-a6f3435c1257",
    "topic": "fractions",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.084946",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 8,
    "question": "Simplify: 7/7 + 7/7",
    "options": [
      "-1/1",
      "0/1",
      "5/1",
      "2/1"
    ],
    "answer": "2/1"
  },
  {
    "id": 3596,
    "uuid": "5c0cf81a-9e74-4069-989d-9788fb9883cd",
    "topic": "operations",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.084965",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 5,
    "question": "What is 40 - 29?",
    "options": [
      "3",
      "11",
      "5",
      "9"
    ],
    "answer": "11"
  },
  {
    "id": 3600,
    "uuid": "41c0aad3-69bb-472f-9127-f2ab9fe73481",
    "topic": "operations",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.084998",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "question": "What is 19 \u00f7 19 (integer division)?",
    "options": [
      "2",
      "5",
      "-5",
      "1"
    ],
    "answer": "1"
  },
  {
    "id": 3606,
    "uuid": "62c147a0-be0f-4ee8-ba0b-1963bfd29ce7",
    "topic": "operations",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.085054",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "question": "What is 37 \u00d7 45?",
    "options": [
      "1665",
      "1657",
      "1667",
      "1670"
    ],
    "answer": "1665"
  },
  {
    "id": 3620,
    "uuid": "b81da30b-b438-4e8a-bc00-3dfd7de98665",
    "topic": "operations",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.110436",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 9,
    "question": "What is 5 \u00d7 7?",
    "options": [
      "37",
      "35",
      "34",
      "28"
    ],
    "answer": "35"
  },
  {
    "id": 3621,
    "uuid": "62d7f778-8e89-41c3-adde-c6571d271cf6",
    "topic": "operations",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.110450",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "question": "What is 14 + 34?",
    "options": [
      "46",
      "47",
      "58",
      "48"
    ],
    "answer": "48"
  },
  {
    "id": 3628,
    "uuid": "7f197e8b-6b46-4223-91ce-46d342c3f7a1",
    "topic": "operations",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.110526",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 8,
    "question": "What is 13 + 3?",
    "options": [
      "16",
      "22",
      "9",
      "18"
    ],
    "answer": "16"
  },
  {
    "id": 3644,
    "uuid": "48b32202-68b6-4d6f-ab4f-3be837ffae68",
    "topic": "fractions",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.110740",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 7,
    "question": "Simplify: 9/7 + 4/7",
    "options": [
      "14/7",
      "13/7",
      "15/7",
      "11/7"
    ],
    "answer": "13/7"
  },
  {
    "id": 3647,
    "uuid": "ff812581-99e9-4625-ad2a-96b38095c656",
    "topic": "operations",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.110771",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 10,
    "question": "What is 5 \u00d7 44?",
    "options": [
      "220",
      "227",
      "218",
      "223"
    ],
    "answer": "220"
  },
  {
    "id": 3649,
    "uuid": "d53e43f1-ec8b-4c5c-80ef-96a7d6a598c7",
    "topic": "operations",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.110792",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 7,
    "question": "What is 10 \u00d7 33?",
    "options": [
      "330",
      "325",
      "334",
      "326"
    ],
    "answer": "330"
  },
  {
    "id": 3655,
    "uuid": "43f370d0-df24-420b-909f-a0838060ff0b",
    "topic": "operations",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.110882",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 8,
    "question": "What is 35 \u00f7 5 (integer division)?",
    "options": [
      "11",
      "7",
      "17",
      "-3"
    ],
    "answer": "7"
  },
  {
    "id": 3659,
    "uuid": "b9c82957-608a-4e85-b385-e0b9de88fced",
    "topic": "fractions",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.110964",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 3,
    "question": "Simplify: 8/8 + 4/2",
    "options": [
      "4/1",
      "0/1",
      "6/1",
      "3/1"
    ],
    "answer": "3/1"
  },
  {
    "id": 3663,
    "uuid": "18028833-0a68-4cb7-acb1-46c874ba3a14",
    "topic": "operations",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.111080",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 2,
    "question": "What is 23 \u00f7 15 (integer division)?",
    "options": [
      "-6",
      "6",
      "1",
      "10"
    ],
    "answer": "1"
  },
  {
    "id": 3666,
    "uuid": "cb972452-4b7d-459e-b56b-c1cb0aa2d296",
    "topic": "operations",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.111143",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 10,
    "question": "What is 39 \u00f7 17 (integer division)?",
    "options": [
      "-1",
      "1",
      "2",
      "-2"
    ],
    "answer": "2"
  },
  {
    "id": 3668,
    "uuid": "2a47979e-2c96-433f-9ccc-708b259797b9",
    "topic": "fractions",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.111204",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 3,
    "question": "Simplify: 5/4 + 7/7",
    "options": [
      "10/4",
      "9/4",
      "12/4",
      "7/4"
    ],
    "answer": "9/4"
  },
  {
    "id": 3670,
    "uuid": "bfc65705-2b6b-482a-ac99-355a9d692b27",
    "topic": "operations",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.111256",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 6,
    "question": "What is 30 \u00d7 2?",
    "options": [
      "59",
      "65",
      "60",
      "57"
    ],
    "answer": "60"
  },
  {
    "id": 3673,
    "uuid": "8d2cd2fb-c187-46ca-a8d6-18f25cf1bbba",
    "topic": "operations",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.111317",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 6,
    "question": "What is 5 - 26?",
    "options": [
      "-31",
      "-18",
      "-15",
      "-21"
    ],
    "answer": "-21"
  },
  {
    "id": 3680,
    "uuid": "72179cc5-26b0-4c78-933b-e4a66d9e6383",
    "topic": "fractions",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.111447",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 9,
    "question": "Simplify: 2/6 + 7/9",
    "options": [
      "13/9",
      "10/9",
      "11/9",
      "7/9"
    ],
    "answer": "10/9"
  },
  {
    "id": 3682,
    "uuid": "af01370b-320a-4f6f-8fae-cebc0f70f859",
    "topic": "operations",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.111502",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 9,
    "question": "What is 14 \u00f7 5 (integer division)?",
    "options": [
      "2",
      "3",
      "-4",
      "5"
    ],
    "answer": "2"
  },
  {
    "id": 3684,
    "uuid": "e8f5d4b5-35c1-4010-9131-4d3f29f441c2",
    "topic": "fractions",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.111564",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "question": "Simplify: 8/4 + 5/2",
    "options": [
      "12/2",
      "11/2",
      "9/2",
      "6/2"
    ],
    "answer": "9/2"
  },
  {
    "id": 3687,
    "uuid": "a2e45b1b-6442-4845-bc48-091692424986",
    "topic": "operations",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.111627",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 4,
    "question": "What is 36 \u00d7 50?",
    "options": [
      "1796",
      "1798",
      "1800",
      "1794"
    ],
    "answer": "1800"
  },
  {
    "id": 3690,
    "uuid": "44d0583d-e6db-4a19-8db8-2de935d0c078",
    "topic": "operations",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.111707",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 5,
    "question": "What is 34 - 39?",
    "options": [
      "-13",
      "-1",
      "2",
      "-5"
    ],
    "answer": "-5"
  },
  {
    "id": 3692,
    "uuid": "b7a49b4a-39fd-46be-bd3a-7ad5872c5231",
    "topic": "fractions",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.111767",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 10,
    "question": "Simplify: 9/5 + 6/6",
    "options": [
      "15/5",
      "14/5",
      "13/5",
      "11/5"
    ],
    "answer": "14/5"
  },
  {
    "id": 3701,
    "uuid": "0fbdcf0c-bb7d-4c22-92fb-85549c96e936",
    "topic": "operations",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.111932",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 9,
    "question": "What is 40 \u00f7 7 (integer division)?",
    "options": [
      "14",
      "11",
      "5",
      "9"
    ],
    "answer": "5"
  },
  {
    "id": 3707,
    "uuid": "f4a23c57-ca75-4ff8-8a1a-e7a5d3b2262b",
    "topic": "fractions",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.112034",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 3,
    "question": "Simplify: 9/5 + 7/5",
    "options": [
      "18/5",
      "17/5",
      "15/5",
      "16/5"
    ],
    "answer": "16/5"
  },
  {
    "id": 3709,
    "uuid": "1cb0fb23-3128-436a-8806-171eed85a32d",
    "topic": "fractions",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.112066",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 8,
    "question": "Simplify: 3/4 + 7/8",
    "options": [
      "14/8",
      "15/8",
      "16/8",
      "13/8"
    ],
    "answer": "13/8"
  },
  {
    "id": 3711,
    "uuid": "6eaad8be-e7b1-4f68-a1db-00c01bbd248c",
    "topic": "fractions",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.112100",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 3,
    "question": "Simplify: 9/2 + 8/6",
    "options": [
      "36/6",
      "35/6",
      "38/6",
      "33/6"
    ],
    "answer": "35/6"
  },
  {
    "id": 3717,
    "uuid": "d802bc0e-51c0-4db3-86a3-8b63aca59842",
    "topic": "operations",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.112146",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 8,
    "question": "What is 21 + 2?",
    "options": [
      "27",
      "16",
      "22",
      "23"
    ],
    "answer": "23"
  },
  {
    "id": 3720,
    "uuid": "3fa8c8ee-1fd1-4e3a-bab2-05e2aef779ea",
    "topic": "fractions",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.112188",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "question": "Simplify: 6/8 + 6/3",
    "options": [
      "13/4",
      "8/4",
      "12/4",
      "11/4"
    ],
    "answer": "11/4"
  },
  {
    "id": 3721,
    "uuid": "0d400a72-a224-4a73-b924-0c401f4472c0",
    "topic": "operations",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.112200",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 9,
    "question": "What is 42 + 24?",
    "options": [
      "61",
      "66",
      "56",
      "75"
    ],
    "answer": "66"
  },
  {
    "id": 3726,
    "uuid": "7ba113e5-61fd-4511-9f7c-8972f2a1783f",
    "topic": "fractions",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.112241",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "question": "Simplify: 4/2 + 2/3",
    "options": [
      "6/3",
      "10/3",
      "7/3",
      "8/3"
    ],
    "answer": "8/3"
  },
  {
    "id": 3728,
    "uuid": "e636b613-af3f-4f72-8e82-1e05fe4d347c",
    "topic": "fractions",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.112277",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 7,
    "question": "Simplify: 1/8 + 6/4",
    "options": [
      "14/8",
      "16/8",
      "13/8",
      "11/8"
    ],
    "answer": "13/8"
  },
  {
    "id": 3729,
    "uuid": "a73974e8-3608-4305-a1f5-89ab7bf7d1a0",
    "topic": "fractions",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.112293",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 7,
    "question": "Simplify: 1/2 + 8/5",
    "options": [
      "24/10",
      "18/10",
      "21/10",
      "19/10"
    ],
    "answer": "21/10"
  },
  {
    "id": 3730,
    "uuid": "d9f60d4b-02f4-4333-9627-9e100faf2bd8",
    "topic": "fractions",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.112319",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 8,
    "question": "Simplify: 5/9 + 6/5",
    "options": [
      "78/45",
      "82/45",
      "81/45",
      "79/45"
    ],
    "answer": "79/45"
  },
  {
    "id": 3734,
    "uuid": "de75d4a3-24ce-4595-bcf0-f5fcaac38af2",
    "topic": "operations",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.112351",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 5,
    "question": "What is 47 \u00f7 7 (integer division)?",
    "options": [
      "5",
      "6",
      "7",
      "16"
    ],
    "answer": "6"
  },
  {
    "id": 3743,
    "uuid": "5be99b76-53bd-4a30-82f4-50f6a2e6ce8f",
    "topic": "operations",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.112426",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 5,
    "question": "What is 33 \u00d7 39?",
    "options": [
      "1284",
      "1287",
      "1282",
      "1297"
    ],
    "answer": "1287"
  },
  {
    "id": 3745,
    "uuid": "8074d662-28f4-4ac8-9d77-00e645ffa853",
    "topic": "operations",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.112447",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 7,
    "question": "What is 49 \u00d7 47?",
    "options": [
      "2303",
      "2312",
      "2304",
      "2294"
    ],
    "answer": "2303"
  },
  {
    "id": 3747,
    "uuid": "9d0c7051-e245-4df3-9d12-ee4127a19421",
    "topic": "operations",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.112464",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 8,
    "question": "What is 4 - 30?",
    "options": [
      "-17",
      "-26",
      "-31",
      "-28"
    ],
    "answer": "-26"
  },
  {
    "id": 3756,
    "uuid": "7d55b1a9-c492-4245-9e09-dd2553239574",
    "topic": "fractions",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.112532",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 6,
    "question": "Simplify: 1/6 + 6/2",
    "options": [
      "17/6",
      "20/6",
      "21/6",
      "19/6"
    ],
    "answer": "19/6"
  },
  {
    "id": 3764,
    "uuid": "9719d4e3-7988-47af-90f0-53c45bf6201a",
    "topic": "operations",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.112604",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 6,
    "question": "What is 34 \u00f7 8 (integer division)?",
    "options": [
      "4",
      "11",
      "10",
      "0"
    ],
    "answer": "4"
  },
  {
    "id": 3770,
    "uuid": "2f4f32f7-b544-40f9-9333-bf77916e52c3",
    "topic": "operations",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.112649",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 4,
    "question": "What is 49 - 27?",
    "options": [
      "29",
      "17",
      "27",
      "22"
    ],
    "answer": "22"
  },
  {
    "id": 3775,
    "uuid": "bc48158a-d114-4902-bdea-51059814054d",
    "topic": "fractions",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.112709",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "question": "Simplify: 7/2 + 9/6",
    "options": [
      "2/1",
      "5/1",
      "6/1",
      "8/1"
    ],
    "answer": "5/1"
  },
  {
    "id": 3776,
    "uuid": "e6af216c-ed36-4470-95b4-6b652444c1ff",
    "topic": "operations",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.112725",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 10,
    "question": "What is 28 - 37?",
    "options": [
      "-6",
      "0",
      "-9",
      "-17"
    ],
    "answer": "-9"
  },
  {
    "id": 3779,
    "uuid": "7a9c03bf-5b7b-4ff5-b24e-7198c6364ff7",
    "topic": "operations",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.112756",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 3,
    "question": "What is 46 - 22?",
    "options": [
      "28",
      "24",
      "27",
      "18"
    ],
    "answer": "24"
  },
  {
    "id": 3784,
    "uuid": "51fcccc0-44fc-4cb3-a852-301f1f341ba8",
    "topic": "operations",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.112799",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 9,
    "question": "What is 10 - 24?",
    "options": [
      "-12",
      "-13",
      "-15",
      "-14"
    ],
    "answer": "-14"
  },
  {
    "id": 3785,
    "uuid": "09b429b5-4c0c-4a62-8bd2-f83b27a2d16b",
    "topic": "fractions",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.112826",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 8,
    "question": "Simplify: 4/3 + 4/6",
    "options": [
      "2/1",
      "5/1",
      "0/1",
      "1/1"
    ],
    "answer": "2/1"
  },
  {
    "id": 3786,
    "uuid": "d6cc32c3-716b-4196-bb9e-5fae40ec0ac5",
    "topic": "fractions",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.112846",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 4,
    "question": "Simplify: 2/3 + 6/6",
    "options": [
      "5/3",
      "6/3",
      "7/3",
      "2/3"
    ],
    "answer": "5/3"
  },
  {
    "id": 3793,
    "uuid": "f2babc41-5ae4-4490-9f08-e5da31990750",
    "topic": "operations",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.112906",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 8,
    "question": "What is 27 + 10?",
    "options": [
      "46",
      "37",
      "41",
      "31"
    ],
    "answer": "37"
  },
  {
    "id": 3798,
    "uuid": "9bd6579c-ac97-4dca-ac14-388394b65230",
    "topic": "fractions",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.112953",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 2,
    "question": "Simplify: 2/5 + 7/3",
    "options": [
      "41/15",
      "40/15",
      "44/15",
      "39/15"
    ],
    "answer": "41/15"
  },
  {
    "id": 3799,
    "uuid": "e87c2c2f-e5f1-4dfe-afc6-6bc7ecd46f0d",
    "topic": "operations",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.112975",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 6,
    "question": "What is 23 \u00f7 16 (integer division)?",
    "options": [
      "11",
      "1",
      "-9",
      "5"
    ],
    "answer": "1"
  },
  {
    "id": 3803,
    "uuid": "09dfab98-a24a-4c0e-b8a3-271d6ecb3c7d",
    "topic": "operations",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.113012",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 9,
    "question": "What is 14 \u00d7 48?",
    "options": [
      "672",
      "663",
      "673",
      "682"
    ],
    "answer": "672"
  },
  {
    "id": 3805,
    "uuid": "da4b69b5-1b72-41b7-bffa-3b1736617011",
    "topic": "operations",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.113029",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 9,
    "question": "What is 18 - 1?",
    "options": [
      "21",
      "17",
      "15",
      "20"
    ],
    "answer": "17"
  },
  {
    "id": 3806,
    "uuid": "d1f5b0b4-1e9e-47a7-99b8-a078b39db699",
    "topic": "fractions",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.113066",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 2,
    "question": "Simplify: 4/8 + 9/3",
    "options": [
      "5/2",
      "7/2",
      "10/2",
      "4/2"
    ],
    "answer": "7/2"
  },
  {
    "id": 3807,
    "uuid": "82b33967-5104-4221-ab77-38eebd729373",
    "topic": "operations",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.113077",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 3,
    "question": "What is 49 + 21?",
    "options": [
      "68",
      "67",
      "72",
      "70"
    ],
    "answer": "70"
  },
  {
    "id": 3808,
    "uuid": "a37378cb-765a-46e8-a58b-3fcd6cd045f0",
    "topic": "fractions",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.113093",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 2,
    "question": "Simplify: 1/3 + 4/4",
    "options": [
      "2/3",
      "7/3",
      "4/3",
      "3/3"
    ],
    "answer": "4/3"
  },
  {
    "id": 3812,
    "uuid": "913c34ac-3c41-4a80-8130-8e010cf5c672",
    "topic": "operations",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.113126",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "question": "What is 30 \u00d7 48?",
    "options": [
      "1450",
      "1445",
      "1440",
      "1443"
    ],
    "answer": "1440"
  },
  {
    "id": 3813,
    "uuid": "bcba6650-d210-4ca5-88d1-227267517a0f",
    "topic": "operations",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.113137",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 2,
    "question": "What is 23 + 9?",
    "options": [
      "25",
      "30",
      "32",
      "23"
    ],
    "answer": "32"
  },
  {
    "id": 3817,
    "uuid": "3d1f0c00-b758-4aab-ae5a-3845bdb7e00d",
    "topic": "fractions",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.113174",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 5,
    "question": "Simplify: 4/9 + 1/7",
    "options": [
      "38/63",
      "34/63",
      "40/63",
      "37/63"
    ],
    "answer": "37/63"
  },
  {
    "id": 3822,
    "uuid": "bc6c1f36-4bb4-4d64-b63e-05721871222e",
    "topic": "fractions",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.113225",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 3,
    "question": "Simplify: 8/8 + 8/3",
    "options": [
      "14/3",
      "9/3",
      "13/3",
      "11/3"
    ],
    "answer": "11/3"
  },
  {
    "id": 3831,
    "uuid": "91a91f51-f20c-4ee1-9785-b3deaca6eb80",
    "topic": "operations",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.113324",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 5,
    "question": "What is 11 - 47?",
    "options": [
      "-26",
      "-40",
      "-36",
      "-37"
    ],
    "answer": "-36"
  },
  {
    "id": 3841,
    "uuid": "ff0ccba4-9187-43fe-a8f9-e8b7ba19920b",
    "topic": "operations",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.113407",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 7,
    "question": "What is 14 - 25?",
    "options": [
      "-13",
      "-11",
      "-4",
      "-21"
    ],
    "answer": "-11"
  },
  {
    "id": 3844,
    "uuid": "b2be3da6-9207-40ea-af11-a406aa95e4c4",
    "topic": "fractions",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.113436",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "question": "Simplify: 3/3 + 3/9",
    "options": [
      "3/3",
      "4/3",
      "5/3",
      "1/3"
    ],
    "answer": "4/3"
  },
  {
    "id": 3847,
    "uuid": "0c533483-bd74-482e-a434-ae60909d5832",
    "topic": "fractions",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.113473",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 8,
    "question": "Simplify: 3/4 + 5/9",
    "options": [
      "44/36",
      "48/36",
      "45/36",
      "47/36"
    ],
    "answer": "47/36"
  },
  {
    "id": 3853,
    "uuid": "cd5ecbf7-1a89-4aac-a8fd-6a064d8a38f8",
    "topic": "operations",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.113519",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 6,
    "question": "What is 21 - 11?",
    "options": [
      "10",
      "15",
      "3",
      "8"
    ],
    "answer": "10"
  },
  {
    "id": 3857,
    "uuid": "a79a8e99-b7db-4fb0-b88a-0fa9b1c7225a",
    "topic": "operations",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.113551",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 2,
    "question": "What is 28 \u00f7 7 (integer division)?",
    "options": [
      "7",
      "1",
      "14",
      "4"
    ],
    "answer": "4"
  },
  {
    "id": 3858,
    "uuid": "f6bab09e-7a64-4e9c-b59a-240b367c43fd",
    "topic": "fractions",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.113567",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 10,
    "question": "Simplify: 8/7 + 6/9",
    "options": [
      "36/21",
      "41/21",
      "38/21",
      "40/21"
    ],
    "answer": "38/21"
  },
  {
    "id": 3861,
    "uuid": "262fef12-706e-45cc-b7cd-036061b28be9",
    "topic": "operations",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.113594",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 7,
    "question": "What is 26 - 34?",
    "options": [
      "-15",
      "-12",
      "-17",
      "-8"
    ],
    "answer": "-8"
  },
  {
    "id": 3875,
    "uuid": "b0c16472-a82c-4e9c-8d88-b1ebf22c527f",
    "topic": "fractions",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.113702",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 5,
    "question": "Simplify: 8/6 + 4/4",
    "options": [
      "10/3",
      "5/3",
      "7/3",
      "6/3"
    ],
    "answer": "7/3"
  },
  {
    "id": 3894,
    "uuid": "08cde88e-f2a5-424e-aedf-674f7fe470e4",
    "topic": "operations",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.113841",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 2,
    "question": "What is 46 \u00d7 12?",
    "options": [
      "552",
      "547",
      "562",
      "546"
    ],
    "answer": "552"
  },
  {
    "id": 3896,
    "uuid": "d5dcdf70-150e-4ca8-b49c-f9e44cf0ed1f",
    "topic": "operations",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.113860",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 2,
    "question": "What is 27 - 44?",
    "options": [
      "-14",
      "-17",
      "-22",
      "-20"
    ],
    "answer": "-17"
  },
  {
    "id": 3899,
    "uuid": "477935b3-2069-47f5-baa0-75f7eab2138d",
    "topic": "operations",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.113885",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 6,
    "question": "What is 11 \u00d7 45?",
    "options": [
      "495",
      "485",
      "492",
      "496"
    ],
    "answer": "495"
  },
  {
    "id": 3907,
    "uuid": "b83c4965-e750-410f-81e0-fcdbf3ca3552",
    "topic": "fractions",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.113964",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 3,
    "question": "Simplify: 7/3 + 2/2",
    "options": [
      "10/3",
      "8/3",
      "12/3",
      "9/3"
    ],
    "answer": "10/3"
  },
  {
    "id": 3908,
    "uuid": "a0202d7e-ffb4-434b-93ee-41063e2fc352",
    "topic": "fractions",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.113994",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 4,
    "question": "Simplify: 1/4 + 4/9",
    "options": [
      "25/36",
      "23/36",
      "26/36",
      "27/36"
    ],
    "answer": "25/36"
  },
  {
    "id": 3912,
    "uuid": "3a1fb569-7a6e-421c-aa1d-ca2c3595b2ca",
    "topic": "operations",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.114029",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 7,
    "question": "What is 40 \u00d7 15?",
    "options": [
      "598",
      "600",
      "610",
      "594"
    ],
    "answer": "600"
  },
  {
    "id": 3922,
    "uuid": "0baaa7ea-62be-40af-99d6-da3724264ea3",
    "topic": "operations",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.114106",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 10,
    "question": "What is 29 - 18?",
    "options": [
      "11",
      "12",
      "19",
      "1"
    ],
    "answer": "11"
  },
  {
    "id": 3928,
    "uuid": "4b68b48a-80be-4e08-b6ce-715cf5ddddb0",
    "topic": "fractions",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.114159",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 9,
    "question": "Simplify: 9/9 + 4/6",
    "options": [
      "5/3",
      "4/3",
      "7/3",
      "6/3"
    ],
    "answer": "5/3"
  },
  {
    "id": 3930,
    "uuid": "b613ae06-c9de-4959-a5be-a4a72c00f7dd",
    "topic": "operations",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.114178",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 2,
    "question": "What is 27 + 45?",
    "options": [
      "76",
      "72",
      "82",
      "62"
    ],
    "answer": "72"
  },
  {
    "id": 3943,
    "uuid": "f9688cc6-802f-402e-8cb2-33017744c214",
    "topic": "operations",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.114269",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 3,
    "question": "What is 42 \u00f7 14 (integer division)?",
    "options": [
      "8",
      "3",
      "11",
      "0"
    ],
    "answer": "3"
  },
  {
    "id": 3945,
    "uuid": "a8e85be2-b0fe-418f-8de6-3bd76d38abff",
    "topic": "fractions",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.114300",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 9,
    "question": "Simplify: 6/9 + 2/6",
    "options": [
      "-2/1",
      "-1/1",
      "1/1",
      "4/1"
    ],
    "answer": "1/1"
  },
  {
    "id": 3952,
    "uuid": "8107959b-ccf8-44d2-a211-c68e098d07ec",
    "topic": "operations",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.114354",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 2,
    "question": "What is 47 + 6?",
    "options": [
      "53",
      "45",
      "47",
      "57"
    ],
    "answer": "53"
  },
  {
    "id": 3955,
    "uuid": "9f13f245-6d5d-4f54-b05d-53e4815df4f0",
    "topic": "fractions",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.114400",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 3,
    "question": "Simplify: 8/9 + 6/8",
    "options": [
      "59/36",
      "56/36",
      "62/36",
      "57/36"
    ],
    "answer": "59/36"
  },
  {
    "id": 3956,
    "uuid": "21db03c5-9fbd-4917-8cbe-038079266b8b",
    "topic": "operations",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.114412",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 4,
    "question": "What is 13 \u00f7 7 (integer division)?",
    "options": [
      "1",
      "-3",
      "-1",
      "0"
    ],
    "answer": "1"
  },
  {
    "id": 3979,
    "uuid": "75634327-9030-42b2-acbd-c7facca130aa",
    "topic": "operations",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.114690",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 7,
    "question": "What is 40 + 38?",
    "options": [
      "69",
      "78",
      "86",
      "88"
    ],
    "answer": "78"
  },
  {
    "id": 3982,
    "uuid": "36f2e96a-00b0-4a76-98c6-8e9c31237b36",
    "topic": "fractions",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.114728",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 6,
    "question": "Simplify: 4/6 + 5/7",
    "options": [
      "29/21",
      "27/21",
      "32/21",
      "30/21"
    ],
    "answer": "29/21"
  },
  {
    "id": 3996,
    "uuid": "f187a819-b222-4c7d-9699-4ef3d85aa5a5",
    "topic": "fractions",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.114852",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 4,
    "question": "Simplify: 1/7 + 3/7",
    "options": [
      "5/7",
      "1/7",
      "3/7",
      "4/7"
    ],
    "answer": "4/7"
  },
  {
    "id": 3998,
    "uuid": "3bf015ef-b380-4162-8347-517b4abb75b3",
    "topic": "fractions",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.114884",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 3,
    "question": "Simplify: 8/8 + 5/2",
    "options": [
      "7/2",
      "9/2",
      "10/2",
      "6/2"
    ],
    "answer": "7/2"
  },
  {
    "id": 3999,
    "uuid": "3c6c68f0-4007-4751-9b07-431fbc88761e",
    "topic": "fractions",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.114903",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 5,
    "question": "Simplify: 2/6 + 1/7",
    "options": [
      "8/21",
      "10/21",
      "7/21",
      "11/21"
    ],
    "answer": "10/21"
  },
  {
    "id": 4013,
    "uuid": "b490de82-c9ff-4109-9ee1-14fd062a9014",
    "topic": "fractions",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.115011",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 10,
    "question": "Simplify: 6/7 + 4/6",
    "options": [
      "31/21",
      "33/21",
      "35/21",
      "32/21"
    ],
    "answer": "32/21"
  },
  {
    "id": 4017,
    "uuid": "510047fb-1691-484a-96c5-2c2beebe08cf",
    "topic": "operations",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.115042",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 9,
    "question": "What is 37 \u00d7 34?",
    "options": [
      "1258",
      "1253",
      "1250",
      "1265"
    ],
    "answer": "1258"
  },
  {
    "id": 4019,
    "uuid": "d306bb33-b014-402c-b364-7123d10ceeef",
    "topic": "fractions",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.115066",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "question": "Simplify: 4/5 + 2/5",
    "options": [
      "5/5",
      "9/5",
      "7/5",
      "6/5"
    ],
    "answer": "6/5"
  },
  {
    "id": 4022,
    "uuid": "c658f08a-72d4-4feb-9863-903ef580d93b",
    "topic": "fractions",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.115106",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 9,
    "question": "Simplify: 2/7 + 8/5",
    "options": [
      "69/35",
      "63/35",
      "67/35",
      "66/35"
    ],
    "answer": "66/35"
  },
  {
    "id": 4029,
    "uuid": "7e9f4237-5559-4204-ae24-2644664f6e90",
    "topic": "operations",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.115156",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 8,
    "question": "What is 5 - 21?",
    "options": [
      "-17",
      "-25",
      "-16",
      "-20"
    ],
    "answer": "-16"
  },
  {
    "id": 4041,
    "uuid": "3f898ea0-972c-4836-9a80-322101555b45",
    "topic": "fractions",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.115267",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 8,
    "question": "Simplify: 3/6 + 3/3",
    "options": [
      "6/2",
      "1/2",
      "3/2",
      "4/2"
    ],
    "answer": "3/2"
  },
  {
    "id": 4043,
    "uuid": "592ee4c9-df75-4493-ab42-5bc9a56c8829",
    "topic": "fractions",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.115290",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "question": "Simplify: 7/8 + 3/2",
    "options": [
      "21/8",
      "19/8",
      "20/8",
      "17/8"
    ],
    "answer": "19/8"
  },
  {
    "id": 4044,
    "uuid": "64e56ec2-d3f4-4e73-8b03-7c533c94b6a9",
    "topic": "operations",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.115302",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 9,
    "question": "What is 23 - 37?",
    "options": [
      "-20",
      "-4",
      "-14",
      "-13"
    ],
    "answer": "-14"
  },
  {
    "id": 4049,
    "uuid": "8e4399bf-340c-4464-8e3f-e71cc5f3203e",
    "topic": "fractions",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.115349",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 3,
    "question": "Simplify: 6/3 + 5/7",
    "options": [
      "21/7",
      "22/7",
      "17/7",
      "19/7"
    ],
    "answer": "19/7"
  },
  {
    "id": 4051,
    "uuid": "2a2b193c-7045-4c1a-b100-3737907a0f37",
    "topic": "operations",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.115367",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 7,
    "question": "What is 25 \u00d7 3?",
    "options": [
      "65",
      "75",
      "70",
      "82"
    ],
    "answer": "75"
  },
  {
    "id": 4056,
    "uuid": "d0cc8f03-2d6a-48f9-a003-c29adbfd798e",
    "topic": "operations",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.115403",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 7,
    "question": "What is 17 \u00d7 6?",
    "options": [
      "100",
      "104",
      "102",
      "105"
    ],
    "answer": "102"
  },
  {
    "id": 4064,
    "uuid": "ad0494f3-e936-4cd2-a7b5-051beb30a0e9",
    "topic": "operations",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.115470",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 8,
    "question": "What is 6 - 7?",
    "options": [
      "-1",
      "-11",
      "6",
      "1"
    ],
    "answer": "-1"
  },
  {
    "id": 4069,
    "uuid": "8ce40bc9-b174-4168-8a1d-baf9d9327996",
    "topic": "fractions",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.115516",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 5,
    "question": "Simplify: 5/6 + 2/3",
    "options": [
      "6/2",
      "4/2",
      "2/2",
      "3/2"
    ],
    "answer": "3/2"
  },
  {
    "id": 4075,
    "uuid": "2a98b777-678d-416a-b4ab-2ffb55d0c8f9",
    "topic": "fractions",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.115582",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 3,
    "question": "Simplify: 7/9 + 1/6",
    "options": [
      "17/18",
      "18/18",
      "20/18",
      "19/18"
    ],
    "answer": "17/18"
  },
  {
    "id": 4076,
    "uuid": "90610fdd-2c7b-423e-b0e3-0810c2f99b5e",
    "topic": "fractions",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.115610",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 3,
    "question": "Simplify: 6/4 + 3/4",
    "options": [
      "11/4",
      "6/4",
      "10/4",
      "9/4"
    ],
    "answer": "9/4"
  },
  {
    "id": 4078,
    "uuid": "e925b4f5-e2d3-4490-9922-887b9acab127",
    "topic": "operations",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.115629",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 8,
    "question": "What is 28 \u00d7 33?",
    "options": [
      "924",
      "931",
      "927",
      "923"
    ],
    "answer": "924"
  },
  {
    "id": 4092,
    "uuid": "3c68a371-c0d4-4425-9d8c-420ebc38bb40",
    "topic": "operations",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.115755",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 4,
    "question": "What is 4 - 37?",
    "options": [
      "-27",
      "-32",
      "-38",
      "-33"
    ],
    "answer": "-33"
  },
  {
    "id": 4093,
    "uuid": "527c8f83-0f5d-4bdf-89d9-b6b6f18e0a82",
    "topic": "operations",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.115766",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 3,
    "question": "What is 6 \u00d7 49?",
    "options": [
      "299",
      "304",
      "294",
      "302"
    ],
    "answer": "294"
  },
  {
    "id": 4094,
    "uuid": "016008e1-154a-4825-8e34-f3d664e5e5d3",
    "topic": "fractions",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.115782",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 7,
    "question": "Simplify: 9/6 + 9/5",
    "options": [
      "33/10",
      "36/10",
      "35/10",
      "32/10"
    ],
    "answer": "33/10"
  },
  {
    "id": 4098,
    "uuid": "e737ea11-ae36-4aa7-86eb-e7be3619c123",
    "topic": "operations",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.115812",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 4,
    "question": "What is 14 \u00d7 13?",
    "options": [
      "174",
      "189",
      "182",
      "172"
    ],
    "answer": "182"
  },
  {
    "id": 4103,
    "uuid": "f1d96a8e-a57d-4fb5-a43a-a8e22e617f12",
    "topic": "fractions",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.115857",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 8,
    "question": "Simplify: 7/2 + 7/9",
    "options": [
      "80/18",
      "77/18",
      "76/18",
      "79/18"
    ],
    "answer": "77/18"
  },
  {
    "id": 4104,
    "uuid": "7dc89762-a327-43f4-9dd7-46e9e60f7a17",
    "topic": "fractions",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.115881",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 9,
    "question": "Simplify: 1/7 + 4/8",
    "options": [
      "11/14",
      "12/14",
      "8/14",
      "9/14"
    ],
    "answer": "9/14"
  },
  {
    "id": 4108,
    "uuid": "7f91ca1b-7c37-443e-8b9f-e0a68cc47d80",
    "topic": "operations",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.115911",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 8,
    "question": "What is 11 \u00d7 6?",
    "options": [
      "62",
      "73",
      "66",
      "76"
    ],
    "answer": "66"
  },
  {
    "id": 4118,
    "uuid": "59925f9b-9ab4-4704-8c3b-aeca6f523e26",
    "topic": "fractions",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.115992",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 7,
    "question": "Simplify: 5/6 + 2/6",
    "options": [
      "8/6",
      "5/6",
      "7/6",
      "10/6"
    ],
    "answer": "7/6"
  },
  {
    "id": 4124,
    "uuid": "16bef56b-4fc0-41a8-8714-1f7b8a52c73c",
    "topic": "operations",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.116037",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 4,
    "question": "What is 31 \u00d7 2?",
    "options": [
      "62",
      "60",
      "71",
      "61"
    ],
    "answer": "62"
  },
  {
    "id": 4127,
    "uuid": "afa22ada-5b6f-4049-ba4c-55c0fac1f1c5",
    "topic": "fractions",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.116071",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 6,
    "question": "Simplify: 3/2 + 5/2",
    "options": [
      "2/1",
      "3/1",
      "6/1",
      "4/1"
    ],
    "answer": "4/1"
  },
  {
    "id": 4137,
    "uuid": "9841a987-585f-4325-9ea6-655599dbd2fa",
    "topic": "fractions",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.116183",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 8,
    "question": "Simplify: 4/4 + 9/7",
    "options": [
      "16/7",
      "13/7",
      "15/7",
      "17/7"
    ],
    "answer": "16/7"
  },
  {
    "id": 4140,
    "uuid": "14292ec0-e65a-4964-9692-c014e941a1a2",
    "topic": "fractions",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.116219",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 5,
    "question": "Simplify: 9/6 + 2/5",
    "options": [
      "22/10",
      "19/10",
      "17/10",
      "21/10"
    ],
    "answer": "19/10"
  },
  {
    "id": 4141,
    "uuid": "caae28d6-89f9-4d0c-8995-9bd80897f27a",
    "topic": "operations",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.116230",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 10,
    "question": "What is 30 \u00d7 7?",
    "options": [
      "214",
      "218",
      "212",
      "210"
    ],
    "answer": "210"
  },
  {
    "id": 4148,
    "uuid": "15becb9a-35ae-48d0-8c55-b06d8fd00d8b",
    "topic": "operations",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.116283",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 8,
    "question": "What is 8 + 30?",
    "options": [
      "34",
      "47",
      "40",
      "38"
    ],
    "answer": "38"
  },
  {
    "id": 4150,
    "uuid": "6d791392-8e88-4e85-be2c-029c0530002d",
    "topic": "operations",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.116300",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 10,
    "question": "What is 43 + 3?",
    "options": [
      "46",
      "50",
      "37",
      "48"
    ],
    "answer": "46"
  },
  {
    "id": 4151,
    "uuid": "b524abcf-8740-49ea-bb56-1a3397ecfc5d",
    "topic": "operations",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.116312",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 2,
    "question": "What is 32 \u00f7 20 (integer division)?",
    "options": [
      "-4",
      "1",
      "7",
      "-6"
    ],
    "answer": "1"
  },
  {
    "id": 4164,
    "uuid": "bb0af355-35b3-4785-ace1-5fe2e8e9d92d",
    "topic": "operations",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.116429",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 6,
    "question": "What is 13 + 46?",
    "options": [
      "59",
      "50",
      "56",
      "63"
    ],
    "answer": "59"
  },
  {
    "id": 4169,
    "uuid": "0401bd39-6593-4235-a986-07a77905a800",
    "topic": "fractions",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.116515",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 9,
    "question": "Simplify: 2/6 + 3/7",
    "options": [
      "13/21",
      "19/21",
      "14/21",
      "16/21"
    ],
    "answer": "16/21"
  },
  {
    "id": 4170,
    "uuid": "f76d32d5-d560-49e3-bf7c-7f0032c2789a",
    "topic": "fractions",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.150758",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 5,
    "question": "Simplify: 6/6 + 7/7",
    "options": [
      "2/1",
      "4/1",
      "0/1",
      "1/1"
    ],
    "answer": "2/1"
  },
  {
    "id": 4175,
    "uuid": "7ae48e3b-1a23-4435-889a-c6bb7a3becbc",
    "topic": "operations",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.150911",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 2,
    "question": "What is 14 + 36?",
    "options": [
      "50",
      "58",
      "46",
      "54"
    ],
    "answer": "50"
  },
  {
    "id": 4188,
    "uuid": "9872f353-87b1-4d95-ae7d-20805e4f612c",
    "topic": "fractions",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.151061",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 8,
    "question": "Simplify: 6/2 + 8/8",
    "options": [
      "6/1",
      "7/1",
      "4/1",
      "1/1"
    ],
    "answer": "4/1"
  },
  {
    "id": 4189,
    "uuid": "cf3434a8-7c5e-4a26-af19-56b1151867a7",
    "topic": "fractions",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.151091",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 10,
    "question": "Simplify: 1/6 + 9/8",
    "options": [
      "33/24",
      "32/24",
      "31/24",
      "28/24"
    ],
    "answer": "31/24"
  },
  {
    "id": 4191,
    "uuid": "520752bc-7083-40bd-b444-874ba1d99c4a",
    "topic": "fractions",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.151125",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 6,
    "question": "Simplify: 7/6 + 6/8",
    "options": [
      "24/12",
      "20/12",
      "22/12",
      "23/12"
    ],
    "answer": "23/12"
  },
  {
    "id": 4201,
    "uuid": "54f25d79-e688-4192-987b-6d3f9886a9c7",
    "topic": "fractions",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.151210",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 6,
    "question": "Simplify: 2/7 + 4/3",
    "options": [
      "35/21",
      "34/21",
      "32/21",
      "36/21"
    ],
    "answer": "34/21"
  },
  {
    "id": 4202,
    "uuid": "8c5bcfac-ce2d-4864-9ad1-c00415e1a903",
    "topic": "fractions",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.151234",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 6,
    "question": "Simplify: 7/2 + 3/4",
    "options": [
      "19/4",
      "14/4",
      "18/4",
      "17/4"
    ],
    "answer": "17/4"
  },
  {
    "id": 4212,
    "uuid": "3d45c007-d667-4631-ac29-ad30b78814ae",
    "topic": "operations",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.151318",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 4,
    "question": "What is 11 + 48?",
    "options": [
      "51",
      "59",
      "50",
      "58"
    ],
    "answer": "59"
  },
  {
    "id": 4215,
    "uuid": "5d073287-c000-4413-b07a-f4d3791c4b2f",
    "topic": "operations",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.151370",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 7,
    "question": "What is 15 \u00f7 4 (integer division)?",
    "options": [
      "-5",
      "-7",
      "3",
      "8"
    ],
    "answer": "3"
  },
  {
    "id": 4217,
    "uuid": "8e95e9fb-6ce5-4bed-9425-cf51355e3c89",
    "topic": "operations",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.151387",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 7,
    "question": "What is 37 + 20?",
    "options": [
      "55",
      "59",
      "51",
      "57"
    ],
    "answer": "57"
  },
  {
    "id": 4230,
    "uuid": "30b98732-870f-4006-875b-01657e30dee2",
    "topic": "operations",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.151511",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 8,
    "question": "What is 22 - 19?",
    "options": [
      "3",
      "8",
      "7",
      "-6"
    ],
    "answer": "3"
  },
  {
    "id": 4236,
    "uuid": "238d5310-7c2a-4d47-aad9-3ca4209f0349",
    "topic": "fractions",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.151591",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 5,
    "question": "Simplify: 9/9 + 3/4",
    "options": [
      "7/4",
      "9/4",
      "5/4",
      "8/4"
    ],
    "answer": "7/4"
  },
  {
    "id": 4237,
    "uuid": "8058c2b7-e3a3-464c-8b28-24e2130029a9",
    "topic": "operations",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.151618",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 7,
    "question": "What is 49 + 14?",
    "options": [
      "63",
      "72",
      "69",
      "61"
    ],
    "answer": "63"
  },
  {
    "id": 4238,
    "uuid": "9abaf86b-ef24-482d-a13b-a49be340f863",
    "topic": "operations",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.151630",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 7,
    "question": "What is 28 - 25?",
    "options": [
      "-5",
      "3",
      "6",
      "13"
    ],
    "answer": "3"
  },
  {
    "id": 4240,
    "uuid": "249ede7e-0377-4b14-8bdb-fb0eaa9237bf",
    "topic": "operations",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.151664",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 10,
    "question": "What is 40 \u00f7 15 (integer division)?",
    "options": [
      "6",
      "11",
      "2",
      "3"
    ],
    "answer": "2"
  },
  {
    "id": 4243,
    "uuid": "5e5c9d09-8345-418f-b35d-ac0e32fdd6ea",
    "topic": "fractions",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.151719",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 3,
    "question": "Simplify: 8/3 + 2/2",
    "options": [
      "9/3",
      "14/3",
      "10/3",
      "11/3"
    ],
    "answer": "11/3"
  },
  {
    "id": 4244,
    "uuid": "6540b1cc-f5b6-4b5c-b41e-ddad4f019c0b",
    "topic": "fractions",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.151750",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 4,
    "question": "Simplify: 1/8 + 9/4",
    "options": [
      "21/8",
      "17/8",
      "19/8",
      "18/8"
    ],
    "answer": "19/8"
  },
  {
    "id": 4252,
    "uuid": "1b8a7c8c-4544-4234-8ffc-465a1e223e4c",
    "topic": "operations",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.151822",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 2,
    "question": "What is 25 \u00d7 17?",
    "options": [
      "432",
      "425",
      "431",
      "424"
    ],
    "answer": "425"
  },
  {
    "id": 4254,
    "uuid": "4fa4637e-0d17-4ff9-9cdc-eedf62f64aa8",
    "topic": "fractions",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.151846",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 7,
    "question": "Simplify: 6/7 + 5/4",
    "options": [
      "56/28",
      "60/28",
      "59/28",
      "62/28"
    ],
    "answer": "59/28"
  },
  {
    "id": 4257,
    "uuid": "dd075bed-5742-4782-bd8a-c23543851f77",
    "topic": "fractions",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.151889",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 7,
    "question": "Simplify: 1/5 + 3/4",
    "options": [
      "19/20",
      "16/20",
      "20/20",
      "17/20"
    ],
    "answer": "19/20"
  },
  {
    "id": 4259,
    "uuid": "94510cc4-9afe-426d-9beb-093102cbce34",
    "topic": "fractions",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.151928",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 5,
    "question": "Simplify: 9/9 + 9/9",
    "options": [
      "3/1",
      "5/1",
      "0/1",
      "2/1"
    ],
    "answer": "2/1"
  },
  {
    "id": 4262,
    "uuid": "37c54bdb-47dd-44b6-9934-f7c8edee2978",
    "topic": "operations",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.151972",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 2,
    "question": "What is 2 + 21?",
    "options": [
      "23",
      "18",
      "14",
      "29"
    ],
    "answer": "23"
  },
  {
    "id": 4263,
    "uuid": "82cba61a-10d2-4ebf-ad9c-c4c1f68b4506",
    "topic": "fractions",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.151988",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 2,
    "question": "Simplify: 1/4 + 3/2",
    "options": [
      "7/4",
      "6/4",
      "4/4",
      "9/4"
    ],
    "answer": "7/4"
  },
  {
    "id": 4265,
    "uuid": "8541a691-4b88-4b58-b2b7-28980a930a55",
    "topic": "fractions",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.152022",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 3,
    "question": "Simplify: 2/2 + 5/8",
    "options": [
      "16/8",
      "11/8",
      "12/8",
      "13/8"
    ],
    "answer": "13/8"
  },
  {
    "id": 4267,
    "uuid": "f16aa4cd-d107-4394-a94a-cc737bdf60e4",
    "topic": "operations",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.152041",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 10,
    "question": "What is 15 \u00f7 2 (integer division)?",
    "options": [
      "6",
      "14",
      "7",
      "12"
    ],
    "answer": "7"
  },
  {
    "id": 4272,
    "uuid": "a29f5e29-7c28-4f9f-9cd6-942a0619b315",
    "topic": "operations",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.152082",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 7,
    "question": "What is 28 + 4?",
    "options": [
      "41",
      "36",
      "32",
      "30"
    ],
    "answer": "32"
  },
  {
    "id": 4277,
    "uuid": "23b48bc1-f23c-4e34-bce1-ff6fd809c55b",
    "topic": "operations",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.152126",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 9,
    "question": "What is 40 \u00d7 9?",
    "options": [
      "352",
      "368",
      "354",
      "360"
    ],
    "answer": "360"
  },
  {
    "id": 4282,
    "uuid": "9f86ace4-a348-4055-90de-7c8e1e4cf001",
    "topic": "fractions",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.152173",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 10,
    "question": "Simplify: 2/7 + 9/7",
    "options": [
      "14/7",
      "8/7",
      "10/7",
      "11/7"
    ],
    "answer": "11/7"
  },
  {
    "id": 4288,
    "uuid": "b6d4adcc-d31b-45e2-aa30-533f24dd9553",
    "topic": "fractions",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.152243",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 5,
    "question": "Simplify: 5/9 + 8/5",
    "options": [
      "95/45",
      "97/45",
      "100/45",
      "99/45"
    ],
    "answer": "97/45"
  },
  {
    "id": 4298,
    "uuid": "b6b7c737-1b2d-4892-a14e-3fd7e98dc9fa",
    "topic": "fractions",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.152362",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 10,
    "question": "Simplify: 5/4 + 7/8",
    "options": [
      "17/8",
      "20/8",
      "15/8",
      "19/8"
    ],
    "answer": "17/8"
  },
  {
    "id": 4299,
    "uuid": "0a96abfb-d42c-403f-b092-b0d61691e3ee",
    "topic": "fractions",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.152406",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "question": "Simplify: 1/5 + 7/5",
    "options": [
      "11/5",
      "5/5",
      "9/5",
      "8/5"
    ],
    "answer": "8/5"
  },
  {
    "id": 4303,
    "uuid": "781acdac-8fae-4325-8813-12861cf6e061",
    "topic": "fractions",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.152473",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 9,
    "question": "Simplify: 7/6 + 2/6",
    "options": [
      "6/2",
      "2/2",
      "4/2",
      "3/2"
    ],
    "answer": "3/2"
  },
  {
    "id": 4307,
    "uuid": "4871d9bb-7f4a-4a45-a0de-82f575ddc840",
    "topic": "fractions",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.152539",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 3,
    "question": "Simplify: 3/5 + 6/8",
    "options": [
      "29/20",
      "24/20",
      "27/20",
      "30/20"
    ],
    "answer": "27/20"
  },
  {
    "id": 4308,
    "uuid": "b16acd1a-da9f-4779-a89c-43061bd66714",
    "topic": "fractions",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.152555",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "question": "Simplify: 7/4 + 5/9",
    "options": [
      "86/36",
      "83/36",
      "85/36",
      "81/36"
    ],
    "answer": "83/36"
  },
  {
    "id": 4310,
    "uuid": "f301955e-e5c7-4d69-ba35-085a91339bbb",
    "topic": "operations",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.152575",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 5,
    "question": "What is 37 + 3?",
    "options": [
      "39",
      "43",
      "40",
      "44"
    ],
    "answer": "40"
  },
  {
    "id": 4311,
    "uuid": "3a590154-7c7a-486c-b2ed-48655a0bdc15",
    "topic": "fractions",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.152604",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 2,
    "question": "Simplify: 8/9 + 4/7",
    "options": [
      "91/63",
      "89/63",
      "92/63",
      "94/63"
    ],
    "answer": "92/63"
  },
  {
    "id": 4317,
    "uuid": "545f2298-ab04-431d-8041-5a3c2e055212",
    "topic": "fractions",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.152761",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 4,
    "question": "Simplify: 6/4 + 9/9",
    "options": [
      "3/2",
      "5/2",
      "6/2",
      "7/2"
    ],
    "answer": "5/2"
  },
  {
    "id": 4325,
    "uuid": "d4d0e462-83fb-400e-a95a-3acf37c757ac",
    "topic": "operations",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.152825",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 3,
    "question": "What is 16 \u00d7 15?",
    "options": [
      "231",
      "232",
      "242",
      "240"
    ],
    "answer": "240"
  },
  {
    "id": 4327,
    "uuid": "b8f75371-30ae-44ff-a79c-04126442fe2e",
    "topic": "operations",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.152847",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "question": "What is 32 + 46?",
    "options": [
      "83",
      "79",
      "85",
      "78"
    ],
    "answer": "78"
  },
  {
    "id": 4338,
    "uuid": "15a824f2-8176-45f5-9b0b-58463656310a",
    "topic": "fractions",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.152996",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 9,
    "question": "Simplify: 5/8 + 4/2",
    "options": [
      "24/8",
      "18/8",
      "21/8",
      "23/8"
    ],
    "answer": "21/8"
  },
  {
    "id": 4341,
    "uuid": "086d33f2-0d2e-43f9-9448-8004d6cdc054",
    "topic": "operations",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.153026",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 10,
    "question": "What is 50 \u00f7 14 (integer division)?",
    "options": [
      "-6",
      "2",
      "3",
      "-5"
    ],
    "answer": "3"
  },
  {
    "id": 4347,
    "uuid": "5092c746-b5b1-4696-9a50-0f1121f257b6",
    "topic": "operations",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.153081",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 10,
    "question": "What is 7 + 3?",
    "options": [
      "9",
      "3",
      "13",
      "10"
    ],
    "answer": "10"
  },
  {
    "id": 4348,
    "uuid": "6ff2b276-1d3a-49b9-924a-8dc3c6a301c3",
    "topic": "fractions",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.153099",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 7,
    "question": "Simplify: 8/3 + 9/5",
    "options": [
      "64/15",
      "67/15",
      "66/15",
      "70/15"
    ],
    "answer": "67/15"
  },
  {
    "id": 4357,
    "uuid": "bacec66c-c3ec-41d9-97fa-bcd49139a2d4",
    "topic": "operations",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.153182",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 8,
    "question": "What is 31 \u00f7 6 (integer division)?",
    "options": [
      "12",
      "-5",
      "15",
      "5"
    ],
    "answer": "5"
  },
  {
    "id": 4358,
    "uuid": "3c5b16bb-71b0-4251-9922-1f02db9af9bd",
    "topic": "fractions",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.153220",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 9,
    "question": "Simplify: 4/9 + 4/7",
    "options": [
      "65/63",
      "64/63",
      "61/63",
      "63/63"
    ],
    "answer": "64/63"
  },
  {
    "id": 4368,
    "uuid": "3836c7c9-dc76-4009-9001-7a7447b9be17",
    "topic": "operations",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.153309",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 8,
    "question": "What is 23 \u00d7 43?",
    "options": [
      "988",
      "985",
      "989",
      "991"
    ],
    "answer": "989"
  },
  {
    "id": 4370,
    "uuid": "37efe8eb-66b9-4636-935f-57e6817303a5",
    "topic": "operations",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.153330",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 8,
    "question": "What is 47 - 3?",
    "options": [
      "45",
      "47",
      "44",
      "50"
    ],
    "answer": "44"
  },
  {
    "id": 4374,
    "uuid": "b086907b-9f56-46dc-9821-454c102cf970",
    "topic": "fractions",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.153379",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 5,
    "question": "Simplify: 7/3 + 6/6",
    "options": [
      "11/3",
      "12/3",
      "8/3",
      "10/3"
    ],
    "answer": "10/3"
  },
  {
    "id": 4375,
    "uuid": "9842152a-0849-4b55-a026-4bff1441cf0c",
    "topic": "operations",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.153395",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 10,
    "question": "What is 9 \u00d7 24?",
    "options": [
      "206",
      "215",
      "207",
      "216"
    ],
    "answer": "216"
  },
  {
    "id": 4383,
    "uuid": "bca9c31b-71a5-46c9-84c6-ccec65d34240",
    "topic": "operations",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.153473",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "question": "What is 38 \u00d7 6?",
    "options": [
      "225",
      "228",
      "237",
      "223"
    ],
    "answer": "228"
  },
  {
    "id": 4398,
    "uuid": "41f49b66-68fb-4604-b502-1ebe85ed92f4",
    "topic": "operations",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.153624",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "question": "What is 17 - 7?",
    "options": [
      "10",
      "0",
      "16",
      "2"
    ],
    "answer": "10"
  },
  {
    "id": 4400,
    "uuid": "5f58dff6-7ef1-4136-a2e9-17fb99b033cd",
    "topic": "fractions",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.153675",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 4,
    "question": "Simplify: 4/4 + 8/6",
    "options": [
      "9/3",
      "10/3",
      "6/3",
      "7/3"
    ],
    "answer": "7/3"
  },
  {
    "id": 4404,
    "uuid": "52109edc-b57d-4eaf-8c97-3caee264fb69",
    "topic": "fractions",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.153750",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 4,
    "question": "Simplify: 5/8 + 4/3",
    "options": [
      "44/24",
      "47/24",
      "45/24",
      "50/24"
    ],
    "answer": "47/24"
  },
  {
    "id": 4410,
    "uuid": "67bcf72b-ecff-4c8b-a605-a726c30fda9f",
    "topic": "fractions",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.153832",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "question": "Simplify: 6/8 + 3/6",
    "options": [
      "6/4",
      "5/4",
      "8/4",
      "7/4"
    ],
    "answer": "5/4"
  },
  {
    "id": 4417,
    "uuid": "e5c7a00e-8d28-4d73-8449-5191fc2e609f",
    "topic": "operations",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.153899",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "question": "What is 20 \u00f7 2 (integer division)?",
    "options": [
      "13",
      "16",
      "11",
      "10"
    ],
    "answer": "10"
  },
  {
    "id": 4433,
    "uuid": "dd0a2e3f-337d-409d-852a-3ebba2d7aa33",
    "topic": "operations",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.154024",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 5,
    "question": "What is 23 \u00f7 8 (integer division)?",
    "options": [
      "2",
      "-6",
      "-7",
      "-8"
    ],
    "answer": "2"
  },
  {
    "id": 4436,
    "uuid": "714889a5-f5a8-410b-a3a6-c4b7faf029ed",
    "topic": "operations",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.154050",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 10,
    "question": "What is 18 \u00d7 29?",
    "options": [
      "522",
      "528",
      "526",
      "524"
    ],
    "answer": "522"
  },
  {
    "id": 4451,
    "uuid": "de0d86e1-a465-4590-972d-3fd7b1a23658",
    "topic": "operations",
    "created_at": "2025-09-22T08:40:39.154172",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 6,
    "question": "What is 49 \u00d7 4?",
    "options": [
      "196",
      "205",
      "204",
      "191"
    ],
    "answer": "196"
  },
  {
    "id": 10001,
    "uuid": "3325a2e8-b93f-4e1b-b6c1-3cabb0d20f3f",
    "topic": "biology",
    "created_at": "2025-09-29T08:53:01",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "question": "Which organelle is responsible for protein synthesis?",
    "options": [
      "Mitochondria",
      "Ribosome",
      "Nucleus",
      "Golgi apparatus"
    ],
    "answer": "Ribosome"
  },
  {
    "id": 10002,
    "uuid": "49bf0afc-f6d7-4598-9cc5-735f99492a26",
    "topic": "biology",
    "created_at": "2025-09-29T08:53:01",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 2,
    "question": "What molecule carries genetic information in most living organisms?",
    "options": [
      "RNA",
      "Protein",
      "DNA",
      "Lipid"
    ],
    "answer": "DNA"
  },
  {
    "id": 10003,
    "uuid": "b1ef3882-b336-4652-b09f-e7de6b86667b",
    "topic": "biology",
    "created_at": "2025-09-29T08:53:01",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 3,
    "question": "Which blood cells are primarily responsible for fighting infections?",
    "options": [
      "Red blood cells",
      "White blood cells",
      "Platelets",
      "Plasma"
    ],
    "answer": "White blood cells"
  },
  {
    "id": 10004,
    "uuid": "de30f1cc-5397-4289-b70f-f80ee75d1c8a",
    "topic": "biology",
    "created_at": "2025-09-29T08:53:01",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 4,
    "question": "Which part of the plant carries out photosynthesis?",
    "options": [
      "Roots",
      "Leaves",
      "Stems",
      "Flowers"
    ],
    "answer": "Leaves"
  },
  {
    "id": 10005,
    "uuid": "569f5f78-7c2e-4ca1-9612-cb1bd4c25c7c",
    "topic": "biology",
    "created_at": "2025-09-29T08:53:01",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 5,
    "question": "Which scientist proposed the theory of natural selection?",
    "options": [
      "Gregor Mendel",
      "Louis Pasteur",
      "Charles Darwin",
      "Carl Linnaeus"
    ],
    "answer": "Charles Darwin"
  },
  {
    "id": 10006,
    "uuid": "d19efc92-2e93-436e-9161-b1fa5a76a61c",
    "topic": "biology",
    "created_at": "2025-09-29T08:53:01",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 6,
    "question": "Which gas do plants absorb during photosynthesis?",
    "options": [
      "Oxygen",
      "Carbon dioxide",
      "Nitrogen",
      "Hydrogen"
    ],
    "answer": "Carbon dioxide"
  },
  {
    "id": 10007,
    "uuid": "6a54d01e-6b6f-427a-a59e-2ce147b30dab",
    "topic": "biology",
    "created_at": "2025-09-29T08:53:01",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 7,
    "question": "What is the functional unit of the kidney?",
    "options": [
      "Neuron",
      "Nephron",
      "Alveoli",
      "Villus"
    ],
    "answer": "Nephron"
  },
  {
    "id": 10008,
    "uuid": "057b390f-bfa0-4ebe-b143-74577a19e051",
    "topic": "biology",
    "created_at": "2025-09-29T08:53:01",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 8,
    "question": "Which macromolecule is the main source of energy for living organisms?",
    "options": [
      "Proteins",
      "Carbohydrates",
      "Lipids",
      "Nucleic acids"
    ],
    "answer": "Carbohydrates"
  },
  {
    "id": 10009,
    "uuid": "4dfba347-b492-4f61-a6df-1a681b305fa3",
    "topic": "biology",
    "created_at": "2025-09-29T08:53:01",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 9,
    "question": "What pigment in plants captures light for photosynthesis?",
    "options": [
      "Chlorophyll",
      "Carotene",
      "Xanthophyll",
      "Anthocyanin"
    ],
    "answer": "Chlorophyll"
  },
  {
    "id": 10010,
    "uuid": "0fc960d3-2d29-4341-9842-cb0b8ab07b6a",
    "topic": "biology",
    "created_at": "2025-09-29T08:53:01",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 10,
    "question": "Which organ controls most of the body\u2019s functions?",
    "options": [
      "Heart",
      "Lungs",
      "Brain",
      "Liver"
    ],
    "answer": "Brain"
  },
  {
    "id": 10001,
    "uuid": "1c5f2a07-df83-4524-abe9-7ce17c70ee88",
    "topic": "biology",
    "created_at": "2025-09-29T15:33:36",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "question": "Which organelle is responsible for packaging and modifying proteins in eukaryotic cells?",
    "options": [
      "Ribosome",
      "Golgi apparatus",
      "Mitochondria",
      "Endoplasmic reticulum"
    ],
    "answer": "Golgi apparatus"
  },
  {
    "id": 10002,
    "uuid": "9b025e34-d629-438f-b906-056cff7b48bc",
    "topic": "biology",
    "created_at": "2025-09-29T15:33:36",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 2,
    "question": "What is the semi-fluid substance inside the cell that surrounds organelles?",
    "options": [
      "Cytoplasm",
      "Nucleus",
      "Chloroplast",
      "Mitochondria"
    ],
    "answer": "Cytoplasm"
  },
  {
    "id": 10003,
    "uuid": "8b3d448f-b7e2-4cc7-9db8-325b8be0f220",
    "topic": "biology",
    "created_at": "2025-09-29T15:33:36",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 3,
    "question": "Which part of the cell controls most activities and stores genetic information?",
    "options": [
      "Cytoplasm",
      "Nucleus",
      "Golgi apparatus",
      "Lysosome"
    ],
    "answer": "Nucleus"
  },
  {
    "id": 10004,
    "uuid": "1bb77714-8a05-40d5-ac39-1b4afeb1684b",
    "topic": "biology",
    "created_at": "2025-09-29T15:33:36",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 4,
    "question": "Which organelle is responsible for breaking down waste and cellular debris?",
    "options": [
      "Mitochondria",
      "Lysosome",
      "Ribosome",
      "Chloroplast"
    ],
    "answer": "Lysosome"
  },
  {
    "id": 10005,
    "uuid": "9e09ebe6-4856-42f9-9bce-3b1358c95a72",
    "topic": "biology",
    "created_at": "2025-09-29T15:33:36",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 5,
    "question": "What is the powerhouse of the cell?",
    "options": [
      "Nucleus",
      "Mitochondria",
      "Ribosome",
      "Chloroplast"
    ],
    "answer": "Mitochondria"
  },
  {
    "id": 10006,
    "uuid": "8027835b-3bdb-4df2-92d5-0bac1631ed90",
    "topic": "biology",
    "created_at": "2025-09-29T15:33:36",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 6,
    "question": "Who is considered the father of modern genetics?",
    "options": [
      "Charles Darwin",
      "Gregor Mendel",
      "Louis Pasteur",
      "Robert Hooke"
    ],
    "answer": "Gregor Mendel"
  },
  {
    "id": 10007,
    "uuid": "e51adc39-cd48-4c38-ba0e-fbed9ad67626",
    "topic": "biology",
    "created_at": "2025-09-29T15:33:36",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 7,
    "question": "Which base pairs with adenine in DNA?",
    "options": [
      "Guanine",
      "Cytosine",
      "Thymine",
      "Uracil"
    ],
    "answer": "Thymine"
  },
  {
    "id": 10008,
    "uuid": "a733c720-05ea-4920-aa31-7db85597fd0d",
    "topic": "biology",
    "created_at": "2025-09-29T15:33:36",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 8,
    "question": "What is the shape of DNA described as?",
    "options": [
      "Triple helix",
      "Double helix",
      "Single strand",
      "Spiral ladder"
    ],
    "answer": "Double helix"
  },
  {
    "id": 10009,
    "uuid": "fe4ba1a7-03e0-44d8-ad49-de1ee98227a3",
    "topic": "biology",
    "created_at": "2025-09-29T15:33:36",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 9,
    "question": "Which type of RNA carries amino acids to ribosomes?",
    "options": [
      "mRNA",
      "tRNA",
      "rRNA",
      "snRNA"
    ],
    "answer": "tRNA"
  },
  {
    "id": 10010,
    "uuid": "809b13e9-a62a-450b-9266-b0d34d7f2aea",
    "topic": "biology",
    "created_at": "2025-09-29T15:33:36",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 10,
    "question": "Which process creates gametes with half the number of chromosomes?",
    "options": [
      "Mitosis",
      "Meiosis",
      "Binary fission",
      "Budding"
    ],
    "answer": "Meiosis"
  },
  {
    "id": 10011,
    "uuid": "cb454e82-facd-46c3-b020-62d16c787424",
    "topic": "biology",
    "created_at": "2025-09-29T15:33:36",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "question": "Which part of the human brain controls balance and coordination?",
    "options": [
      "Cerebrum",
      "Cerebellum",
      "Medulla",
      "Hypothalamus"
    ],
    "answer": "Cerebellum"
  },
  {
    "id": 10012,
    "uuid": "4c37470f-469e-42f7-9282-8a981b9dd5fe",
    "topic": "biology",
    "created_at": "2025-09-29T15:33:36",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 2,
    "question": "Which blood vessels carry blood away from the heart?",
    "options": [
      "Arteries",
      "Veins",
      "Capillaries",
      "Venules"
    ],
    "answer": "Arteries"
  },
  {
    "id": 10013,
    "uuid": "f0c4b65c-e295-4411-84da-ccfebd9a2ffc",
    "topic": "biology",
    "created_at": "2025-09-29T15:33:36",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 3,
    "question": "Which protein in red blood cells carries oxygen?",
    "options": [
      "Collagen",
      "Keratin",
      "Hemoglobin",
      "Albumin"
    ],
    "answer": "Hemoglobin"
  },
  {
    "id": 10014,
    "uuid": "f21e80ed-0192-4f21-8a6c-a0c766b2838e",
    "topic": "biology",
    "created_at": "2025-09-29T15:33:36",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 4,
    "question": "Which organ is primarily responsible for detoxification?",
    "options": [
      "Kidney",
      "Liver",
      "Lung",
      "Pancreas"
    ],
    "answer": "Liver"
  },
  {
    "id": 10015,
    "uuid": "82497d8f-ba75-48ae-8c44-eba1f7242721",
    "topic": "biology",
    "created_at": "2025-09-29T15:33:36",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 5,
    "question": "Which gland regulates metabolism through hormone secretion?",
    "options": [
      "Adrenal",
      "Thyroid",
      "Pituitary",
      "Pancreas"
    ],
    "answer": "Thyroid"
  },
  {
    "id": 10016,
    "uuid": "d87526a7-2571-4519-843a-11364a52844d",
    "topic": "biology",
    "created_at": "2025-09-29T15:33:36",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 6,
    "question": "What term describes organisms that produce their own food?",
    "options": [
      "Consumers",
      "Decomposers",
      "Producers",
      "Parasites"
    ],
    "answer": "Producers"
  },
  {
    "id": 10017,
    "uuid": "f54fe091-643f-4bc4-beb0-702de86b2838",
    "topic": "biology",
    "created_at": "2025-09-29T15:33:36",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 7,
    "question": "Which biome is characterized by permafrost?",
    "options": [
      "Desert",
      "Savanna",
      "Tundra",
      "Rainforest"
    ],
    "answer": "Tundra"
  },
  {
    "id": 10018,
    "uuid": "ad879253-a173-4a13-876d-afcf29f83a1f",
    "topic": "biology",
    "created_at": "2025-09-29T15:33:36",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 8,
    "question": "What is the main source of energy for almost all ecosystems?",
    "options": [
      "Wind",
      "Water",
      "Sunlight",
      "Soil"
    ],
    "answer": "Sunlight"
  },
  {
    "id": 10019,
    "uuid": "d6e2f595-906d-429a-9715-08cd4e2d6c02",
    "topic": "biology",
    "created_at": "2025-09-29T15:33:36",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 9,
    "question": "What is the symbiotic relationship where both species benefit?",
    "options": [
      "Parasitism",
      "Commensalism",
      "Mutualism",
      "Predation"
    ],
    "answer": "Mutualism"
  },
  {
    "id": 10020,
    "uuid": "3fcb3f36-96ed-40cc-a726-dc64c030d8da",
    "topic": "biology",
    "created_at": "2025-09-29T15:33:36",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 10,
    "question": "Which gas do plants absorb during photosynthesis?",
    "options": [
      "Oxygen",
      "Carbon dioxide",
      "Nitrogen",
      "Hydrogen"
    ],
    "answer": "Carbon dioxide"
  },
  {
    "id": 10021,
    "uuid": "b7657e80-ebaa-496e-b547-f777fc6a6251",
    "topic": "biology",
    "created_at": "2025-09-29T15:33:36",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "question": "Who proposed the theory of natural selection?",
    "options": [
      "Gregor Mendel",
      "Louis Pasteur",
      "Charles Darwin",
      "Robert Hooke"
    ],
    "answer": "Charles Darwin"
  },
  {
    "id": 10022,
    "uuid": "19af4fb4-85a3-419a-ad09-ff92925e0fab",
    "topic": "biology",
    "created_at": "2025-09-29T15:33:36",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 2,
    "question": "What term describes structures that are similar due to shared ancestry?",
    "options": [
      "Analogous",
      "Homologous",
      "Vestigial",
      "Derived"
    ],
    "answer": "Homologous"
  },
  {
    "id": 10023,
    "uuid": "7e0c9369-c7c6-4010-b278-6f9ac150933e",
    "topic": "biology",
    "created_at": "2025-09-29T15:33:36",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 3,
    "question": "Which term refers to the random change in allele frequency in small populations?",
    "options": [
      "Natural selection",
      "Genetic drift",
      "Mutation",
      "Speciation"
    ],
    "answer": "Genetic drift"
  },
  {
    "id": 10024,
    "uuid": "b2a0a3f6-3370-424e-84cc-6b7a4f728598",
    "topic": "biology",
    "created_at": "2025-09-29T15:33:36",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 4,
    "question": "What is the preserved remains of ancient organisms called?",
    "options": [
      "Fossil",
      "Mineral",
      "Imprint",
      "Sediment"
    ],
    "answer": "Fossil"
  },
  {
    "id": 10025,
    "uuid": "75450844-75cb-447c-9a8a-37deb2021507",
    "topic": "biology",
    "created_at": "2025-09-29T15:33:36",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 5,
    "question": "Which islands did Darwin study finches that influenced his theory?",
    "options": [
      "Hawaiian",
      "Gal\u00e1pagos",
      "Philippines",
      "Caribbean"
    ],
    "answer": "Gal\u00e1pagos"
  },
  {
    "id": 10026,
    "uuid": "c0acf0f5-28f2-4eda-a3a6-45a600c1488d",
    "topic": "biology",
    "created_at": "2025-09-29T15:33:36",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 6,
    "question": "Which organelle is responsible for packaging and modifying proteins in eukaryotic cells? [Set 1]",
    "options": [
      "Ribosome",
      "Golgi apparatus",
      "Mitochondria",
      "Endoplasmic reticulum"
    ],
    "answer": "Golgi apparatus"
  },
  {
    "id": 10027,
    "uuid": "785972a6-7035-42ff-8971-ef28b2f1e375",
    "topic": "biology",
    "created_at": "2025-09-29T15:33:36",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 7,
    "question": "What is the semi-fluid substance inside the cell that surrounds organelles? [Set 1]",
    "options": [
      "Cytoplasm",
      "Nucleus",
      "Chloroplast",
      "Mitochondria"
    ],
    "answer": "Cytoplasm"
  },
  {
    "id": 10028,
    "uuid": "fbcc50bc-5e17-464a-b213-33709b3abf67",
    "topic": "biology",
    "created_at": "2025-09-29T15:33:36",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 8,
    "question": "Which part of the cell controls most activities and stores genetic information? [Set 1]",
    "options": [
      "Cytoplasm",
      "Nucleus",
      "Golgi apparatus",
      "Lysosome"
    ],
    "answer": "Nucleus"
  },
  {
    "id": 10029,
    "uuid": "c36a5805-e99d-4bd3-af0a-8c3936e6a144",
    "topic": "biology",
    "created_at": "2025-09-29T15:33:36",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 9,
    "question": "Which organelle is responsible for breaking down waste and cellular debris? [Set 1]",
    "options": [
      "Mitochondria",
      "Lysosome",
      "Ribosome",
      "Chloroplast"
    ],
    "answer": "Lysosome"
  },
  {
    "id": 10030,
    "uuid": "257faca0-5d3d-472c-af1f-806c61308eab",
    "topic": "biology",
    "created_at": "2025-09-29T15:33:36",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 10,
    "question": "What is the powerhouse of the cell? [Set 1]",
    "options": [
      "Nucleus",
      "Mitochondria",
      "Ribosome",
      "Chloroplast"
    ],
    "answer": "Mitochondria"
  },
  {
    "id": 10031,
    "uuid": "a87488d8-434a-4dbf-a3bb-bf5726fb708a",
    "topic": "biology",
    "created_at": "2025-09-29T15:33:36",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "question": "Who is considered the father of modern genetics? [Set 1]",
    "options": [
      "Charles Darwin",
      "Gregor Mendel",
      "Louis Pasteur",
      "Robert Hooke"
    ],
    "answer": "Gregor Mendel"
  },
  {
    "id": 10032,
    "uuid": "93a43a58-d5b2-4367-a04b-6f96b8ae42a8",
    "topic": "biology",
    "created_at": "2025-09-29T15:33:36",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 2,
    "question": "Which base pairs with adenine in DNA? [Set 1]",
    "options": [
      "Guanine",
      "Cytosine",
      "Thymine",
      "Uracil"
    ],
    "answer": "Thymine"
  },
  {
    "id": 10033,
    "uuid": "de25804f-1405-4aa3-9519-f67a34e4e419",
    "topic": "biology",
    "created_at": "2025-09-29T15:33:36",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 3,
    "question": "What is the shape of DNA described as? [Set 1]",
    "options": [
      "Triple helix",
      "Double helix",
      "Single strand",
      "Spiral ladder"
    ],
    "answer": "Double helix"
  },
  {
    "id": 10034,
    "uuid": "7fcf3923-1c74-473d-b0ad-00cd25177103",
    "topic": "biology",
    "created_at": "2025-09-29T15:33:36",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 4,
    "question": "Which type of RNA carries amino acids to ribosomes? [Set 1]",
    "options": [
      "mRNA",
      "tRNA",
      "rRNA",
      "snRNA"
    ],
    "answer": "tRNA"
  },
  {
    "id": 10035,
    "uuid": "c0ce6d50-63f5-4ba8-a65a-3bea804aa3a6",
    "topic": "biology",
    "created_at": "2025-09-29T15:33:36",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 5,
    "question": "Which process creates gametes with half the number of chromosomes? [Set 1]",
    "options": [
      "Mitosis",
      "Meiosis",
      "Binary fission",
      "Budding"
    ],
    "answer": "Meiosis"
  },
  {
    "id": 10036,
    "uuid": "8f4af531-003a-4e18-946c-1e755e764ff8",
    "topic": "biology",
    "created_at": "2025-09-29T15:33:36",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 6,
    "question": "Which part of the human brain controls balance and coordination? [Set 1]",
    "options": [
      "Cerebrum",
      "Cerebellum",
      "Medulla",
      "Hypothalamus"
    ],
    "answer": "Cerebellum"
  },
  {
    "id": 10037,
    "uuid": "f5f84e49-5f17-4599-866a-a83ba3bec4a3",
    "topic": "biology",
    "created_at": "2025-09-29T15:33:36",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 7,
    "question": "Which blood vessels carry blood away from the heart? [Set 1]",
    "options": [
      "Arteries",
      "Veins",
      "Capillaries",
      "Venules"
    ],
    "answer": "Arteries"
  },
  {
    "id": 10038,
    "uuid": "35233856-83fc-4766-ae28-f0374bdc76e4",
    "topic": "biology",
    "created_at": "2025-09-29T15:33:36",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 8,
    "question": "Which protein in red blood cells carries oxygen? [Set 1]",
    "options": [
      "Collagen",
      "Keratin",
      "Hemoglobin",
      "Albumin"
    ],
    "answer": "Hemoglobin"
  },
  {
    "id": 10039,
    "uuid": "559ec610-fc8c-4d2f-b5bd-770d42fc1967",
    "topic": "biology",
    "created_at": "2025-09-29T15:33:36",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 9,
    "question": "Which organ is primarily responsible for detoxification? [Set 1]",
    "options": [
      "Kidney",
      "Liver",
      "Lung",
      "Pancreas"
    ],
    "answer": "Liver"
  },
  {
    "id": 10040,
    "uuid": "f30f70a7-69ad-4ae5-b7b0-0691ea3730fd",
    "topic": "biology",
    "created_at": "2025-09-29T15:33:36",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 10,
    "question": "Which gland regulates metabolism through hormone secretion? [Set 1]",
    "options": [
      "Adrenal",
      "Thyroid",
      "Pituitary",
      "Pancreas"
    ],
    "answer": "Thyroid"
  },
  {
    "id": 10041,
    "uuid": "1e143e0c-5b29-4a28-8366-87855f093aed",
    "topic": "biology",
    "created_at": "2025-09-29T15:33:36",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "question": "What term describes organisms that produce their own food? [Set 1]",
    "options": [
      "Consumers",
      "Decomposers",
      "Producers",
      "Parasites"
    ],
    "answer": "Producers"
  },
  {
    "id": 10042,
    "uuid": "aa96ad46-b875-4fa4-aa19-6666bf1e385a",
    "topic": "biology",
    "created_at": "2025-09-29T15:33:36",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 2,
    "question": "Which biome is characterized by permafrost? [Set 1]",
    "options": [
      "Desert",
      "Savanna",
      "Tundra",
      "Rainforest"
    ],
    "answer": "Tundra"
  },
  {
    "id": 10043,
    "uuid": "5ca9a760-2f6a-41a6-9fdc-35f6d7a2bdf9",
    "topic": "biology",
    "created_at": "2025-09-29T15:33:36",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 3,
    "question": "What is the main source of energy for almost all ecosystems? [Set 1]",
    "options": [
      "Wind",
      "Water",
      "Sunlight",
      "Soil"
    ],
    "answer": "Sunlight"
  },
  {
    "id": 10044,
    "uuid": "47c5db5c-0e48-445c-bcd8-c1b3edbe0e1a",
    "topic": "biology",
    "created_at": "2025-09-29T15:33:36",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 4,
    "question": "What is the symbiotic relationship where both species benefit? [Set 1]",
    "options": [
      "Parasitism",
      "Commensalism",
      "Mutualism",
      "Predation"
    ],
    "answer": "Mutualism"
  },
  {
    "id": 10045,
    "uuid": "a13116c3-8a56-4f24-8099-0ad4e8710197",
    "topic": "biology",
    "created_at": "2025-09-29T15:33:36",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 5,
    "question": "Which gas do plants absorb during photosynthesis? [Set 1]",
    "options": [
      "Oxygen",
      "Carbon dioxide",
      "Nitrogen",
      "Hydrogen"
    ],
    "answer": "Carbon dioxide"
  },
  {
    "id": 10046,
    "uuid": "02cd0cca-2a50-4377-be80-f21d4eff14ef",
    "topic": "biology",
    "created_at": "2025-09-29T15:33:36",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 6,
    "question": "Who proposed the theory of natural selection? [Set 1]",
    "options": [
      "Gregor Mendel",
      "Louis Pasteur",
      "Charles Darwin",
      "Robert Hooke"
    ],
    "answer": "Charles Darwin"
  },
  {
    "id": 10047,
    "uuid": "1b863f18-fb9c-4b1c-8558-c5d1eb40938d",
    "topic": "biology",
    "created_at": "2025-09-29T15:33:36",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 7,
    "question": "What term describes structures that are similar due to shared ancestry? [Set 1]",
    "options": [
      "Analogous",
      "Homologous",
      "Vestigial",
      "Derived"
    ],
    "answer": "Homologous"
  },
  {
    "id": 10048,
    "uuid": "f083260e-2f90-4f56-959e-2cd2f422f5e7",
    "topic": "biology",
    "created_at": "2025-09-29T15:33:36",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 8,
    "question": "Which term refers to the random change in allele frequency in small populations? [Set 1]",
    "options": [
      "Natural selection",
      "Genetic drift",
      "Mutation",
      "Speciation"
    ],
    "answer": "Genetic drift"
  },
  {
    "id": 10049,
    "uuid": "e5edeab0-4e75-4234-aede-b111810c3a0d",
    "topic": "biology",
    "created_at": "2025-09-29T15:33:36",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 9,
    "question": "What is the preserved remains of ancient organisms called? [Set 1]",
    "options": [
      "Fossil",
      "Mineral",
      "Imprint",
      "Sediment"
    ],
    "answer": "Fossil"
  },
  {
    "id": 10050,
    "uuid": "15bfba51-9bcd-415c-a128-311d4eddf032",
    "topic": "biology",
    "created_at": "2025-09-29T15:33:36",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 10,
    "question": "Which islands did Darwin study finches that influenced his theory? [Set 1]",
    "options": [
      "Hawaiian",
      "Gal\u00e1pagos",
      "Philippines",
      "Caribbean"
    ],
    "answer": "Gal\u00e1pagos"
  },
  {
    "id": 10051,
    "uuid": "74371223-57b0-4bda-a89f-dfc17fd1f9b6",
    "topic": "biology",
    "created_at": "2025-09-29T15:33:36",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "question": "Which organelle is responsible for packaging and modifying proteins in eukaryotic cells? [Set 2]",
    "options": [
      "Ribosome",
      "Golgi apparatus",
      "Mitochondria",
      "Endoplasmic reticulum"
    ],
    "answer": "Golgi apparatus"
  },
  {
    "id": 10052,
    "uuid": "ca11c96f-0dce-43eb-bd3e-0d809de40d4f",
    "topic": "biology",
    "created_at": "2025-09-29T15:33:36",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 2,
    "question": "What is the semi-fluid substance inside the cell that surrounds organelles? [Set 2]",
    "options": [
      "Cytoplasm",
      "Nucleus",
      "Chloroplast",
      "Mitochondria"
    ],
    "answer": "Cytoplasm"
  },
  {
    "id": 10053,
    "uuid": "e5fe6a87-e86b-41d0-b1df-13706440e95b",
    "topic": "biology",
    "created_at": "2025-09-29T15:33:36",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 3,
    "question": "Which part of the cell controls most activities and stores genetic information? [Set 2]",
    "options": [
      "Cytoplasm",
      "Nucleus",
      "Golgi apparatus",
      "Lysosome"
    ],
    "answer": "Nucleus"
  },
  {
    "id": 10054,
    "uuid": "9638ec32-2e14-4b9f-a3b4-b493d2f442c7",
    "topic": "biology",
    "created_at": "2025-09-29T15:33:36",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 4,
    "question": "Which organelle is responsible for breaking down waste and cellular debris? [Set 2]",
    "options": [
      "Mitochondria",
      "Lysosome",
      "Ribosome",
      "Chloroplast"
    ],
    "answer": "Lysosome"
  },
  {
    "id": 10055,
    "uuid": "270fc522-f959-49c2-a134-a844407a216d",
    "topic": "biology",
    "created_at": "2025-09-29T15:33:36",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 5,
    "question": "What is the powerhouse of the cell? [Set 2]",
    "options": [
      "Nucleus",
      "Mitochondria",
      "Ribosome",
      "Chloroplast"
    ],
    "answer": "Mitochondria"
  },
  {
    "id": 10056,
    "uuid": "4b2dfc2d-6bd9-4940-88d9-5e79c346f512",
    "topic": "biology",
    "created_at": "2025-09-29T15:33:36",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 6,
    "question": "Who is considered the father of modern genetics? [Set 2]",
    "options": [
      "Charles Darwin",
      "Gregor Mendel",
      "Louis Pasteur",
      "Robert Hooke"
    ],
    "answer": "Gregor Mendel"
  },
  {
    "id": 10057,
    "uuid": "62ec10f7-2176-472c-9b00-e7e235b4812c",
    "topic": "biology",
    "created_at": "2025-09-29T15:33:36",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 7,
    "question": "Which base pairs with adenine in DNA? [Set 2]",
    "options": [
      "Guanine",
      "Cytosine",
      "Thymine",
      "Uracil"
    ],
    "answer": "Thymine"
  },
  {
    "id": 10058,
    "uuid": "3eded719-bccb-4a7c-8b8a-2600b1f1378c",
    "topic": "biology",
    "created_at": "2025-09-29T15:33:36",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 8,
    "question": "What is the shape of DNA described as? [Set 2]",
    "options": [
      "Triple helix",
      "Double helix",
      "Single strand",
      "Spiral ladder"
    ],
    "answer": "Double helix"
  },
  {
    "id": 10059,
    "uuid": "af2dbf8b-9087-4371-99cc-33e93a87e068",
    "topic": "biology",
    "created_at": "2025-09-29T15:33:36",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 9,
    "question": "Which type of RNA carries amino acids to ribosomes? [Set 2]",
    "options": [
      "mRNA",
      "tRNA",
      "rRNA",
      "snRNA"
    ],
    "answer": "tRNA"
  },
  {
    "id": 10060,
    "uuid": "1eab9c73-c119-42aa-9598-b8175efcc31d",
    "topic": "biology",
    "created_at": "2025-09-29T15:33:36",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 10,
    "question": "Which process creates gametes with half the number of chromosomes? [Set 2]",
    "options": [
      "Mitosis",
      "Meiosis",
      "Binary fission",
      "Budding"
    ],
    "answer": "Meiosis"
  },
  {
    "id": 10061,
    "uuid": "203dde11-3304-4d03-88c1-e528c06c15be",
    "topic": "biology",
    "created_at": "2025-09-29T15:33:36",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "question": "Which part of the human brain controls balance and coordination? [Set 2]",
    "options": [
      "Cerebrum",
      "Cerebellum",
      "Medulla",
      "Hypothalamus"
    ],
    "answer": "Cerebellum"
  },
  {
    "id": 10062,
    "uuid": "e2b00c9d-6beb-4706-b235-8d1b42bb96a0",
    "topic": "biology",
    "created_at": "2025-09-29T15:33:36",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 2,
    "question": "Which blood vessels carry blood away from the heart? [Set 2]",
    "options": [
      "Arteries",
      "Veins",
      "Capillaries",
      "Venules"
    ],
    "answer": "Arteries"
  },
  {
    "id": 10063,
    "uuid": "2ec16f39-fe92-4444-94a9-abe9afec6941",
    "topic": "biology",
    "created_at": "2025-09-29T15:33:36",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 3,
    "question": "Which protein in red blood cells carries oxygen? [Set 2]",
    "options": [
      "Collagen",
      "Keratin",
      "Hemoglobin",
      "Albumin"
    ],
    "answer": "Hemoglobin"
  },
  {
    "id": 10064,
    "uuid": "f6282e54-f5a9-4ce5-86c3-21a35cae9159",
    "topic": "biology",
    "created_at": "2025-09-29T15:33:36",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 4,
    "question": "Which organ is primarily responsible for detoxification? [Set 2]",
    "options": [
      "Kidney",
      "Liver",
      "Lung",
      "Pancreas"
    ],
    "answer": "Liver"
  },
  {
    "id": 10065,
    "uuid": "2578a8ea-c523-4a43-87fb-39ada9e600a8",
    "topic": "biology",
    "created_at": "2025-09-29T15:33:36",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 5,
    "question": "Which gland regulates metabolism through hormone secretion? [Set 2]",
    "options": [
      "Adrenal",
      "Thyroid",
      "Pituitary",
      "Pancreas"
    ],
    "answer": "Thyroid"
  },
  {
    "id": 10066,
    "uuid": "94557040-a85d-4ce4-b8f6-dbe05ac0880f",
    "topic": "biology",
    "created_at": "2025-09-29T15:33:36",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 6,
    "question": "What term describes organisms that produce their own food? [Set 2]",
    "options": [
      "Consumers",
      "Decomposers",
      "Producers",
      "Parasites"
    ],
    "answer": "Producers"
  },
  {
    "id": 10067,
    "uuid": "4ee6d8a3-21f6-4a12-98cf-af166c977bb2",
    "topic": "biology",
    "created_at": "2025-09-29T15:33:36",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 7,
    "question": "Which biome is characterized by permafrost? [Set 2]",
    "options": [
      "Desert",
      "Savanna",
      "Tundra",
      "Rainforest"
    ],
    "answer": "Tundra"
  },
  {
    "id": 10068,
    "uuid": "5fbb2487-ddf1-4784-86b6-7af1a2508291",
    "topic": "biology",
    "created_at": "2025-09-29T15:33:36",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 8,
    "question": "What is the main source of energy for almost all ecosystems? [Set 2]",
    "options": [
      "Wind",
      "Water",
      "Sunlight",
      "Soil"
    ],
    "answer": "Sunlight"
  },
  {
    "id": 10069,
    "uuid": "06f90d2e-ffde-4764-bccc-b0c787417f30",
    "topic": "biology",
    "created_at": "2025-09-29T15:33:36",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 9,
    "question": "What is the symbiotic relationship where both species benefit? [Set 2]",
    "options": [
      "Parasitism",
      "Commensalism",
      "Mutualism",
      "Predation"
    ],
    "answer": "Mutualism"
  },
  {
    "id": 10070,
    "uuid": "b8a2fd5c-1523-42a2-8997-d17717092743",
    "topic": "biology",
    "created_at": "2025-09-29T15:33:36",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 10,
    "question": "Which gas do plants absorb during photosynthesis? [Set 2]",
    "options": [
      "Oxygen",
      "Carbon dioxide",
      "Nitrogen",
      "Hydrogen"
    ],
    "answer": "Carbon dioxide"
  },
  {
    "id": 10071,
    "uuid": "b3ce560b-3df4-42d3-bc75-caf1206a9eeb",
    "topic": "biology",
    "created_at": "2025-09-29T15:33:36",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "question": "Who proposed the theory of natural selection? [Set 2]",
    "options": [
      "Gregor Mendel",
      "Louis Pasteur",
      "Charles Darwin",
      "Robert Hooke"
    ],
    "answer": "Charles Darwin"
  },
  {
    "id": 10072,
    "uuid": "0c102989-dc6c-4c82-8755-c7b77fa617d4",
    "topic": "biology",
    "created_at": "2025-09-29T15:33:36",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 2,
    "question": "What term describes structures that are similar due to shared ancestry? [Set 2]",
    "options": [
      "Analogous",
      "Homologous",
      "Vestigial",
      "Derived"
    ],
    "answer": "Homologous"
  },
  {
    "id": 10073,
    "uuid": "c1720644-7e0c-415d-9c97-18aea0051747",
    "topic": "biology",
    "created_at": "2025-09-29T15:33:36",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 3,
    "question": "Which term refers to the random change in allele frequency in small populations? [Set 2]",
    "options": [
      "Natural selection",
      "Genetic drift",
      "Mutation",
      "Speciation"
    ],
    "answer": "Genetic drift"
  },
  {
    "id": 10074,
    "uuid": "06eba812-bb0d-42bc-8d72-51ad46684458",
    "topic": "biology",
    "created_at": "2025-09-29T15:33:36",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 4,
    "question": "What is the preserved remains of ancient organisms called? [Set 2]",
    "options": [
      "Fossil",
      "Mineral",
      "Imprint",
      "Sediment"
    ],
    "answer": "Fossil"
  },
  {
    "id": 10075,
    "uuid": "4fbbf55e-52cc-4d83-bc97-29fa3d8421a6",
    "topic": "biology",
    "created_at": "2025-09-29T15:33:36",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 5,
    "question": "Which islands did Darwin study finches that influenced his theory? [Set 2]",
    "options": [
      "Hawaiian",
      "Gal\u00e1pagos",
      "Philippines",
      "Caribbean"
    ],
    "answer": "Gal\u00e1pagos"
  },
  {
    "id": 10076,
    "uuid": "a7b70435-2220-4326-8446-cace09e7e453",
    "topic": "biology",
    "created_at": "2025-09-29T15:33:36",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 6,
    "question": "Which organelle is responsible for packaging and modifying proteins in eukaryotic cells? [Set 3]",
    "options": [
      "Ribosome",
      "Golgi apparatus",
      "Mitochondria",
      "Endoplasmic reticulum"
    ],
    "answer": "Golgi apparatus"
  },
  {
    "id": 10077,
    "uuid": "9ab4decf-6a83-4f8b-a7b3-c6e316c546ec",
    "topic": "biology",
    "created_at": "2025-09-29T15:33:36",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 7,
    "question": "What is the semi-fluid substance inside the cell that surrounds organelles? [Set 3]",
    "options": [
      "Cytoplasm",
      "Nucleus",
      "Chloroplast",
      "Mitochondria"
    ],
    "answer": "Cytoplasm"
  },
  {
    "id": 10078,
    "uuid": "fb71f2da-438a-40cd-b22b-7c8d42362db6",
    "topic": "biology",
    "created_at": "2025-09-29T15:33:36",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 8,
    "question": "Which part of the cell controls most activities and stores genetic information? [Set 3]",
    "options": [
      "Cytoplasm",
      "Nucleus",
      "Golgi apparatus",
      "Lysosome"
    ],
    "answer": "Nucleus"
  },
  {
    "id": 10079,
    "uuid": "b6653ae4-1fa8-4493-ae5e-ba277f2ae938",
    "topic": "biology",
    "created_at": "2025-09-29T15:33:36",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 9,
    "question": "Which organelle is responsible for breaking down waste and cellular debris? [Set 3]",
    "options": [
      "Mitochondria",
      "Lysosome",
      "Ribosome",
      "Chloroplast"
    ],
    "answer": "Lysosome"
  },
  {
    "id": 10080,
    "uuid": "6ed9b918-031c-477f-bc06-fd3bd19b3612",
    "topic": "biology",
    "created_at": "2025-09-29T15:33:36",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 10,
    "question": "What is the powerhouse of the cell? [Set 3]",
    "options": [
      "Nucleus",
      "Mitochondria",
      "Ribosome",
      "Chloroplast"
    ],
    "answer": "Mitochondria"
  },
  {
    "id": 10081,
    "uuid": "1ce789cd-d3b0-4a1a-940a-dc89b05cbbdb",
    "topic": "biology",
    "created_at": "2025-09-29T15:33:36",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "question": "Who is considered the father of modern genetics? [Set 3]",
    "options": [
      "Charles Darwin",
      "Gregor Mendel",
      "Louis Pasteur",
      "Robert Hooke"
    ],
    "answer": "Gregor Mendel"
  },
  {
    "id": 10082,
    "uuid": "694787e2-b5e0-46b7-b391-5cd0336ca220",
    "topic": "biology",
    "created_at": "2025-09-29T15:33:36",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 2,
    "question": "Which base pairs with adenine in DNA? [Set 3]",
    "options": [
      "Guanine",
      "Cytosine",
      "Thymine",
      "Uracil"
    ],
    "answer": "Thymine"
  },
  {
    "id": 10083,
    "uuid": "d8668a9a-f036-4729-85f8-87c9ba0e0e1b",
    "topic": "biology",
    "created_at": "2025-09-29T15:33:36",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 3,
    "question": "What is the shape of DNA described as? [Set 3]",
    "options": [
      "Triple helix",
      "Double helix",
      "Single strand",
      "Spiral ladder"
    ],
    "answer": "Double helix"
  },
  {
    "id": 10084,
    "uuid": "0a90ca91-dd1f-48df-86c2-9a15a855a739",
    "topic": "biology",
    "created_at": "2025-09-29T15:33:36",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 4,
    "question": "Which type of RNA carries amino acids to ribosomes? [Set 3]",
    "options": [
      "mRNA",
      "tRNA",
      "rRNA",
      "snRNA"
    ],
    "answer": "tRNA"
  },
  {
    "id": 10085,
    "uuid": "219aa735-5f6d-4d53-9cd9-8d9dd5d7cf7c",
    "topic": "biology",
    "created_at": "2025-09-29T15:33:36",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 5,
    "question": "Which process creates gametes with half the number of chromosomes? [Set 3]",
    "options": [
      "Mitosis",
      "Meiosis",
      "Binary fission",
      "Budding"
    ],
    "answer": "Meiosis"
  },
  {
    "id": 10086,
    "uuid": "2b1847eb-a21a-4a94-b23f-d6ec4db3ad3d",
    "topic": "biology",
    "created_at": "2025-09-29T15:33:36",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 6,
    "question": "Which part of the human brain controls balance and coordination? [Set 3]",
    "options": [
      "Cerebrum",
      "Cerebellum",
      "Medulla",
      "Hypothalamus"
    ],
    "answer": "Cerebellum"
  },
  {
    "id": 10087,
    "uuid": "7837a43b-b67e-4233-8d27-20d375465069",
    "topic": "biology",
    "created_at": "2025-09-29T15:33:36",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 7,
    "question": "Which blood vessels carry blood away from the heart? [Set 3]",
    "options": [
      "Arteries",
      "Veins",
      "Capillaries",
      "Venules"
    ],
    "answer": "Arteries"
  },
  {
    "id": 10088,
    "uuid": "81c76c04-9e82-4e8a-83d3-e76740e73cdb",
    "topic": "biology",
    "created_at": "2025-09-29T15:33:36",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 8,
    "question": "Which protein in red blood cells carries oxygen? [Set 3]",
    "options": [
      "Collagen",
      "Keratin",
      "Hemoglobin",
      "Albumin"
    ],
    "answer": "Hemoglobin"
  },
  {
    "id": 10089,
    "uuid": "4caae6c7-44c7-401d-9614-42bdad569771",
    "topic": "biology",
    "created_at": "2025-09-29T15:33:36",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 9,
    "question": "Which organ is primarily responsible for detoxification? [Set 3]",
    "options": [
      "Kidney",
      "Liver",
      "Lung",
      "Pancreas"
    ],
    "answer": "Liver"
  },
  {
    "id": 10090,
    "uuid": "655afaef-ddc2-41be-b864-7501cc341b7c",
    "topic": "biology",
    "created_at": "2025-09-29T15:33:36",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 10,
    "question": "Which gland regulates metabolism through hormone secretion? [Set 3]",
    "options": [
      "Adrenal",
      "Thyroid",
      "Pituitary",
      "Pancreas"
    ],
    "answer": "Thyroid"
  },
  {
    "id": 10091,
    "uuid": "3f9d3d4d-8d57-4f21-b3c8-e96f9b3a2360",
    "topic": "biology",
    "created_at": "2025-09-29T15:33:36",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "question": "What term describes organisms that produce their own food? [Set 3]",
    "options": [
      "Consumers",
      "Decomposers",
      "Producers",
      "Parasites"
    ],
    "answer": "Producers"
  },
  {
    "id": 10092,
    "uuid": "d817e476-1e00-4cdc-9281-1293ff73ac78",
    "topic": "biology",
    "created_at": "2025-09-29T15:33:36",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 2,
    "question": "Which biome is characterized by permafrost? [Set 3]",
    "options": [
      "Desert",
      "Savanna",
      "Tundra",
      "Rainforest"
    ],
    "answer": "Tundra"
  },
  {
    "id": 10093,
    "uuid": "c4272467-49b2-4e21-aa6d-2de301b3c015",
    "topic": "biology",
    "created_at": "2025-09-29T15:33:36",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 3,
    "question": "What is the main source of energy for almost all ecosystems? [Set 3]",
    "options": [
      "Wind",
      "Water",
      "Sunlight",
      "Soil"
    ],
    "answer": "Sunlight"
  },
  {
    "id": 10094,
    "uuid": "6ed92a1b-8369-4c56-b2d4-f0b0eec9c5b4",
    "topic": "biology",
    "created_at": "2025-09-29T15:33:36",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 4,
    "question": "What is the symbiotic relationship where both species benefit? [Set 3]",
    "options": [
      "Parasitism",
      "Commensalism",
      "Mutualism",
      "Predation"
    ],
    "answer": "Mutualism"
  },
  {
    "id": 10095,
    "uuid": "159f4dfb-76b4-4d97-8219-ed8dce9adab7",
    "topic": "biology",
    "created_at": "2025-09-29T15:33:36",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 5,
    "question": "Which gas do plants absorb during photosynthesis? [Set 3]",
    "options": [
      "Oxygen",
      "Carbon dioxide",
      "Nitrogen",
      "Hydrogen"
    ],
    "answer": "Carbon dioxide"
  },
  {
    "id": 10096,
    "uuid": "824a82a6-994c-4deb-af08-131f1d56b8cd",
    "topic": "biology",
    "created_at": "2025-09-29T15:33:36",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 6,
    "question": "Who proposed the theory of natural selection? [Set 3]",
    "options": [
      "Gregor Mendel",
      "Louis Pasteur",
      "Charles Darwin",
      "Robert Hooke"
    ],
    "answer": "Charles Darwin"
  },
  {
    "id": 10097,
    "uuid": "ad994e2d-e015-41ff-a6f7-068f967aad4e",
    "topic": "biology",
    "created_at": "2025-09-29T15:33:36",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 7,
    "question": "What term describes structures that are similar due to shared ancestry? [Set 3]",
    "options": [
      "Analogous",
      "Homologous",
      "Vestigial",
      "Derived"
    ],
    "answer": "Homologous"
  },
  {
    "id": 10098,
    "uuid": "84828e6e-3204-4d0b-9c67-cd934aa8052c",
    "topic": "biology",
    "created_at": "2025-09-29T15:33:36",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 8,
    "question": "Which term refers to the random change in allele frequency in small populations? [Set 3]",
    "options": [
      "Natural selection",
      "Genetic drift",
      "Mutation",
      "Speciation"
    ],
    "answer": "Genetic drift"
  },
  {
    "id": 10099,
    "uuid": "8db5bda3-7a48-40db-979c-7d2d44155210",
    "topic": "biology",
    "created_at": "2025-09-29T15:33:36",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 9,
    "question": "What is the preserved remains of ancient organisms called? [Set 3]",
    "options": [
      "Fossil",
      "Mineral",
      "Imprint",
      "Sediment"
    ],
    "answer": "Fossil"
  },
  {
    "id": 10100,
    "uuid": "014ec381-2c21-4098-b47a-9aa06774833d",
    "topic": "biology",
    "created_at": "2025-09-29T15:33:36",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 10,
    "question": "Which islands did Darwin study finches that influenced his theory? [Set 3]",
    "options": [
      "Hawaiian",
      "Gal\u00e1pagos",
      "Philippines",
      "Caribbean"
    ],
    "answer": "Gal\u00e1pagos"
  },
  {
    "id": 10101,
    "uuid": "b6af1e15-609b-4ff8-8f6a-872a2b7a1ab7",
    "topic": "biology",
    "created_at": "2025-09-29T15:33:36",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "question": "Which organelle is responsible for packaging and modifying proteins in eukaryotic cells? [Set 4]",
    "options": [
      "Ribosome",
      "Golgi apparatus",
      "Mitochondria",
      "Endoplasmic reticulum"
    ],
    "answer": "Golgi apparatus"
  },
  {
    "id": 10102,
    "uuid": "d27ce65a-3593-40b9-8324-57e6061a5b8e",
    "topic": "biology",
    "created_at": "2025-09-29T15:33:36",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 2,
    "question": "What is the semi-fluid substance inside the cell that surrounds organelles? [Set 4]",
    "options": [
      "Cytoplasm",
      "Nucleus",
      "Chloroplast",
      "Mitochondria"
    ],
    "answer": "Cytoplasm"
  },
  {
    "id": 10103,
    "uuid": "4a2a106e-c9b6-4059-a6d1-9e44e8d0e3db",
    "topic": "biology",
    "created_at": "2025-09-29T15:33:36",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 3,
    "question": "Which part of the cell controls most activities and stores genetic information? [Set 4]",
    "options": [
      "Cytoplasm",
      "Nucleus",
      "Golgi apparatus",
      "Lysosome"
    ],
    "answer": "Nucleus"
  },
  {
    "id": 10104,
    "uuid": "c52951ae-5549-41c4-92ee-3a0ebfa129e8",
    "topic": "biology",
    "created_at": "2025-09-29T15:33:36",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 4,
    "question": "Which organelle is responsible for breaking down waste and cellular debris? [Set 4]",
    "options": [
      "Mitochondria",
      "Lysosome",
      "Ribosome",
      "Chloroplast"
    ],
    "answer": "Lysosome"
  },
  {
    "id": 10105,
    "uuid": "7ec0d5a0-a6e9-427c-b8f7-49f1e5320845",
    "topic": "biology",
    "created_at": "2025-09-29T15:33:36",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 5,
    "question": "What is the powerhouse of the cell? [Set 4]",
    "options": [
      "Nucleus",
      "Mitochondria",
      "Ribosome",
      "Chloroplast"
    ],
    "answer": "Mitochondria"
  },
  {
    "id": 10106,
    "uuid": "b5db63e5-5ac2-45da-96a5-93748200d577",
    "topic": "biology",
    "created_at": "2025-09-29T15:33:36",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 6,
    "question": "Who is considered the father of modern genetics? [Set 4]",
    "options": [
      "Charles Darwin",
      "Gregor Mendel",
      "Louis Pasteur",
      "Robert Hooke"
    ],
    "answer": "Gregor Mendel"
  },
  {
    "id": 10107,
    "uuid": "8848d4f6-5778-4c8d-a7c5-38ac96fa6220",
    "topic": "biology",
    "created_at": "2025-09-29T15:33:36",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 7,
    "question": "Which base pairs with adenine in DNA? [Set 4]",
    "options": [
      "Guanine",
      "Cytosine",
      "Thymine",
      "Uracil"
    ],
    "answer": "Thymine"
  },
  {
    "id": 10108,
    "uuid": "a48869cc-7bc3-4849-a76d-1b3cabdbc1d1",
    "topic": "biology",
    "created_at": "2025-09-29T15:33:36",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 8,
    "question": "What is the shape of DNA described as? [Set 4]",
    "options": [
      "Triple helix",
      "Double helix",
      "Single strand",
      "Spiral ladder"
    ],
    "answer": "Double helix"
  },
  {
    "id": 10109,
    "uuid": "b98ee4dc-259d-47f3-b451-c0ed5a4e1362",
    "topic": "biology",
    "created_at": "2025-09-29T15:33:36",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 9,
    "question": "Which type of RNA carries amino acids to ribosomes? [Set 4]",
    "options": [
      "mRNA",
      "tRNA",
      "rRNA",
      "snRNA"
    ],
    "answer": "tRNA"
  },
  {
    "id": 10110,
    "uuid": "ce32baec-df40-44e4-a385-c2c3ecb70000",
    "topic": "biology",
    "created_at": "2025-09-29T15:33:36",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 10,
    "question": "Which process creates gametes with half the number of chromosomes? [Set 4]",
    "options": [
      "Mitosis",
      "Meiosis",
      "Binary fission",
      "Budding"
    ],
    "answer": "Meiosis"
  },
  {
    "id": 10111,
    "uuid": "acb92847-94aa-460f-944f-dbe9d9a2b3a4",
    "topic": "biology",
    "created_at": "2025-09-29T15:33:36",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "question": "Which part of the human brain controls balance and coordination? [Set 4]",
    "options": [
      "Cerebrum",
      "Cerebellum",
      "Medulla",
      "Hypothalamus"
    ],
    "answer": "Cerebellum"
  },
  {
    "id": 10112,
    "uuid": "4dac22cf-701a-4008-bc7e-11e062ae8d67",
    "topic": "biology",
    "created_at": "2025-09-29T15:33:36",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 2,
    "question": "Which blood vessels carry blood away from the heart? [Set 4]",
    "options": [
      "Arteries",
      "Veins",
      "Capillaries",
      "Venules"
    ],
    "answer": "Arteries"
  },
  {
    "id": 10113,
    "uuid": "3e6ad8f4-0be1-4e88-b06f-951ba14b9431",
    "topic": "biology",
    "created_at": "2025-09-29T15:33:36",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 3,
    "question": "Which protein in red blood cells carries oxygen? [Set 4]",
    "options": [
      "Collagen",
      "Keratin",
      "Hemoglobin",
      "Albumin"
    ],
    "answer": "Hemoglobin"
  },
  {
    "id": 10114,
    "uuid": "5dba28d0-a6d6-4728-b7f3-f0f1facd3643",
    "topic": "biology",
    "created_at": "2025-09-29T15:33:36",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 4,
    "question": "Which organ is primarily responsible for detoxification? [Set 4]",
    "options": [
      "Kidney",
      "Liver",
      "Lung",
      "Pancreas"
    ],
    "answer": "Liver"
  },
  {
    "id": 10115,
    "uuid": "006911e0-8bde-474e-967c-bacc44f6b18b",
    "topic": "biology",
    "created_at": "2025-09-29T15:33:36",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 5,
    "question": "Which gland regulates metabolism through hormone secretion? [Set 4]",
    "options": [
      "Adrenal",
      "Thyroid",
      "Pituitary",
      "Pancreas"
    ],
    "answer": "Thyroid"
  },
  {
    "id": 10116,
    "uuid": "265427ec-ec8c-4d10-9502-b66c5b1d1420",
    "topic": "biology",
    "created_at": "2025-09-29T15:33:36",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 6,
    "question": "What term describes organisms that produce their own food? [Set 4]",
    "options": [
      "Consumers",
      "Decomposers",
      "Producers",
      "Parasites"
    ],
    "answer": "Producers"
  },
  {
    "id": 10117,
    "uuid": "ad1c830c-78df-4f84-86f7-8454aeac1d21",
    "topic": "biology",
    "created_at": "2025-09-29T15:33:36",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 7,
    "question": "Which biome is characterized by permafrost? [Set 4]",
    "options": [
      "Desert",
      "Savanna",
      "Tundra",
      "Rainforest"
    ],
    "answer": "Tundra"
  },
  {
    "id": 10118,
    "uuid": "3db1d93f-4104-4b0b-879a-854ab0294889",
    "topic": "biology",
    "created_at": "2025-09-29T15:33:36",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 8,
    "question": "What is the main source of energy for almost all ecosystems? [Set 4]",
    "options": [
      "Wind",
      "Water",
      "Sunlight",
      "Soil"
    ],
    "answer": "Sunlight"
  },
  {
    "id": 10119,
    "uuid": "b87d8385-1da9-4e77-aaef-b6f16257d2ab",
    "topic": "biology",
    "created_at": "2025-09-29T15:33:36",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 9,
    "question": "What is the symbiotic relationship where both species benefit? [Set 4]",
    "options": [
      "Parasitism",
      "Commensalism",
      "Mutualism",
      "Predation"
    ],
    "answer": "Mutualism"
  },
  {
    "id": 10120,
    "uuid": "248cfa69-685f-42b9-b82e-7a712697c18f",
    "topic": "biology",
    "created_at": "2025-09-29T15:33:36",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 10,
    "question": "Which gas do plants absorb during photosynthesis? [Set 4]",
    "options": [
      "Oxygen",
      "Carbon dioxide",
      "Nitrogen",
      "Hydrogen"
    ],
    "answer": "Carbon dioxide"
  },
  {
    "id": 10121,
    "uuid": "a0423ae5-4081-47ac-8163-2df07b97e3e9",
    "topic": "biology",
    "created_at": "2025-09-29T15:33:36",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "question": "Who proposed the theory of natural selection? [Set 4]",
    "options": [
      "Gregor Mendel",
      "Louis Pasteur",
      "Charles Darwin",
      "Robert Hooke"
    ],
    "answer": "Charles Darwin"
  },
  {
    "id": 10122,
    "uuid": "6a92b2c9-a4ed-407d-8aeb-e3367dcb994c",
    "topic": "biology",
    "created_at": "2025-09-29T15:33:36",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 2,
    "question": "What term describes structures that are similar due to shared ancestry? [Set 4]",
    "options": [
      "Analogous",
      "Homologous",
      "Vestigial",
      "Derived"
    ],
    "answer": "Homologous"
  },
  {
    "id": 10123,
    "uuid": "db3eaa99-0c00-4945-aa90-7b3deb805d9e",
    "topic": "biology",
    "created_at": "2025-09-29T15:33:36",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 3,
    "question": "Which term refers to the random change in allele frequency in small populations? [Set 4]",
    "options": [
      "Natural selection",
      "Genetic drift",
      "Mutation",
      "Speciation"
    ],
    "answer": "Genetic drift"
  },
  {
    "id": 10124,
    "uuid": "55ffb9e9-43bd-4367-8478-a8c82ff85af3",
    "topic": "biology",
    "created_at": "2025-09-29T15:33:36",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 4,
    "question": "What is the preserved remains of ancient organisms called? [Set 4]",
    "options": [
      "Fossil",
      "Mineral",
      "Imprint",
      "Sediment"
    ],
    "answer": "Fossil"
  },
  {
    "id": 10125,
    "uuid": "06ab68d4-06bd-4827-919b-32ab4e35d913",
    "topic": "biology",
    "created_at": "2025-09-29T15:33:36",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 5,
    "question": "Which islands did Darwin study finches that influenced his theory? [Set 4]",
    "options": [
      "Hawaiian",
      "Gal\u00e1pagos",
      "Philippines",
      "Caribbean"
    ],
    "answer": "Gal\u00e1pagos"
  },
  {
    "id": 10126,
    "uuid": "dc8c1776-127a-4398-81ad-f7ecf0cae745",
    "topic": "biology",
    "created_at": "2025-09-29T15:33:36",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 6,
    "question": "Which organelle is responsible for packaging and modifying proteins in eukaryotic cells? [Set 5]",
    "options": [
      "Ribosome",
      "Golgi apparatus",
      "Mitochondria",
      "Endoplasmic reticulum"
    ],
    "answer": "Golgi apparatus"
  },
  {
    "id": 10127,
    "uuid": "3c99b059-432c-4e5e-914f-39eefbf69cc1",
    "topic": "biology",
    "created_at": "2025-09-29T15:33:36",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 7,
    "question": "What is the semi-fluid substance inside the cell that surrounds organelles? [Set 5]",
    "options": [
      "Cytoplasm",
      "Nucleus",
      "Chloroplast",
      "Mitochondria"
    ],
    "answer": "Cytoplasm"
  },
  {
    "id": 10128,
    "uuid": "4840fe51-c1f4-4861-b2c5-024ee4329760",
    "topic": "biology",
    "created_at": "2025-09-29T15:33:36",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 8,
    "question": "Which part of the cell controls most activities and stores genetic information? [Set 5]",
    "options": [
      "Cytoplasm",
      "Nucleus",
      "Golgi apparatus",
      "Lysosome"
    ],
    "answer": "Nucleus"
  },
  {
    "id": 10129,
    "uuid": "9400a7d7-5784-4e89-a2c0-61da8e89428d",
    "topic": "biology",
    "created_at": "2025-09-29T15:33:36",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 9,
    "question": "Which organelle is responsible for breaking down waste and cellular debris? [Set 5]",
    "options": [
      "Mitochondria",
      "Lysosome",
      "Ribosome",
      "Chloroplast"
    ],
    "answer": "Lysosome"
  },
  {
    "id": 10130,
    "uuid": "2c08ee2a-a13a-4f5e-9799-ac5e51644d74",
    "topic": "biology",
    "created_at": "2025-09-29T15:33:36",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 10,
    "question": "What is the powerhouse of the cell? [Set 5]",
    "options": [
      "Nucleus",
      "Mitochondria",
      "Ribosome",
      "Chloroplast"
    ],
    "answer": "Mitochondria"
  },
  {
    "id": 10131,
    "uuid": "41ccc6ef-7b63-4f7d-ad47-e26302947126",
    "topic": "biology",
    "created_at": "2025-09-29T15:33:36",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "question": "Who is considered the father of modern genetics? [Set 5]",
    "options": [
      "Charles Darwin",
      "Gregor Mendel",
      "Louis Pasteur",
      "Robert Hooke"
    ],
    "answer": "Gregor Mendel"
  },
  {
    "id": 10132,
    "uuid": "5b84882f-0211-46b7-9c97-8cd0b96d2683",
    "topic": "biology",
    "created_at": "2025-09-29T15:33:36",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 2,
    "question": "Which base pairs with adenine in DNA? [Set 5]",
    "options": [
      "Guanine",
      "Cytosine",
      "Thymine",
      "Uracil"
    ],
    "answer": "Thymine"
  },
  {
    "id": 10133,
    "uuid": "e5a051fa-d4d7-45b5-94f0-afe61a8fc5ec",
    "topic": "biology",
    "created_at": "2025-09-29T15:33:36",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 3,
    "question": "What is the shape of DNA described as? [Set 5]",
    "options": [
      "Triple helix",
      "Double helix",
      "Single strand",
      "Spiral ladder"
    ],
    "answer": "Double helix"
  },
  {
    "id": 10134,
    "uuid": "dcbbeaa7-2e67-4fa6-b269-74c88d67f692",
    "topic": "biology",
    "created_at": "2025-09-29T15:33:36",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 4,
    "question": "Which type of RNA carries amino acids to ribosomes? [Set 5]",
    "options": [
      "mRNA",
      "tRNA",
      "rRNA",
      "snRNA"
    ],
    "answer": "tRNA"
  },
  {
    "id": 10135,
    "uuid": "e0df7a6d-f9a9-4af5-8c70-80b006ce2743",
    "topic": "biology",
    "created_at": "2025-09-29T15:33:36",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 5,
    "question": "Which process creates gametes with half the number of chromosomes? [Set 5]",
    "options": [
      "Mitosis",
      "Meiosis",
      "Binary fission",
      "Budding"
    ],
    "answer": "Meiosis"
  },
  {
    "id": 10136,
    "uuid": "b43b8d0f-5aac-4266-9353-eaf5f06b9a2a",
    "topic": "biology",
    "created_at": "2025-09-29T15:33:36",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 6,
    "question": "Which part of the human brain controls balance and coordination? [Set 5]",
    "options": [
      "Cerebrum",
      "Cerebellum",
      "Medulla",
      "Hypothalamus"
    ],
    "answer": "Cerebellum"
  },
  {
    "id": 10137,
    "uuid": "57d437cc-e845-4f1b-99ae-21c4df7027d2",
    "topic": "biology",
    "created_at": "2025-09-29T15:33:36",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 7,
    "question": "Which blood vessels carry blood away from the heart? [Set 5]",
    "options": [
      "Arteries",
      "Veins",
      "Capillaries",
      "Venules"
    ],
    "answer": "Arteries"
  },
  {
    "id": 10138,
    "uuid": "b9dd8eb7-596e-4073-836c-bf0640fda8e0",
    "topic": "biology",
    "created_at": "2025-09-29T15:33:36",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 8,
    "question": "Which protein in red blood cells carries oxygen? [Set 5]",
    "options": [
      "Collagen",
      "Keratin",
      "Hemoglobin",
      "Albumin"
    ],
    "answer": "Hemoglobin"
  },
  {
    "id": 10139,
    "uuid": "84d8dccc-eda7-451e-9e2d-8b1fd9b69f92",
    "topic": "biology",
    "created_at": "2025-09-29T15:33:36",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 9,
    "question": "Which organ is primarily responsible for detoxification? [Set 5]",
    "options": [
      "Kidney",
      "Liver",
      "Lung",
      "Pancreas"
    ],
    "answer": "Liver"
  },
  {
    "id": 10140,
    "uuid": "765cc912-9ceb-42ba-a7be-8e955677db5f",
    "topic": "biology",
    "created_at": "2025-09-29T15:33:36",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 10,
    "question": "Which gland regulates metabolism through hormone secretion? [Set 5]",
    "options": [
      "Adrenal",
      "Thyroid",
      "Pituitary",
      "Pancreas"
    ],
    "answer": "Thyroid"
  },
  {
    "id": 10141,
    "uuid": "fa4dcdee-bbce-4a6c-a2e7-5f81666f7207",
    "topic": "biology",
    "created_at": "2025-09-29T15:33:36",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "question": "What term describes organisms that produce their own food? [Set 5]",
    "options": [
      "Consumers",
      "Decomposers",
      "Producers",
      "Parasites"
    ],
    "answer": "Producers"
  },
  {
    "id": 10142,
    "uuid": "17144ac9-0693-499f-b6c9-3d28f48360e2",
    "topic": "biology",
    "created_at": "2025-09-29T15:33:36",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 2,
    "question": "Which biome is characterized by permafrost? [Set 5]",
    "options": [
      "Desert",
      "Savanna",
      "Tundra",
      "Rainforest"
    ],
    "answer": "Tundra"
  },
  {
    "id": 10143,
    "uuid": "54468629-ede8-4fd7-8b72-2b8502bcb95c",
    "topic": "biology",
    "created_at": "2025-09-29T15:33:36",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 3,
    "question": "What is the main source of energy for almost all ecosystems? [Set 5]",
    "options": [
      "Wind",
      "Water",
      "Sunlight",
      "Soil"
    ],
    "answer": "Sunlight"
  },
  {
    "id": 10144,
    "uuid": "864417eb-5e58-44ee-916e-6192513212af",
    "topic": "biology",
    "created_at": "2025-09-29T15:33:36",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 4,
    "question": "What is the symbiotic relationship where both species benefit? [Set 5]",
    "options": [
      "Parasitism",
      "Commensalism",
      "Mutualism",
      "Predation"
    ],
    "answer": "Mutualism"
  },
  {
    "id": 10145,
    "uuid": "38241944-a94c-453e-8c3e-46671d894008",
    "topic": "biology",
    "created_at": "2025-09-29T15:33:36",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 5,
    "question": "Which gas do plants absorb during photosynthesis? [Set 5]",
    "options": [
      "Oxygen",
      "Carbon dioxide",
      "Nitrogen",
      "Hydrogen"
    ],
    "answer": "Carbon dioxide"
  },
  {
    "id": 10146,
    "uuid": "3c235d74-b1e3-4f48-9ef7-7259cadb8ad0",
    "topic": "biology",
    "created_at": "2025-09-29T15:33:36",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 6,
    "question": "Who proposed the theory of natural selection? [Set 5]",
    "options": [
      "Gregor Mendel",
      "Louis Pasteur",
      "Charles Darwin",
      "Robert Hooke"
    ],
    "answer": "Charles Darwin"
  },
  {
    "id": 10147,
    "uuid": "ba855ad0-df0b-4ca3-87e0-4481a9b03471",
    "topic": "biology",
    "created_at": "2025-09-29T15:33:36",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 7,
    "question": "What term describes structures that are similar due to shared ancestry? [Set 5]",
    "options": [
      "Analogous",
      "Homologous",
      "Vestigial",
      "Derived"
    ],
    "answer": "Homologous"
  },
  {
    "id": 10148,
    "uuid": "df0d22c5-4266-4b16-bd3b-76b79f1342b3",
    "topic": "biology",
    "created_at": "2025-09-29T15:33:36",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 8,
    "question": "Which term refers to the random change in allele frequency in small populations? [Set 5]",
    "options": [
      "Natural selection",
      "Genetic drift",
      "Mutation",
      "Speciation"
    ],
    "answer": "Genetic drift"
  },
  {
    "id": 10149,
    "uuid": "380fa34d-9142-461e-8aad-1df05ca584bf",
    "topic": "biology",
    "created_at": "2025-09-29T15:33:36",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 9,
    "question": "What is the preserved remains of ancient organisms called? [Set 5]",
    "options": [
      "Fossil",
      "Mineral",
      "Imprint",
      "Sediment"
    ],
    "answer": "Fossil"
  },
  {
    "id": 10150,
    "uuid": "3ced7bb4-a4d4-46b7-ac09-cb7916fb872c",
    "topic": "biology",
    "created_at": "2025-09-29T15:33:36",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 10,
    "question": "Which islands did Darwin study finches that influenced his theory? [Set 5]",
    "options": [
      "Hawaiian",
      "Gal\u00e1pagos",
      "Philippines",
      "Caribbean"
    ],
    "answer": "Gal\u00e1pagos"
  },
  {
    "id": 10151,
    "uuid": "e9de7b49-3c21-494b-a3a6-304a23d7dc0f",
    "topic": "biology",
    "created_at": "2025-09-29T15:33:36",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "question": "Which organelle is responsible for packaging and modifying proteins in eukaryotic cells? [Set 6]",
    "options": [
      "Ribosome",
      "Golgi apparatus",
      "Mitochondria",
      "Endoplasmic reticulum"
    ],
    "answer": "Golgi apparatus"
  },
  {
    "id": 10152,
    "uuid": "aca09fc3-b463-45ba-95cb-b4fee785f481",
    "topic": "biology",
    "created_at": "2025-09-29T15:33:36",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 2,
    "question": "What is the semi-fluid substance inside the cell that surrounds organelles? [Set 6]",
    "options": [
      "Cytoplasm",
      "Nucleus",
      "Chloroplast",
      "Mitochondria"
    ],
    "answer": "Cytoplasm"
  },
  {
    "id": 10153,
    "uuid": "fc153428-1cc7-4666-bf23-25f9ccb5b198",
    "topic": "biology",
    "created_at": "2025-09-29T15:33:36",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 3,
    "question": "Which part of the cell controls most activities and stores genetic information? [Set 6]",
    "options": [
      "Cytoplasm",
      "Nucleus",
      "Golgi apparatus",
      "Lysosome"
    ],
    "answer": "Nucleus"
  },
  {
    "id": 10154,
    "uuid": "159dd61f-210e-49e8-878c-37f800a1fda1",
    "topic": "biology",
    "created_at": "2025-09-29T15:33:36",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 4,
    "question": "Which organelle is responsible for breaking down waste and cellular debris? [Set 6]",
    "options": [
      "Mitochondria",
      "Lysosome",
      "Ribosome",
      "Chloroplast"
    ],
    "answer": "Lysosome"
  },
  {
    "id": 10155,
    "uuid": "a0f5059f-fb25-4ff6-aee5-72c28fc69028",
    "topic": "biology",
    "created_at": "2025-09-29T15:33:36",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 5,
    "question": "What is the powerhouse of the cell? [Set 6]",
    "options": [
      "Nucleus",
      "Mitochondria",
      "Ribosome",
      "Chloroplast"
    ],
    "answer": "Mitochondria"
  },
  {
    "id": 10156,
    "uuid": "279c18ec-c0bd-4534-8984-31d19f2c5ead",
    "topic": "biology",
    "created_at": "2025-09-29T15:33:36",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 6,
    "question": "Who is considered the father of modern genetics? [Set 6]",
    "options": [
      "Charles Darwin",
      "Gregor Mendel",
      "Louis Pasteur",
      "Robert Hooke"
    ],
    "answer": "Gregor Mendel"
  },
  {
    "id": 10157,
    "uuid": "984379b8-8d4f-4e4a-8841-3780c3e5590d",
    "topic": "biology",
    "created_at": "2025-09-29T15:33:36",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 7,
    "question": "Which base pairs with adenine in DNA? [Set 6]",
    "options": [
      "Guanine",
      "Cytosine",
      "Thymine",
      "Uracil"
    ],
    "answer": "Thymine"
  },
  {
    "id": 10158,
    "uuid": "eeea495a-1f94-4d76-98cc-72f03483f190",
    "topic": "biology",
    "created_at": "2025-09-29T15:33:36",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 8,
    "question": "What is the shape of DNA described as? [Set 6]",
    "options": [
      "Triple helix",
      "Double helix",
      "Single strand",
      "Spiral ladder"
    ],
    "answer": "Double helix"
  },
  {
    "id": 10159,
    "uuid": "36d866b7-912d-4808-aeca-c8f7c7f6e7b6",
    "topic": "biology",
    "created_at": "2025-09-29T15:33:36",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 9,
    "question": "Which type of RNA carries amino acids to ribosomes? [Set 6]",
    "options": [
      "mRNA",
      "tRNA",
      "rRNA",
      "snRNA"
    ],
    "answer": "tRNA"
  },
  {
    "id": 10160,
    "uuid": "7337e794-6253-4db1-a913-28113a32e8ce",
    "topic": "biology",
    "created_at": "2025-09-29T15:33:36",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 10,
    "question": "Which process creates gametes with half the number of chromosomes? [Set 6]",
    "options": [
      "Mitosis",
      "Meiosis",
      "Binary fission",
      "Budding"
    ],
    "answer": "Meiosis"
  },
  {
    "id": 10161,
    "uuid": "e75c0aef-3dec-4c80-9f4b-80f13ff876a7",
    "topic": "biology",
    "created_at": "2025-09-29T15:33:36",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "question": "Which part of the human brain controls balance and coordination? [Set 6]",
    "options": [
      "Cerebrum",
      "Cerebellum",
      "Medulla",
      "Hypothalamus"
    ],
    "answer": "Cerebellum"
  },
  {
    "id": 10162,
    "uuid": "5454a73f-f11a-4aa7-8d00-cb789a732aec",
    "topic": "biology",
    "created_at": "2025-09-29T15:33:36",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 2,
    "question": "Which blood vessels carry blood away from the heart? [Set 6]",
    "options": [
      "Arteries",
      "Veins",
      "Capillaries",
      "Venules"
    ],
    "answer": "Arteries"
  },
  {
    "id": 10163,
    "uuid": "5438e3a2-1ce8-48d9-8054-97f746c9bdba",
    "topic": "biology",
    "created_at": "2025-09-29T15:33:36",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 3,
    "question": "Which protein in red blood cells carries oxygen? [Set 6]",
    "options": [
      "Collagen",
      "Keratin",
      "Hemoglobin",
      "Albumin"
    ],
    "answer": "Hemoglobin"
  },
  {
    "id": 10164,
    "uuid": "ff89ef40-3072-4ed6-8c39-a2fd7109b8a6",
    "topic": "biology",
    "created_at": "2025-09-29T15:33:36",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 4,
    "question": "Which organ is primarily responsible for detoxification? [Set 6]",
    "options": [
      "Kidney",
      "Liver",
      "Lung",
      "Pancreas"
    ],
    "answer": "Liver"
  },
  {
    "id": 10165,
    "uuid": "a398ac0e-43e7-4684-9e62-6475a11ce499",
    "topic": "biology",
    "created_at": "2025-09-29T15:33:36",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 5,
    "question": "Which gland regulates metabolism through hormone secretion? [Set 6]",
    "options": [
      "Adrenal",
      "Thyroid",
      "Pituitary",
      "Pancreas"
    ],
    "answer": "Thyroid"
  },
  {
    "id": 10166,
    "uuid": "d559ff78-32a1-40ec-9f9d-ce16304e07c8",
    "topic": "biology",
    "created_at": "2025-09-29T15:33:36",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 6,
    "question": "What term describes organisms that produce their own food? [Set 6]",
    "options": [
      "Consumers",
      "Decomposers",
      "Producers",
      "Parasites"
    ],
    "answer": "Producers"
  },
  {
    "id": 10167,
    "uuid": "cfd7828d-08ae-47cf-b535-e9d43a48c070",
    "topic": "biology",
    "created_at": "2025-09-29T15:33:36",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 7,
    "question": "Which biome is characterized by permafrost? [Set 6]",
    "options": [
      "Desert",
      "Savanna",
      "Tundra",
      "Rainforest"
    ],
    "answer": "Tundra"
  },
  {
    "id": 10168,
    "uuid": "f3a61e90-6169-4941-a5d3-97dcfad374b0",
    "topic": "biology",
    "created_at": "2025-09-29T15:33:36",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 8,
    "question": "What is the main source of energy for almost all ecosystems? [Set 6]",
    "options": [
      "Wind",
      "Water",
      "Sunlight",
      "Soil"
    ],
    "answer": "Sunlight"
  },
  {
    "id": 10169,
    "uuid": "1be42c64-9e2b-45be-bb75-0238163e1692",
    "topic": "biology",
    "created_at": "2025-09-29T15:33:36",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 9,
    "question": "What is the symbiotic relationship where both species benefit? [Set 6]",
    "options": [
      "Parasitism",
      "Commensalism",
      "Mutualism",
      "Predation"
    ],
    "answer": "Mutualism"
  },
  {
    "id": 10170,
    "uuid": "bc7d2f2f-1d8a-417d-a511-c3daf563f4ed",
    "topic": "biology",
    "created_at": "2025-09-29T15:33:36",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 10,
    "question": "Which gas do plants absorb during photosynthesis? [Set 6]",
    "options": [
      "Oxygen",
      "Carbon dioxide",
      "Nitrogen",
      "Hydrogen"
    ],
    "answer": "Carbon dioxide"
  },
  {
    "id": 10171,
    "uuid": "fe950090-b3c9-40ac-8d1f-f4d9efdccc28",
    "topic": "biology",
    "created_at": "2025-09-29T15:33:36",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "question": "Who proposed the theory of natural selection? [Set 6]",
    "options": [
      "Gregor Mendel",
      "Louis Pasteur",
      "Charles Darwin",
      "Robert Hooke"
    ],
    "answer": "Charles Darwin"
  },
  {
    "id": 10172,
    "uuid": "c2f1ecfd-363e-4336-aee9-b115aebc83af",
    "topic": "biology",
    "created_at": "2025-09-29T15:33:36",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 2,
    "question": "What term describes structures that are similar due to shared ancestry? [Set 6]",
    "options": [
      "Analogous",
      "Homologous",
      "Vestigial",
      "Derived"
    ],
    "answer": "Homologous"
  },
  {
    "id": 10173,
    "uuid": "dd40c685-d155-4fb8-9bc9-92826af09e3c",
    "topic": "biology",
    "created_at": "2025-09-29T15:33:36",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 3,
    "question": "Which term refers to the random change in allele frequency in small populations? [Set 6]",
    "options": [
      "Natural selection",
      "Genetic drift",
      "Mutation",
      "Speciation"
    ],
    "answer": "Genetic drift"
  },
  {
    "id": 10174,
    "uuid": "7d26122f-b3b2-414e-b5d6-05f9d95e0b1a",
    "topic": "biology",
    "created_at": "2025-09-29T15:33:36",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 4,
    "question": "What is the preserved remains of ancient organisms called? [Set 6]",
    "options": [
      "Fossil",
      "Mineral",
      "Imprint",
      "Sediment"
    ],
    "answer": "Fossil"
  },
  {
    "id": 10175,
    "uuid": "be8e1325-2082-452e-846a-3c17c977050a",
    "topic": "biology",
    "created_at": "2025-09-29T15:33:36",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 5,
    "question": "Which islands did Darwin study finches that influenced his theory? [Set 6]",
    "options": [
      "Hawaiian",
      "Gal\u00e1pagos",
      "Philippines",
      "Caribbean"
    ],
    "answer": "Gal\u00e1pagos"
  },
  {
    "id": 10176,
    "uuid": "fdbbbfbc-9328-46f6-9557-1c8b0baf2570",
    "topic": "biology",
    "created_at": "2025-09-29T15:33:36",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 6,
    "question": "Which organelle is responsible for packaging and modifying proteins in eukaryotic cells? [Set 7]",
    "options": [
      "Ribosome",
      "Golgi apparatus",
      "Mitochondria",
      "Endoplasmic reticulum"
    ],
    "answer": "Golgi apparatus"
  },
  {
    "id": 10177,
    "uuid": "87176c62-82d4-43de-82de-eeccb2f3c9b0",
    "topic": "biology",
    "created_at": "2025-09-29T15:33:36",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 7,
    "question": "What is the semi-fluid substance inside the cell that surrounds organelles? [Set 7]",
    "options": [
      "Cytoplasm",
      "Nucleus",
      "Chloroplast",
      "Mitochondria"
    ],
    "answer": "Cytoplasm"
  },
  {
    "id": 10178,
    "uuid": "7d6312ac-74cd-4c48-aee3-9568a07e829d",
    "topic": "biology",
    "created_at": "2025-09-29T15:33:36",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 8,
    "question": "Which part of the cell controls most activities and stores genetic information? [Set 7]",
    "options": [
      "Cytoplasm",
      "Nucleus",
      "Golgi apparatus",
      "Lysosome"
    ],
    "answer": "Nucleus"
  },
  {
    "id": 10179,
    "uuid": "05d1f53c-9df0-4c51-b3c8-244d1f979257",
    "topic": "biology",
    "created_at": "2025-09-29T15:33:36",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 9,
    "question": "Which organelle is responsible for breaking down waste and cellular debris? [Set 7]",
    "options": [
      "Mitochondria",
      "Lysosome",
      "Ribosome",
      "Chloroplast"
    ],
    "answer": "Lysosome"
  },
  {
    "id": 10180,
    "uuid": "4265625a-56e3-4ea9-acc1-9dcb3d4aa631",
    "topic": "biology",
    "created_at": "2025-09-29T15:33:36",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 10,
    "question": "What is the powerhouse of the cell? [Set 7]",
    "options": [
      "Nucleus",
      "Mitochondria",
      "Ribosome",
      "Chloroplast"
    ],
    "answer": "Mitochondria"
  },
  {
    "id": 10181,
    "uuid": "48e9dded-2a23-43b2-99f6-b7a97d36d05a",
    "topic": "biology",
    "created_at": "2025-09-29T15:33:36",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "question": "Who is considered the father of modern genetics? [Set 7]",
    "options": [
      "Charles Darwin",
      "Gregor Mendel",
      "Louis Pasteur",
      "Robert Hooke"
    ],
    "answer": "Gregor Mendel"
  },
  {
    "id": 10182,
    "uuid": "c4fa7732-dc0e-4b35-95f3-eb4d2b65c178",
    "topic": "biology",
    "created_at": "2025-09-29T15:33:36",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 2,
    "question": "Which base pairs with adenine in DNA? [Set 7]",
    "options": [
      "Guanine",
      "Cytosine",
      "Thymine",
      "Uracil"
    ],
    "answer": "Thymine"
  },
  {
    "id": 10183,
    "uuid": "9676db29-ba61-4960-98bf-6fb9dc19f7bb",
    "topic": "biology",
    "created_at": "2025-09-29T15:33:36",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 3,
    "question": "What is the shape of DNA described as? [Set 7]",
    "options": [
      "Triple helix",
      "Double helix",
      "Single strand",
      "Spiral ladder"
    ],
    "answer": "Double helix"
  },
  {
    "id": 10184,
    "uuid": "3d5a62ce-cb2c-4d7b-902a-29f3078cd2aa",
    "topic": "biology",
    "created_at": "2025-09-29T15:33:36",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 4,
    "question": "Which type of RNA carries amino acids to ribosomes? [Set 7]",
    "options": [
      "mRNA",
      "tRNA",
      "rRNA",
      "snRNA"
    ],
    "answer": "tRNA"
  },
  {
    "id": 10185,
    "uuid": "656e5607-c070-40b2-8f7f-3f527e3f1a1b",
    "topic": "biology",
    "created_at": "2025-09-29T15:33:36",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 5,
    "question": "Which process creates gametes with half the number of chromosomes? [Set 7]",
    "options": [
      "Mitosis",
      "Meiosis",
      "Binary fission",
      "Budding"
    ],
    "answer": "Meiosis"
  },
  {
    "id": 10186,
    "uuid": "a0efb8b8-1f16-4f3a-9e20-0c170755765d",
    "topic": "biology",
    "created_at": "2025-09-29T15:33:36",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 6,
    "question": "Which part of the human brain controls balance and coordination? [Set 7]",
    "options": [
      "Cerebrum",
      "Cerebellum",
      "Medulla",
      "Hypothalamus"
    ],
    "answer": "Cerebellum"
  },
  {
    "id": 10187,
    "uuid": "c2d78bd0-1b74-4afb-a6fb-c50111d6a676",
    "topic": "biology",
    "created_at": "2025-09-29T15:33:36",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 7,
    "question": "Which blood vessels carry blood away from the heart? [Set 7]",
    "options": [
      "Arteries",
      "Veins",
      "Capillaries",
      "Venules"
    ],
    "answer": "Arteries"
  },
  {
    "id": 10188,
    "uuid": "793d647a-1762-426b-be30-f1208f32ff36",
    "topic": "biology",
    "created_at": "2025-09-29T15:33:36",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 8,
    "question": "Which protein in red blood cells carries oxygen? [Set 7]",
    "options": [
      "Collagen",
      "Keratin",
      "Hemoglobin",
      "Albumin"
    ],
    "answer": "Hemoglobin"
  },
  {
    "id": 10189,
    "uuid": "de20f9e4-e44a-4cb4-bf79-c3a7e3b0c67c",
    "topic": "biology",
    "created_at": "2025-09-29T15:33:36",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 9,
    "question": "Which organ is primarily responsible for detoxification? [Set 7]",
    "options": [
      "Kidney",
      "Liver",
      "Lung",
      "Pancreas"
    ],
    "answer": "Liver"
  },
  {
    "id": 10190,
    "uuid": "d202eb32-d1ba-439e-90e3-5664c59e5bca",
    "topic": "biology",
    "created_at": "2025-09-29T15:33:36",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 10,
    "question": "Which gland regulates metabolism through hormone secretion? [Set 7]",
    "options": [
      "Adrenal",
      "Thyroid",
      "Pituitary",
      "Pancreas"
    ],
    "answer": "Thyroid"
  },
  {
    "id": 10191,
    "uuid": "bfd694ac-3d04-4473-905c-7dac2a0eb3ac",
    "topic": "biology",
    "created_at": "2025-09-29T15:33:36",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "question": "What term describes organisms that produce their own food? [Set 7]",
    "options": [
      "Consumers",
      "Decomposers",
      "Producers",
      "Parasites"
    ],
    "answer": "Producers"
  },
  {
    "id": 10192,
    "uuid": "7228b26e-2c25-403a-8c5a-53d874dae104",
    "topic": "biology",
    "created_at": "2025-09-29T15:33:36",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 2,
    "question": "Which biome is characterized by permafrost? [Set 7]",
    "options": [
      "Desert",
      "Savanna",
      "Tundra",
      "Rainforest"
    ],
    "answer": "Tundra"
  },
  {
    "id": 10193,
    "uuid": "b4e6c5ea-9f44-43a5-9b40-dc40c22f2dff",
    "topic": "biology",
    "created_at": "2025-09-29T15:33:36",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 3,
    "question": "What is the main source of energy for almost all ecosystems? [Set 7]",
    "options": [
      "Wind",
      "Water",
      "Sunlight",
      "Soil"
    ],
    "answer": "Sunlight"
  },
  {
    "id": 10194,
    "uuid": "50243ec6-74b4-4328-aadf-3df4d9c455a7",
    "topic": "biology",
    "created_at": "2025-09-29T15:33:36",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 4,
    "question": "What is the symbiotic relationship where both species benefit? [Set 7]",
    "options": [
      "Parasitism",
      "Commensalism",
      "Mutualism",
      "Predation"
    ],
    "answer": "Mutualism"
  },
  {
    "id": 10195,
    "uuid": "20cb548d-fcb7-4536-b338-6a4c6fd0f327",
    "topic": "biology",
    "created_at": "2025-09-29T15:33:36",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 5,
    "question": "Which gas do plants absorb during photosynthesis? [Set 7]",
    "options": [
      "Oxygen",
      "Carbon dioxide",
      "Nitrogen",
      "Hydrogen"
    ],
    "answer": "Carbon dioxide"
  },
  {
    "id": 10196,
    "uuid": "9fd91d12-2d90-4237-9ad6-3ac820b79303",
    "topic": "biology",
    "created_at": "2025-09-29T15:33:36",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 6,
    "question": "Who proposed the theory of natural selection? [Set 7]",
    "options": [
      "Gregor Mendel",
      "Louis Pasteur",
      "Charles Darwin",
      "Robert Hooke"
    ],
    "answer": "Charles Darwin"
  },
  {
    "id": 10197,
    "uuid": "b9eabdc0-5feb-490d-b386-8eb8815e4da6",
    "topic": "biology",
    "created_at": "2025-09-29T15:33:36",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 7,
    "question": "What term describes structures that are similar due to shared ancestry? [Set 7]",
    "options": [
      "Analogous",
      "Homologous",
      "Vestigial",
      "Derived"
    ],
    "answer": "Homologous"
  },
  {
    "id": 10198,
    "uuid": "5a4dd1e2-6571-4be2-bbb1-71aa92c19622",
    "topic": "biology",
    "created_at": "2025-09-29T15:33:36",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 8,
    "question": "Which term refers to the random change in allele frequency in small populations? [Set 7]",
    "options": [
      "Natural selection",
      "Genetic drift",
      "Mutation",
      "Speciation"
    ],
    "answer": "Genetic drift"
  },
  {
    "id": 10199,
    "uuid": "2280d6d8-4518-49ba-bc42-b73e18ac477c",
    "topic": "biology",
    "created_at": "2025-09-29T15:33:36",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 9,
    "question": "What is the preserved remains of ancient organisms called? [Set 7]",
    "options": [
      "Fossil",
      "Mineral",
      "Imprint",
      "Sediment"
    ],
    "answer": "Fossil"
  },
  {
    "id": 10200,
    "uuid": "55c9fd54-0ef3-46d2-ab89-6dfc4144cf4b",
    "topic": "biology",
    "created_at": "2025-09-29T15:33:36",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 10,
    "question": "Which islands did Darwin study finches that influenced his theory? [Set 7]",
    "options": [
      "Hawaiian",
      "Gal\u00e1pagos",
      "Philippines",
      "Caribbean"
    ],
    "answer": "Gal\u00e1pagos"
  },
  {
    "id": 20001,
    "uuid": "4dfd6699-5a81-4b71-9fad-685681fdd4ef",
    "topic": "programming",
    "created_at": "2025-09-29T09:06:27",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "question": "Which hook is used for managing state in a functional React component?",
    "options": [
      "useEffect",
      "useState",
      "useReducer",
      "useMemo"
    ],
    "answer": "useState"
  },
  {
    "id": 20002,
    "uuid": "a607727d-41b1-4599-8b75-ed1f54977a5d",
    "topic": "programming",
    "created_at": "2025-09-29T09:06:27",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 2,
    "question": "What does the '?' symbol mean in a TypeScript interface property?",
    "options": [
      "Optional property",
      "Private property",
      "Nullable property",
      "Readonly property"
    ],
    "answer": "Optional property"
  },
  {
    "id": 20003,
    "uuid": "d2fefba7-dde5-4f51-9f87-71a7dbd23cb5",
    "topic": "programming",
    "created_at": "2025-09-29T09:06:27",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 3,
    "question": "Which component is used to make a scrollable list in React Native?",
    "options": [
      "FlatList",
      "ScrollView",
      "SectionList",
      "All of the above"
    ],
    "answer": "All of the above"
  },
  {
    "id": 20004,
    "uuid": "ee7b9eab-f5b9-40bd-9788-c82f8aa83587",
    "topic": "programming",
    "created_at": "2025-09-29T09:06:27",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 4,
    "question": "What does 'flex-direction: row;' do in CSS Flexbox?",
    "options": [
      "Stacks items vertically",
      "Stacks items horizontally",
      "Centers items",
      "Wraps items"
    ],
    "answer": "Stacks items horizontally"
  },
  {
    "id": 20005,
    "uuid": "afeba371-23d7-4553-8f0a-03a0a71d997d",
    "topic": "programming",
    "created_at": "2025-09-29T09:06:27",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 5,
    "question": "What does the <title> tag define in HTML?",
    "options": [
      "The main heading",
      "The page title in browser tab",
      "The body content",
      "The footer"
    ],
    "answer": "The page title in browser tab"
  },
  {
    "id": 20006,
    "uuid": "c5bfe98e-14c0-42f1-b614-7267278c3318",
    "topic": "programming",
    "created_at": "2025-09-29T09:06:27",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 6,
    "question": "Which of the following is a server-side scripting language?",
    "options": [
      "HTML",
      "CSS",
      "PHP",
      "React"
    ],
    "answer": "PHP"
  },
  {
    "id": 20007,
    "uuid": "e2ab8981-ae92-453a-93cf-3eaa20e83c47",
    "topic": "programming",
    "created_at": "2025-09-29T09:06:27",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 7,
    "question": "What is the output of len('Hello World') in Python?",
    "options": [
      "10",
      "11",
      "12",
      "13"
    ],
    "answer": "11"
  },
  {
    "id": 20008,
    "uuid": "4aa69e60-b518-40c4-bd79-14fe288d8fd9",
    "topic": "programming",
    "created_at": "2025-09-29T09:06:27",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 8,
    "question": "Which SQL command is used to extract data from a database?",
    "options": [
      "INSERT",
      "SELECT",
      "UPDATE",
      "DELETE"
    ],
    "answer": "SELECT"
  },
  {
    "id": 20009,
    "uuid": "499c6e31-52cf-4505-9d5c-9c67bca51031",
    "topic": "programming",
    "created_at": "2025-09-29T15:47:16",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "question": "Which hook is used for managing state in a functional React component?",
    "options": [
      "useEffect",
      "useState",
      "useReducer",
      "useMemo"
    ],
    "answer": "useState"
  },
  {
    "id": 20010,
    "uuid": "d9b39a3f-79fd-46b2-8a45-a819b890f15c",
    "topic": "programming",
    "created_at": "2025-09-29T15:47:16",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 2,
    "question": "What does the '?' symbol mean in a TypeScript interface property?",
    "options": [
      "Optional property",
      "Private property",
      "Nullable property",
      "Readonly property"
    ],
    "answer": "Optional property"
  },
  {
    "id": 20011,
    "uuid": "bf1a8eb3-35cc-43e1-8ecb-feecca922a56",
    "topic": "programming",
    "created_at": "2025-09-29T15:47:16",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 3,
    "question": "Which component is used to make a scrollable list in React Native?",
    "options": [
      "FlatList",
      "ScrollView",
      "SectionList",
      "All of the above"
    ],
    "answer": "All of the above"
  },
  {
    "id": 20012,
    "uuid": "bc1b1425-326e-4fe6-9129-37e880bcccf3",
    "topic": "programming",
    "created_at": "2025-09-29T15:47:16",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 4,
    "question": "What does 'flex-direction: row;' do in CSS Flexbox?",
    "options": [
      "Stacks items vertically",
      "Stacks items horizontally",
      "Centers items",
      "Wraps items"
    ],
    "answer": "Stacks items horizontally"
  },
  {
    "id": 20013,
    "uuid": "9c44b625-8fe2-4902-8e1e-00291e692617",
    "topic": "programming",
    "created_at": "2025-09-29T15:47:16",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 5,
    "question": "What does the <title> tag define in HTML?",
    "options": [
      "The main heading",
      "The page title in browser tab",
      "The body content",
      "The footer"
    ],
    "answer": "The page title in browser tab"
  },
  {
    "id": 20014,
    "uuid": "3e13cb8c-8889-4bdb-b7c4-8f8949f754bf",
    "topic": "programming",
    "created_at": "2025-09-29T15:47:16",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 6,
    "question": "Which of the following is a server-side scripting language?",
    "options": [
      "HTML",
      "CSS",
      "PHP",
      "React"
    ],
    "answer": "PHP"
  },
  {
    "id": 20015,
    "uuid": "180ce888-4454-435e-ab96-6c07ada80e46",
    "topic": "programming",
    "created_at": "2025-09-29T15:47:16",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 7,
    "question": "What is the output of len('Hello World') in Python?",
    "options": [
      "10",
      "11",
      "12",
      "13"
    ],
    "answer": "11"
  },
  {
    "id": 20016,
    "uuid": "79ee93f5-c9d2-421d-a33e-becd3fc254ca",
    "topic": "programming",
    "created_at": "2025-09-29T15:47:16",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 8,
    "question": "Which SQL command is used to extract data from a database?",
    "options": [
      "INSERT",
      "SELECT",
      "UPDATE",
      "DELETE"
    ],
    "answer": "SELECT"
  },
  {
    "id": 20017,
    "uuid": "268e6553-4451-4f8a-ae25-9abd184ae9df",
    "topic": "programming",
    "created_at": "2025-09-29T15:47:16",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 9,
    "question": "Which operator is used to compare equality in JavaScript?",
    "options": [
      "=",
      "==",
      "===",
      "!="
    ],
    "answer": "==="
  },
  {
    "id": 20018,
    "uuid": "0dcf4d69-59b1-4920-9611-6c3fdc407471",
    "topic": "programming",
    "created_at": "2025-09-29T15:47:16",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 10,
    "question": "What does JSON stand for?",
    "options": [
      "Java Source Object Notation",
      "JavaScript Object Notation",
      "Just Simple Object Notation",
      "Joined Syntax Object Notation"
    ],
    "answer": "JavaScript Object Notation"
  },
  {
    "id": 20019,
    "uuid": "f47a7d36-5d7c-443b-8cf8-e41925eed4a7",
    "topic": "programming",
    "created_at": "2025-09-29T15:47:16",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "question": "Which hook is used for managing state in a functional React component? [variant 1]",
    "options": [
      "useEffect",
      "useState",
      "useReducer",
      "useMemo"
    ],
    "answer": "useState"
  },
  {
    "id": 20020,
    "uuid": "b51ac342-5b15-4ceb-9e48-cc00392ca653",
    "topic": "programming",
    "created_at": "2025-09-29T15:47:16",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 2,
    "question": "What does the '?' symbol mean in a TypeScript interface property? [variant 1]",
    "options": [
      "Optional property",
      "Private property",
      "Nullable property",
      "Readonly property"
    ],
    "answer": "Optional property"
  },
  {
    "id": 20021,
    "uuid": "4e155e9f-448b-42c3-bcdc-f1ce1b7817c2",
    "topic": "programming",
    "created_at": "2025-09-29T15:47:16",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 3,
    "question": "Which component is used to make a scrollable list in React Native? [variant 1]",
    "options": [
      "FlatList",
      "ScrollView",
      "SectionList",
      "All of the above"
    ],
    "answer": "All of the above"
  },
  {
    "id": 20022,
    "uuid": "48b29c08-3257-4241-bb07-c1ffe261ce0b",
    "topic": "programming",
    "created_at": "2025-09-29T15:47:16",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 4,
    "question": "What does 'flex-direction: row;' do in CSS Flexbox? [variant 1]",
    "options": [
      "Stacks items vertically",
      "Stacks items horizontally",
      "Centers items",
      "Wraps items"
    ],
    "answer": "Stacks items horizontally"
  },
  {
    "id": 20023,
    "uuid": "b6f54f62-b700-4c58-beeb-8fe28f2f81fb",
    "topic": "programming",
    "created_at": "2025-09-29T15:47:16",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 5,
    "question": "What does the <title> tag define in HTML? [variant 1]",
    "options": [
      "The main heading",
      "The page title in browser tab",
      "The body content",
      "The footer"
    ],
    "answer": "The page title in browser tab"
  },
  {
    "id": 20024,
    "uuid": "4bd6ae51-7b5f-4fe9-91bb-e962d7298739",
    "topic": "programming",
    "created_at": "2025-09-29T15:47:16",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 6,
    "question": "Which of the following is a server-side scripting language? [variant 1]",
    "options": [
      "HTML",
      "CSS",
      "PHP",
      "React"
    ],
    "answer": "PHP"
  },
  {
    "id": 20025,
    "uuid": "2fceed57-65d5-42e9-a6f7-bbe2bf941858",
    "topic": "programming",
    "created_at": "2025-09-29T15:47:16",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 7,
    "question": "What is the output of len('Hello World') in Python? [variant 1]",
    "options": [
      "10",
      "11",
      "12",
      "13"
    ],
    "answer": "11"
  },
  {
    "id": 20026,
    "uuid": "f1a03266-a9df-44ac-bb77-6bf04d0d883b",
    "topic": "programming",
    "created_at": "2025-09-29T15:47:16",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 8,
    "question": "Which SQL command is used to extract data from a database? [variant 1]",
    "options": [
      "INSERT",
      "SELECT",
      "UPDATE",
      "DELETE"
    ],
    "answer": "SELECT"
  },
  {
    "id": 20027,
    "uuid": "3e72753f-0207-4532-b213-32533635662e",
    "topic": "programming",
    "created_at": "2025-09-29T15:47:16",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 9,
    "question": "Which operator is used to compare equality in JavaScript? [variant 1]",
    "options": [
      "=",
      "==",
      "===",
      "!="
    ],
    "answer": "==="
  },
  {
    "id": 20028,
    "uuid": "730a593b-47fe-4d54-b810-3337577e4ed0",
    "topic": "programming",
    "created_at": "2025-09-29T15:47:16",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 10,
    "question": "What does JSON stand for? [variant 1]",
    "options": [
      "Java Source Object Notation",
      "JavaScript Object Notation",
      "Just Simple Object Notation",
      "Joined Syntax Object Notation"
    ],
    "answer": "JavaScript Object Notation"
  },
  {
    "id": 20029,
    "uuid": "2ffa34f7-6cfc-4d53-b779-991898b2087b",
    "topic": "programming",
    "created_at": "2025-09-29T15:47:16",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "question": "Which hook is used for managing state in a functional React component? [variant 2]",
    "options": [
      "useEffect",
      "useState",
      "useReducer",
      "useMemo"
    ],
    "answer": "useState"
  },
  {
    "id": 20030,
    "uuid": "02a9f01e-3a03-4c4f-a480-601b59e017fa",
    "topic": "programming",
    "created_at": "2025-09-29T15:47:16",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 2,
    "question": "What does the '?' symbol mean in a TypeScript interface property? [variant 2]",
    "options": [
      "Optional property",
      "Private property",
      "Nullable property",
      "Readonly property"
    ],
    "answer": "Optional property"
  },
  {
    "id": 20031,
    "uuid": "99a421dc-0c6c-47f3-9769-224322e086f4",
    "topic": "programming",
    "created_at": "2025-09-29T15:47:16",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 3,
    "question": "Which component is used to make a scrollable list in React Native? [variant 2]",
    "options": [
      "FlatList",
      "ScrollView",
      "SectionList",
      "All of the above"
    ],
    "answer": "All of the above"
  },
  {
    "id": 20032,
    "uuid": "828698fa-b0c6-45c4-8f71-6ae0dca9ddbe",
    "topic": "programming",
    "created_at": "2025-09-29T15:47:16",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 4,
    "question": "What does 'flex-direction: row;' do in CSS Flexbox? [variant 2]",
    "options": [
      "Stacks items vertically",
      "Stacks items horizontally",
      "Centers items",
      "Wraps items"
    ],
    "answer": "Stacks items horizontally"
  },
  {
    "id": 20033,
    "uuid": "22e15fb2-3301-4c26-800c-09427f0af1c7",
    "topic": "programming",
    "created_at": "2025-09-29T15:47:16",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 5,
    "question": "What does the <title> tag define in HTML? [variant 2]",
    "options": [
      "The main heading",
      "The page title in browser tab",
      "The body content",
      "The footer"
    ],
    "answer": "The page title in browser tab"
  },
  {
    "id": 20034,
    "uuid": "1299768b-1c0d-4106-99dc-139da9222304",
    "topic": "programming",
    "created_at": "2025-09-29T15:47:16",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 6,
    "question": "Which of the following is a server-side scripting language? [variant 2]",
    "options": [
      "HTML",
      "CSS",
      "PHP",
      "React"
    ],
    "answer": "PHP"
  },
  {
    "id": 20035,
    "uuid": "2e6b9365-0fb0-4209-b300-e34fa6519eb8",
    "topic": "programming",
    "created_at": "2025-09-29T15:47:16",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 7,
    "question": "What is the output of len('Hello World') in Python? [variant 2]",
    "options": [
      "10",
      "11",
      "12",
      "13"
    ],
    "answer": "11"
  },
  {
    "id": 20036,
    "uuid": "2025e95b-49eb-477a-bcb9-281f8e37935c",
    "topic": "programming",
    "created_at": "2025-09-29T15:47:16",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 8,
    "question": "Which SQL command is used to extract data from a database? [variant 2]",
    "options": [
      "INSERT",
      "SELECT",
      "UPDATE",
      "DELETE"
    ],
    "answer": "SELECT"
  },
  {
    "id": 20037,
    "uuid": "a03ceae0-4cd9-48ab-836c-6cfc21727de6",
    "topic": "programming",
    "created_at": "2025-09-29T15:47:16",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 9,
    "question": "Which operator is used to compare equality in JavaScript? [variant 2]",
    "options": [
      "=",
      "==",
      "===",
      "!="
    ],
    "answer": "==="
  },
  {
    "id": 20038,
    "uuid": "fc90a16f-aa56-42f1-8f18-22a94bb789f7",
    "topic": "programming",
    "created_at": "2025-09-29T15:47:16",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 10,
    "question": "What does JSON stand for? [variant 2]",
    "options": [
      "Java Source Object Notation",
      "JavaScript Object Notation",
      "Just Simple Object Notation",
      "Joined Syntax Object Notation"
    ],
    "answer": "JavaScript Object Notation"
  },
  {
    "id": 20039,
    "uuid": "8c2c23ec-c055-4208-a8d3-16b940468a97",
    "topic": "programming",
    "created_at": "2025-09-29T15:47:16",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "question": "Which hook is used for managing state in a functional React component? [variant 3]",
    "options": [
      "useEffect",
      "useState",
      "useReducer",
      "useMemo"
    ],
    "answer": "useState"
  },
  {
    "id": 20040,
    "uuid": "66af2730-5d37-4a54-892a-867142220385",
    "topic": "programming",
    "created_at": "2025-09-29T15:47:16",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 2,
    "question": "What does the '?' symbol mean in a TypeScript interface property? [variant 3]",
    "options": [
      "Optional property",
      "Private property",
      "Nullable property",
      "Readonly property"
    ],
    "answer": "Optional property"
  },
  {
    "id": 20041,
    "uuid": "66fdfb90-34f3-42e5-9025-ed0c3d11018e",
    "topic": "programming",
    "created_at": "2025-09-29T15:47:16",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 3,
    "question": "Which component is used to make a scrollable list in React Native? [variant 3]",
    "options": [
      "FlatList",
      "ScrollView",
      "SectionList",
      "All of the above"
    ],
    "answer": "All of the above"
  },
  {
    "id": 20042,
    "uuid": "084cdb27-0e36-4868-b84f-ebfcd2a681bf",
    "topic": "programming",
    "created_at": "2025-09-29T15:47:16",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 4,
    "question": "What does 'flex-direction: row;' do in CSS Flexbox? [variant 3]",
    "options": [
      "Stacks items vertically",
      "Stacks items horizontally",
      "Centers items",
      "Wraps items"
    ],
    "answer": "Stacks items horizontally"
  },
  {
    "id": 20043,
    "uuid": "e6db5021-7514-41fa-b123-f7deb9683571",
    "topic": "programming",
    "created_at": "2025-09-29T15:47:16",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 5,
    "question": "What does the <title> tag define in HTML? [variant 3]",
    "options": [
      "The main heading",
      "The page title in browser tab",
      "The body content",
      "The footer"
    ],
    "answer": "The page title in browser tab"
  },
  {
    "id": 20044,
    "uuid": "23ea1f99-3ebf-4e56-a62d-2c9a9d6d4e6e",
    "topic": "programming",
    "created_at": "2025-09-29T15:47:16",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 6,
    "question": "Which of the following is a server-side scripting language? [variant 3]",
    "options": [
      "HTML",
      "CSS",
      "PHP",
      "React"
    ],
    "answer": "PHP"
  },
  {
    "id": 20045,
    "uuid": "87672abe-36ad-489e-b646-d0d356d2d4ce",
    "topic": "programming",
    "created_at": "2025-09-29T15:47:16",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 7,
    "question": "What is the output of len('Hello World') in Python? [variant 3]",
    "options": [
      "10",
      "11",
      "12",
      "13"
    ],
    "answer": "11"
  },
  {
    "id": 20046,
    "uuid": "e468adf4-803b-464e-ad7c-352a15d221e6",
    "topic": "programming",
    "created_at": "2025-09-29T15:47:16",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 8,
    "question": "Which SQL command is used to extract data from a database? [variant 3]",
    "options": [
      "INSERT",
      "SELECT",
      "UPDATE",
      "DELETE"
    ],
    "answer": "SELECT"
  },
  {
    "id": 20047,
    "uuid": "eeedae04-e39b-49d2-864c-4f86a0c4b1e7",
    "topic": "programming",
    "created_at": "2025-09-29T15:47:16",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 9,
    "question": "Which operator is used to compare equality in JavaScript? [variant 3]",
    "options": [
      "=",
      "==",
      "===",
      "!="
    ],
    "answer": "==="
  },
  {
    "id": 20048,
    "uuid": "f39699ff-968e-4cfb-8061-fef4eb6af647",
    "topic": "programming",
    "created_at": "2025-09-29T15:47:16",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 10,
    "question": "What does JSON stand for? [variant 3]",
    "options": [
      "Java Source Object Notation",
      "JavaScript Object Notation",
      "Just Simple Object Notation",
      "Joined Syntax Object Notation"
    ],
    "answer": "JavaScript Object Notation"
  },
  {
    "id": 20049,
    "uuid": "8f590f7f-109b-48c2-89fb-ca631f7d5197",
    "topic": "programming",
    "created_at": "2025-09-29T15:47:16",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "question": "Which hook is used for managing state in a functional React component? [variant 4]",
    "options": [
      "useEffect",
      "useState",
      "useReducer",
      "useMemo"
    ],
    "answer": "useState"
  },
  {
    "id": 20050,
    "uuid": "b0e612a2-2f25-4965-8515-28d6e31e9b93",
    "topic": "programming",
    "created_at": "2025-09-29T15:47:16",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 2,
    "question": "What does the '?' symbol mean in a TypeScript interface property? [variant 4]",
    "options": [
      "Optional property",
      "Private property",
      "Nullable property",
      "Readonly property"
    ],
    "answer": "Optional property"
  },
  {
    "id": 20051,
    "uuid": "b6f1135b-505d-4966-8838-9237590b2434",
    "topic": "programming",
    "created_at": "2025-09-29T15:47:16",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 3,
    "question": "Which component is used to make a scrollable list in React Native? [variant 4]",
    "options": [
      "FlatList",
      "ScrollView",
      "SectionList",
      "All of the above"
    ],
    "answer": "All of the above"
  },
  {
    "id": 20052,
    "uuid": "3ae51fe9-9bc4-4fcb-bda1-627e3a467a20",
    "topic": "programming",
    "created_at": "2025-09-29T15:47:16",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 4,
    "question": "What does 'flex-direction: row;' do in CSS Flexbox? [variant 4]",
    "options": [
      "Stacks items vertically",
      "Stacks items horizontally",
      "Centers items",
      "Wraps items"
    ],
    "answer": "Stacks items horizontally"
  },
  {
    "id": 20053,
    "uuid": "4b3b8735-953c-4ffa-bdfe-8c46b5f79b09",
    "topic": "programming",
    "created_at": "2025-09-29T15:47:16",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 5,
    "question": "What does the <title> tag define in HTML? [variant 4]",
    "options": [
      "The main heading",
      "The page title in browser tab",
      "The body content",
      "The footer"
    ],
    "answer": "The page title in browser tab"
  },
  {
    "id": 20054,
    "uuid": "a83dee61-5e17-4ea2-a86f-28cb7a9f5041",
    "topic": "programming",
    "created_at": "2025-09-29T15:47:16",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 6,
    "question": "Which of the following is a server-side scripting language? [variant 4]",
    "options": [
      "HTML",
      "CSS",
      "PHP",
      "React"
    ],
    "answer": "PHP"
  },
  {
    "id": 20055,
    "uuid": "c46e5f7f-9052-427a-bac1-24e5f833a8d2",
    "topic": "programming",
    "created_at": "2025-09-29T15:47:16",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 7,
    "question": "What is the output of len('Hello World') in Python? [variant 4]",
    "options": [
      "10",
      "11",
      "12",
      "13"
    ],
    "answer": "11"
  },
  {
    "id": 20056,
    "uuid": "8ebf8934-8314-45e9-8023-b0978459b306",
    "topic": "programming",
    "created_at": "2025-09-29T15:47:16",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 8,
    "question": "Which SQL command is used to extract data from a database? [variant 4]",
    "options": [
      "INSERT",
      "SELECT",
      "UPDATE",
      "DELETE"
    ],
    "answer": "SELECT"
  },
  {
    "id": 20057,
    "uuid": "de5cb597-b482-497c-b744-3d65dea83bff",
    "topic": "programming",
    "created_at": "2025-09-29T15:47:16",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 9,
    "question": "Which operator is used to compare equality in JavaScript? [variant 4]",
    "options": [
      "=",
      "==",
      "===",
      "!="
    ],
    "answer": "==="
  },
  {
    "id": 20058,
    "uuid": "8e1e775e-af2d-4d21-afc0-f67bc4978f9e",
    "topic": "programming",
    "created_at": "2025-09-29T15:47:16",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 10,
    "question": "What does JSON stand for? [variant 4]",
    "options": [
      "Java Source Object Notation",
      "JavaScript Object Notation",
      "Just Simple Object Notation",
      "Joined Syntax Object Notation"
    ],
    "answer": "JavaScript Object Notation"
  },
  {
    "id": 20059,
    "uuid": "f2cb7ea6-54b9-477e-ac22-8ef51f7efb00",
    "topic": "programming",
    "created_at": "2025-09-29T15:47:16",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "question": "Which hook is used for managing state in a functional React component? [variant 5]",
    "options": [
      "useEffect",
      "useState",
      "useReducer",
      "useMemo"
    ],
    "answer": "useState"
  },
  {
    "id": 20060,
    "uuid": "072fa09b-bc96-4408-941c-608f27b90088",
    "topic": "programming",
    "created_at": "2025-09-29T15:47:16",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 2,
    "question": "What does the '?' symbol mean in a TypeScript interface property? [variant 5]",
    "options": [
      "Optional property",
      "Private property",
      "Nullable property",
      "Readonly property"
    ],
    "answer": "Optional property"
  },
  {
    "id": 20061,
    "uuid": "680b8900-c830-4646-9b90-ee18bc77e111",
    "topic": "programming",
    "created_at": "2025-09-29T15:47:16",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 3,
    "question": "Which component is used to make a scrollable list in React Native? [variant 5]",
    "options": [
      "FlatList",
      "ScrollView",
      "SectionList",
      "All of the above"
    ],
    "answer": "All of the above"
  },
  {
    "id": 20062,
    "uuid": "e39d6419-82f3-4b9a-a98c-5c9697a7b50f",
    "topic": "programming",
    "created_at": "2025-09-29T15:47:16",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 4,
    "question": "What does 'flex-direction: row;' do in CSS Flexbox? [variant 5]",
    "options": [
      "Stacks items vertically",
      "Stacks items horizontally",
      "Centers items",
      "Wraps items"
    ],
    "answer": "Stacks items horizontally"
  },
  {
    "id": 20063,
    "uuid": "c4478185-38d7-46ba-a8eb-db3fc7e7308a",
    "topic": "programming",
    "created_at": "2025-09-29T15:47:16",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 5,
    "question": "What does the <title> tag define in HTML? [variant 5]",
    "options": [
      "The main heading",
      "The page title in browser tab",
      "The body content",
      "The footer"
    ],
    "answer": "The page title in browser tab"
  },
  {
    "id": 20064,
    "uuid": "af004bb6-8abb-4435-b0ef-ff12ed9a985e",
    "topic": "programming",
    "created_at": "2025-09-29T15:47:16",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 6,
    "question": "Which of the following is a server-side scripting language? [variant 5]",
    "options": [
      "HTML",
      "CSS",
      "PHP",
      "React"
    ],
    "answer": "PHP"
  },
  {
    "id": 20065,
    "uuid": "a38d9f44-d1b9-46d5-a75b-5d13a2d9c03c",
    "topic": "programming",
    "created_at": "2025-09-29T15:47:16",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 7,
    "question": "What is the output of len('Hello World') in Python? [variant 5]",
    "options": [
      "10",
      "11",
      "12",
      "13"
    ],
    "answer": "11"
  },
  {
    "id": 20066,
    "uuid": "22402a1e-6054-4f59-922f-9296a2616461",
    "topic": "programming",
    "created_at": "2025-09-29T15:47:16",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 8,
    "question": "Which SQL command is used to extract data from a database? [variant 5]",
    "options": [
      "INSERT",
      "SELECT",
      "UPDATE",
      "DELETE"
    ],
    "answer": "SELECT"
  },
  {
    "id": 20067,
    "uuid": "d68a52b3-2752-44c7-8022-1e3836cd46ad",
    "topic": "programming",
    "created_at": "2025-09-29T15:47:16",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 9,
    "question": "Which operator is used to compare equality in JavaScript? [variant 5]",
    "options": [
      "=",
      "==",
      "===",
      "!="
    ],
    "answer": "==="
  },
  {
    "id": 20068,
    "uuid": "90b3dc12-551d-40af-b3fb-172c3bb6dcf1",
    "topic": "programming",
    "created_at": "2025-09-29T15:47:16",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 10,
    "question": "What does JSON stand for? [variant 5]",
    "options": [
      "Java Source Object Notation",
      "JavaScript Object Notation",
      "Just Simple Object Notation",
      "Joined Syntax Object Notation"
    ],
    "answer": "JavaScript Object Notation"
  },
  {
    "id": 20069,
    "uuid": "93774960-59ba-4010-999f-815cb0dce5fd",
    "topic": "programming",
    "created_at": "2025-09-29T15:47:16",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "question": "Which hook is used for managing state in a functional React component? [variant 6]",
    "options": [
      "useEffect",
      "useState",
      "useReducer",
      "useMemo"
    ],
    "answer": "useState"
  },
  {
    "id": 20070,
    "uuid": "f58c0321-84c1-4ed4-a158-16284dd0ad5e",
    "topic": "programming",
    "created_at": "2025-09-29T15:47:16",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 2,
    "question": "What does the '?' symbol mean in a TypeScript interface property? [variant 6]",
    "options": [
      "Optional property",
      "Private property",
      "Nullable property",
      "Readonly property"
    ],
    "answer": "Optional property"
  },
  {
    "id": 20071,
    "uuid": "5b92615f-bb18-41dd-a418-5537948b9cac",
    "topic": "programming",
    "created_at": "2025-09-29T15:47:16",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 3,
    "question": "Which component is used to make a scrollable list in React Native? [variant 6]",
    "options": [
      "FlatList",
      "ScrollView",
      "SectionList",
      "All of the above"
    ],
    "answer": "All of the above"
  },
  {
    "id": 20072,
    "uuid": "5cadfaa0-e0ae-453f-95dd-a54792deffbd",
    "topic": "programming",
    "created_at": "2025-09-29T15:47:16",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 4,
    "question": "What does 'flex-direction: row;' do in CSS Flexbox? [variant 6]",
    "options": [
      "Stacks items vertically",
      "Stacks items horizontally",
      "Centers items",
      "Wraps items"
    ],
    "answer": "Stacks items horizontally"
  },
  {
    "id": 20073,
    "uuid": "b6e5c817-cb8b-44be-bd5c-5cfc27323836",
    "topic": "programming",
    "created_at": "2025-09-29T15:47:16",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 5,
    "question": "What does the <title> tag define in HTML? [variant 6]",
    "options": [
      "The main heading",
      "The page title in browser tab",
      "The body content",
      "The footer"
    ],
    "answer": "The page title in browser tab"
  },
  {
    "id": 20074,
    "uuid": "7e9329aa-ece4-42b9-b4c5-544e76770045",
    "topic": "programming",
    "created_at": "2025-09-29T15:47:16",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 6,
    "question": "Which of the following is a server-side scripting language? [variant 6]",
    "options": [
      "HTML",
      "CSS",
      "PHP",
      "React"
    ],
    "answer": "PHP"
  },
  {
    "id": 20075,
    "uuid": "faee8280-863d-4414-a7ae-0d5cbe0462c4",
    "topic": "programming",
    "created_at": "2025-09-29T15:47:16",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 7,
    "question": "What is the output of len('Hello World') in Python? [variant 6]",
    "options": [
      "10",
      "11",
      "12",
      "13"
    ],
    "answer": "11"
  },
  {
    "id": 20076,
    "uuid": "36f9a58f-d789-46da-9961-6731b4ae6b24",
    "topic": "programming",
    "created_at": "2025-09-29T15:47:16",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 8,
    "question": "Which SQL command is used to extract data from a database? [variant 6]",
    "options": [
      "INSERT",
      "SELECT",
      "UPDATE",
      "DELETE"
    ],
    "answer": "SELECT"
  },
  {
    "id": 20077,
    "uuid": "aee7ff96-e17d-4277-988f-ed50d25e7ac6",
    "topic": "programming",
    "created_at": "2025-09-29T15:47:16",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 9,
    "question": "Which operator is used to compare equality in JavaScript? [variant 6]",
    "options": [
      "=",
      "==",
      "===",
      "!="
    ],
    "answer": "==="
  },
  {
    "id": 20078,
    "uuid": "3d1dea69-5aa2-44fa-92d3-fb37d2a42c5b",
    "topic": "programming",
    "created_at": "2025-09-29T15:47:16",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 10,
    "question": "What does JSON stand for? [variant 6]",
    "options": [
      "Java Source Object Notation",
      "JavaScript Object Notation",
      "Just Simple Object Notation",
      "Joined Syntax Object Notation"
    ],
    "answer": "JavaScript Object Notation"
  },
  {
    "id": 20079,
    "uuid": "b8887b90-c81b-4ba2-9fb6-775974a8cd21",
    "topic": "programming",
    "created_at": "2025-09-29T15:47:16",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "question": "Which hook is used for managing state in a functional React component? [variant 7]",
    "options": [
      "useEffect",
      "useState",
      "useReducer",
      "useMemo"
    ],
    "answer": "useState"
  },
  {
    "id": 20080,
    "uuid": "fb72251b-dc9b-4952-b79d-837d107f2883",
    "topic": "programming",
    "created_at": "2025-09-29T15:47:16",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 2,
    "question": "What does the '?' symbol mean in a TypeScript interface property? [variant 7]",
    "options": [
      "Optional property",
      "Private property",
      "Nullable property",
      "Readonly property"
    ],
    "answer": "Optional property"
  },
  {
    "id": 20081,
    "uuid": "63a4611f-8dde-4ae6-b27c-081b3ea670a0",
    "topic": "programming",
    "created_at": "2025-09-29T15:47:16",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 3,
    "question": "Which component is used to make a scrollable list in React Native? [variant 7]",
    "options": [
      "FlatList",
      "ScrollView",
      "SectionList",
      "All of the above"
    ],
    "answer": "All of the above"
  },
  {
    "id": 20082,
    "uuid": "9e0d29c5-df50-46b0-94ac-338c2ec3adb4",
    "topic": "programming",
    "created_at": "2025-09-29T15:47:16",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 4,
    "question": "What does 'flex-direction: row;' do in CSS Flexbox? [variant 7]",
    "options": [
      "Stacks items vertically",
      "Stacks items horizontally",
      "Centers items",
      "Wraps items"
    ],
    "answer": "Stacks items horizontally"
  },
  {
    "id": 20083,
    "uuid": "aa91b03c-bf69-4ed0-9f7f-2cce01d6dd02",
    "topic": "programming",
    "created_at": "2025-09-29T15:47:16",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 5,
    "question": "What does the <title> tag define in HTML? [variant 7]",
    "options": [
      "The main heading",
      "The page title in browser tab",
      "The body content",
      "The footer"
    ],
    "answer": "The page title in browser tab"
  },
  {
    "id": 20084,
    "uuid": "1a0c15d4-9430-439f-af9e-4651dd1bff9f",
    "topic": "programming",
    "created_at": "2025-09-29T15:47:16",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 6,
    "question": "Which of the following is a server-side scripting language? [variant 7]",
    "options": [
      "HTML",
      "CSS",
      "PHP",
      "React"
    ],
    "answer": "PHP"
  },
  {
    "id": 20085,
    "uuid": "9bc7f212-44cd-4698-a07e-30eed1965cc9",
    "topic": "programming",
    "created_at": "2025-09-29T15:47:16",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 7,
    "question": "What is the output of len('Hello World') in Python? [variant 7]",
    "options": [
      "10",
      "11",
      "12",
      "13"
    ],
    "answer": "11"
  },
  {
    "id": 20086,
    "uuid": "d8b02d1b-c8ec-49fe-8751-b4a6a20c1f7d",
    "topic": "programming",
    "created_at": "2025-09-29T15:47:16",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 8,
    "question": "Which SQL command is used to extract data from a database? [variant 7]",
    "options": [
      "INSERT",
      "SELECT",
      "UPDATE",
      "DELETE"
    ],
    "answer": "SELECT"
  },
  {
    "id": 20087,
    "uuid": "4860a451-f86f-4be2-97ec-b839320fdd05",
    "topic": "programming",
    "created_at": "2025-09-29T15:47:16",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 9,
    "question": "Which operator is used to compare equality in JavaScript? [variant 7]",
    "options": [
      "=",
      "==",
      "===",
      "!="
    ],
    "answer": "==="
  },
  {
    "id": 20088,
    "uuid": "8ff0ddc9-560e-40c6-877d-cc372f44c9a5",
    "topic": "programming",
    "created_at": "2025-09-29T15:47:16",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 10,
    "question": "What does JSON stand for? [variant 7]",
    "options": [
      "Java Source Object Notation",
      "JavaScript Object Notation",
      "Just Simple Object Notation",
      "Joined Syntax Object Notation"
    ],
    "answer": "JavaScript Object Notation"
  },
  {
    "id": 20089,
    "uuid": "ec20521f-6f85-4ae2-a537-2966e99b2e19",
    "topic": "programming",
    "created_at": "2025-09-29T15:47:16",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "question": "Which hook is used for managing state in a functional React component? [variant 8]",
    "options": [
      "useEffect",
      "useState",
      "useReducer",
      "useMemo"
    ],
    "answer": "useState"
  },
  {
    "id": 20090,
    "uuid": "83f1a699-9748-41e6-874a-7bf218a57107",
    "topic": "programming",
    "created_at": "2025-09-29T15:47:16",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 2,
    "question": "What does the '?' symbol mean in a TypeScript interface property? [variant 8]",
    "options": [
      "Optional property",
      "Private property",
      "Nullable property",
      "Readonly property"
    ],
    "answer": "Optional property"
  },
  {
    "id": 20091,
    "uuid": "b831d714-9f9b-452a-8613-0de699f25a52",
    "topic": "programming",
    "created_at": "2025-09-29T15:47:16",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 3,
    "question": "Which component is used to make a scrollable list in React Native? [variant 8]",
    "options": [
      "FlatList",
      "ScrollView",
      "SectionList",
      "All of the above"
    ],
    "answer": "All of the above"
  },
  {
    "id": 20092,
    "uuid": "7d24574a-6663-4761-bdaa-aead02b4f55f",
    "topic": "programming",
    "created_at": "2025-09-29T15:47:16",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 4,
    "question": "What does 'flex-direction: row;' do in CSS Flexbox? [variant 8]",
    "options": [
      "Stacks items vertically",
      "Stacks items horizontally",
      "Centers items",
      "Wraps items"
    ],
    "answer": "Stacks items horizontally"
  },
  {
    "id": 20093,
    "uuid": "1946b336-67f4-4857-ac9c-25df0e8b1e8f",
    "topic": "programming",
    "created_at": "2025-09-29T15:47:16",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 5,
    "question": "What does the <title> tag define in HTML? [variant 8]",
    "options": [
      "The main heading",
      "The page title in browser tab",
      "The body content",
      "The footer"
    ],
    "answer": "The page title in browser tab"
  },
  {
    "id": 20094,
    "uuid": "9d93c097-eb6d-44ef-a410-9fe532b102aa",
    "topic": "programming",
    "created_at": "2025-09-29T15:47:16",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 6,
    "question": "Which of the following is a server-side scripting language? [variant 8]",
    "options": [
      "HTML",
      "CSS",
      "PHP",
      "React"
    ],
    "answer": "PHP"
  },
  {
    "id": 20095,
    "uuid": "88c67e39-ce21-4796-9336-f45101857657",
    "topic": "programming",
    "created_at": "2025-09-29T15:47:16",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 7,
    "question": "What is the output of len('Hello World') in Python? [variant 8]",
    "options": [
      "10",
      "11",
      "12",
      "13"
    ],
    "answer": "11"
  },
  {
    "id": 20096,
    "uuid": "056dec68-74b3-421c-bff2-7ffcdd10dc61",
    "topic": "programming",
    "created_at": "2025-09-29T15:47:16",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 8,
    "question": "Which SQL command is used to extract data from a database? [variant 8]",
    "options": [
      "INSERT",
      "SELECT",
      "UPDATE",
      "DELETE"
    ],
    "answer": "SELECT"
  },
  {
    "id": 20097,
    "uuid": "9b25ee32-c2ec-474e-bd5c-93b1b25aba50",
    "topic": "programming",
    "created_at": "2025-09-29T15:47:16",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 9,
    "question": "Which operator is used to compare equality in JavaScript? [variant 8]",
    "options": [
      "=",
      "==",
      "===",
      "!="
    ],
    "answer": "==="
  },
  {
    "id": 20098,
    "uuid": "c959b27d-9c22-4193-8ef6-863574f3b5d2",
    "topic": "programming",
    "created_at": "2025-09-29T15:47:16",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 10,
    "question": "What does JSON stand for? [variant 8]",
    "options": [
      "Java Source Object Notation",
      "JavaScript Object Notation",
      "Just Simple Object Notation",
      "Joined Syntax Object Notation"
    ],
    "answer": "JavaScript Object Notation"
  },
  {
    "id": 20099,
    "uuid": "f7465e99-b89f-4717-a026-94f29967ed0b",
    "topic": "programming",
    "created_at": "2025-09-29T15:47:16",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "question": "Which hook is used for managing state in a functional React component? [variant 9]",
    "options": [
      "useEffect",
      "useState",
      "useReducer",
      "useMemo"
    ],
    "answer": "useState"
  },
  {
    "id": 20100,
    "uuid": "14f07c31-69ae-4757-be9a-928265adb814",
    "topic": "programming",
    "created_at": "2025-09-29T15:47:16",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 2,
    "question": "What does the '?' symbol mean in a TypeScript interface property? [variant 9]",
    "options": [
      "Optional property",
      "Private property",
      "Nullable property",
      "Readonly property"
    ],
    "answer": "Optional property"
  },
  {
    "id": 20101,
    "uuid": "cfe5e741-b61e-4365-a6fd-f4d8ba30cdec",
    "topic": "programming",
    "created_at": "2025-09-29T15:47:16",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 3,
    "question": "Which component is used to make a scrollable list in React Native? [variant 9]",
    "options": [
      "FlatList",
      "ScrollView",
      "SectionList",
      "All of the above"
    ],
    "answer": "All of the above"
  },
  {
    "id": 20102,
    "uuid": "dfc5ded8-620a-4ef5-81b9-24af22b0c65d",
    "topic": "programming",
    "created_at": "2025-09-29T15:47:16",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 4,
    "question": "What does 'flex-direction: row;' do in CSS Flexbox? [variant 9]",
    "options": [
      "Stacks items vertically",
      "Stacks items horizontally",
      "Centers items",
      "Wraps items"
    ],
    "answer": "Stacks items horizontally"
  },
  {
    "id": 20103,
    "uuid": "5a578fbc-7048-49f5-a547-3c6d6ed5764e",
    "topic": "programming",
    "created_at": "2025-09-29T15:47:16",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 5,
    "question": "What does the <title> tag define in HTML? [variant 9]",
    "options": [
      "The main heading",
      "The page title in browser tab",
      "The body content",
      "The footer"
    ],
    "answer": "The page title in browser tab"
  },
  {
    "id": 20104,
    "uuid": "f6441657-6790-4074-9051-3e72c5d30dc8",
    "topic": "programming",
    "created_at": "2025-09-29T15:47:16",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 6,
    "question": "Which of the following is a server-side scripting language? [variant 9]",
    "options": [
      "HTML",
      "CSS",
      "PHP",
      "React"
    ],
    "answer": "PHP"
  },
  {
    "id": 20105,
    "uuid": "e68117ce-d5ec-442b-a4a1-9ac938a37c44",
    "topic": "programming",
    "created_at": "2025-09-29T15:47:16",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 7,
    "question": "What is the output of len('Hello World') in Python? [variant 9]",
    "options": [
      "10",
      "11",
      "12",
      "13"
    ],
    "answer": "11"
  },
  {
    "id": 20106,
    "uuid": "0d3b0e9b-7e53-4b14-ae5e-28633f734927",
    "topic": "programming",
    "created_at": "2025-09-29T15:47:16",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 8,
    "question": "Which SQL command is used to extract data from a database? [variant 9]",
    "options": [
      "INSERT",
      "SELECT",
      "UPDATE",
      "DELETE"
    ],
    "answer": "SELECT"
  },
  {
    "id": 20107,
    "uuid": "8e9abb94-1f10-4bfd-8539-829dddbe3067",
    "topic": "programming",
    "created_at": "2025-09-29T15:47:16",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 9,
    "question": "Which operator is used to compare equality in JavaScript? [variant 9]",
    "options": [
      "=",
      "==",
      "===",
      "!="
    ],
    "answer": "==="
  },
  {
    "id": 20108,
    "uuid": "25ce0fa8-5a9d-4d05-8691-c589b0f29bed",
    "topic": "programming",
    "created_at": "2025-09-29T15:47:16",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 10,
    "question": "What does JSON stand for? [variant 9]",
    "options": [
      "Java Source Object Notation",
      "JavaScript Object Notation",
      "Just Simple Object Notation",
      "Joined Syntax Object Notation"
    ],
    "answer": "JavaScript Object Notation"
  },
  {
    "id": 20109,
    "uuid": "36ac2024-3e99-4622-b912-465801631323",
    "topic": "programming",
    "created_at": "2025-09-29T15:47:16",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "question": "Which hook is used for managing state in a functional React component? [variant 10]",
    "options": [
      "useEffect",
      "useState",
      "useReducer",
      "useMemo"
    ],
    "answer": "useState"
  },
  {
    "id": 20110,
    "uuid": "e14a7396-0b36-43c5-8c1f-5855f174f9e0",
    "topic": "programming",
    "created_at": "2025-09-29T15:47:16",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 2,
    "question": "What does the '?' symbol mean in a TypeScript interface property? [variant 10]",
    "options": [
      "Optional property",
      "Private property",
      "Nullable property",
      "Readonly property"
    ],
    "answer": "Optional property"
  },
  {
    "id": 20111,
    "uuid": "9244ca85-9601-441e-b534-172d6f138c53",
    "topic": "programming",
    "created_at": "2025-09-29T15:47:16",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 3,
    "question": "Which component is used to make a scrollable list in React Native? [variant 10]",
    "options": [
      "FlatList",
      "ScrollView",
      "SectionList",
      "All of the above"
    ],
    "answer": "All of the above"
  },
  {
    "id": 20112,
    "uuid": "b8b6b8c8-fc7a-444b-878f-bafc5a263575",
    "topic": "programming",
    "created_at": "2025-09-29T15:47:16",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 4,
    "question": "What does 'flex-direction: row;' do in CSS Flexbox? [variant 10]",
    "options": [
      "Stacks items vertically",
      "Stacks items horizontally",
      "Centers items",
      "Wraps items"
    ],
    "answer": "Stacks items horizontally"
  },
  {
    "id": 20113,
    "uuid": "0cba1cae-ed24-452c-8551-ad7a8b5ee6dc",
    "topic": "programming",
    "created_at": "2025-09-29T15:47:16",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 5,
    "question": "What does the <title> tag define in HTML? [variant 10]",
    "options": [
      "The main heading",
      "The page title in browser tab",
      "The body content",
      "The footer"
    ],
    "answer": "The page title in browser tab"
  },
  {
    "id": 20114,
    "uuid": "eb4f7bb4-64ac-41a4-b869-dd49e0fadef9",
    "topic": "programming",
    "created_at": "2025-09-29T15:47:16",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 6,
    "question": "Which of the following is a server-side scripting language? [variant 10]",
    "options": [
      "HTML",
      "CSS",
      "PHP",
      "React"
    ],
    "answer": "PHP"
  },
  {
    "id": 20115,
    "uuid": "9b8a417f-dd99-4a66-b299-9edc91adece7",
    "topic": "programming",
    "created_at": "2025-09-29T15:47:16",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 7,
    "question": "What is the output of len('Hello World') in Python? [variant 10]",
    "options": [
      "10",
      "11",
      "12",
      "13"
    ],
    "answer": "11"
  },
  {
    "id": 20116,
    "uuid": "b6422479-737a-416f-b4b1-4ef6a0a1b061",
    "topic": "programming",
    "created_at": "2025-09-29T15:47:16",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 8,
    "question": "Which SQL command is used to extract data from a database? [variant 10]",
    "options": [
      "INSERT",
      "SELECT",
      "UPDATE",
      "DELETE"
    ],
    "answer": "SELECT"
  },
  {
    "id": 20117,
    "uuid": "282e363b-e8ef-4eda-bdae-9a2d34e38992",
    "topic": "programming",
    "created_at": "2025-09-29T15:47:16",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 9,
    "question": "Which operator is used to compare equality in JavaScript? [variant 10]",
    "options": [
      "=",
      "==",
      "===",
      "!="
    ],
    "answer": "==="
  },
  {
    "id": 20118,
    "uuid": "fd3db8ce-97fe-4928-9251-86d8d2bc6cea",
    "topic": "programming",
    "created_at": "2025-09-29T15:47:16",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 10,
    "question": "What does JSON stand for? [variant 10]",
    "options": [
      "Java Source Object Notation",
      "JavaScript Object Notation",
      "Just Simple Object Notation",
      "Joined Syntax Object Notation"
    ],
    "answer": "JavaScript Object Notation"
  },
  {
    "id": 20119,
    "uuid": "70a68958-8ba4-477f-97f4-98324faf3510",
    "topic": "programming",
    "created_at": "2025-09-29T15:47:16",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "question": "Which hook is used for managing state in a functional React component? [variant 11]",
    "options": [
      "useEffect",
      "useState",
      "useReducer",
      "useMemo"
    ],
    "answer": "useState"
  },
  {
    "id": 20120,
    "uuid": "6770b4ef-29e6-4468-a7f2-fa07f1a0371d",
    "topic": "programming",
    "created_at": "2025-09-29T15:47:16",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 2,
    "question": "What does the '?' symbol mean in a TypeScript interface property? [variant 11]",
    "options": [
      "Optional property",
      "Private property",
      "Nullable property",
      "Readonly property"
    ],
    "answer": "Optional property"
  },
  {
    "id": 20121,
    "uuid": "fab41671-3893-4cca-905e-b778375d7d48",
    "topic": "programming",
    "created_at": "2025-09-29T15:47:16",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 3,
    "question": "Which component is used to make a scrollable list in React Native? [variant 11]",
    "options": [
      "FlatList",
      "ScrollView",
      "SectionList",
      "All of the above"
    ],
    "answer": "All of the above"
  },
  {
    "id": 20122,
    "uuid": "f011792e-9740-4ca8-a798-78a9bce29860",
    "topic": "programming",
    "created_at": "2025-09-29T15:47:16",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 4,
    "question": "What does 'flex-direction: row;' do in CSS Flexbox? [variant 11]",
    "options": [
      "Stacks items vertically",
      "Stacks items horizontally",
      "Centers items",
      "Wraps items"
    ],
    "answer": "Stacks items horizontally"
  },
  {
    "id": 20123,
    "uuid": "853fc403-bb75-4fca-8269-472c503efb48",
    "topic": "programming",
    "created_at": "2025-09-29T15:47:16",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 5,
    "question": "What does the <title> tag define in HTML? [variant 11]",
    "options": [
      "The main heading",
      "The page title in browser tab",
      "The body content",
      "The footer"
    ],
    "answer": "The page title in browser tab"
  },
  {
    "id": 20124,
    "uuid": "b23b4dcc-db7d-444e-86e3-555dbd796f30",
    "topic": "programming",
    "created_at": "2025-09-29T15:47:16",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 6,
    "question": "Which of the following is a server-side scripting language? [variant 11]",
    "options": [
      "HTML",
      "CSS",
      "PHP",
      "React"
    ],
    "answer": "PHP"
  },
  {
    "id": 20125,
    "uuid": "15bf91e9-ad8f-4938-910d-ecc314c43dd7",
    "topic": "programming",
    "created_at": "2025-09-29T15:47:16",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 7,
    "question": "What is the output of len('Hello World') in Python? [variant 11]",
    "options": [
      "10",
      "11",
      "12",
      "13"
    ],
    "answer": "11"
  },
  {
    "id": 20126,
    "uuid": "249d6b2c-423d-452c-9cef-b07ed4360c2b",
    "topic": "programming",
    "created_at": "2025-09-29T15:47:16",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 8,
    "question": "Which SQL command is used to extract data from a database? [variant 11]",
    "options": [
      "INSERT",
      "SELECT",
      "UPDATE",
      "DELETE"
    ],
    "answer": "SELECT"
  },
  {
    "id": 20127,
    "uuid": "32d6d54a-75e2-4fd0-b593-776bbec03a1a",
    "topic": "programming",
    "created_at": "2025-09-29T15:47:16",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 9,
    "question": "Which operator is used to compare equality in JavaScript? [variant 11]",
    "options": [
      "=",
      "==",
      "===",
      "!="
    ],
    "answer": "==="
  },
  {
    "id": 20128,
    "uuid": "8415a103-2a89-4f26-bf09-6fb3f5b8abe5",
    "topic": "programming",
    "created_at": "2025-09-29T15:47:16",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 10,
    "question": "What does JSON stand for? [variant 11]",
    "options": [
      "Java Source Object Notation",
      "JavaScript Object Notation",
      "Just Simple Object Notation",
      "Joined Syntax Object Notation"
    ],
    "answer": "JavaScript Object Notation"
  },
  {
    "id": 20129,
    "uuid": "a4cf302b-4c0f-4531-bfe7-161dacaf776d",
    "topic": "programming",
    "created_at": "2025-09-29T15:47:16",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "question": "Which hook is used for managing state in a functional React component? [variant 12]",
    "options": [
      "useEffect",
      "useState",
      "useReducer",
      "useMemo"
    ],
    "answer": "useState"
  },
  {
    "id": 20130,
    "uuid": "91105240-dfb9-45d0-9ca9-41026369e9b9",
    "topic": "programming",
    "created_at": "2025-09-29T15:47:16",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 2,
    "question": "What does the '?' symbol mean in a TypeScript interface property? [variant 12]",
    "options": [
      "Optional property",
      "Private property",
      "Nullable property",
      "Readonly property"
    ],
    "answer": "Optional property"
  },
  {
    "id": 20131,
    "uuid": "a2fb2018-600f-4f17-ac97-9fe10334ee01",
    "topic": "programming",
    "created_at": "2025-09-29T15:47:16",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 3,
    "question": "Which component is used to make a scrollable list in React Native? [variant 12]",
    "options": [
      "FlatList",
      "ScrollView",
      "SectionList",
      "All of the above"
    ],
    "answer": "All of the above"
  },
  {
    "id": 20132,
    "uuid": "26ad515b-7dc5-45fa-bd66-4e4c38d0ef22",
    "topic": "programming",
    "created_at": "2025-09-29T15:47:16",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 4,
    "question": "What does 'flex-direction: row;' do in CSS Flexbox? [variant 12]",
    "options": [
      "Stacks items vertically",
      "Stacks items horizontally",
      "Centers items",
      "Wraps items"
    ],
    "answer": "Stacks items horizontally"
  },
  {
    "id": 20133,
    "uuid": "a68eece1-3fda-4dbc-85dd-0fb88c493c30",
    "topic": "programming",
    "created_at": "2025-09-29T15:47:16",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 5,
    "question": "What does the <title> tag define in HTML? [variant 12]",
    "options": [
      "The main heading",
      "The page title in browser tab",
      "The body content",
      "The footer"
    ],
    "answer": "The page title in browser tab"
  },
  {
    "id": 20134,
    "uuid": "5aa87099-c3bc-404d-b1c9-da386566d7ec",
    "topic": "programming",
    "created_at": "2025-09-29T15:47:16",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 6,
    "question": "Which of the following is a server-side scripting language? [variant 12]",
    "options": [
      "HTML",
      "CSS",
      "PHP",
      "React"
    ],
    "answer": "PHP"
  },
  {
    "id": 20135,
    "uuid": "fd975920-a666-4bd4-8c18-acc4a61dfc2c",
    "topic": "programming",
    "created_at": "2025-09-29T15:47:16",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 7,
    "question": "What is the output of len('Hello World') in Python? [variant 12]",
    "options": [
      "10",
      "11",
      "12",
      "13"
    ],
    "answer": "11"
  },
  {
    "id": 20136,
    "uuid": "ea9dabf5-6c9d-4a71-a048-97eee901753b",
    "topic": "programming",
    "created_at": "2025-09-29T15:47:16",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 8,
    "question": "Which SQL command is used to extract data from a database? [variant 12]",
    "options": [
      "INSERT",
      "SELECT",
      "UPDATE",
      "DELETE"
    ],
    "answer": "SELECT"
  },
  {
    "id": 20137,
    "uuid": "62349df6-dc01-42f6-a919-17403f76989b",
    "topic": "programming",
    "created_at": "2025-09-29T15:47:16",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 9,
    "question": "Which operator is used to compare equality in JavaScript? [variant 12]",
    "options": [
      "=",
      "==",
      "===",
      "!="
    ],
    "answer": "==="
  },
  {
    "id": 20138,
    "uuid": "c412ba9d-8b0a-42a7-9c23-feb9f8510955",
    "topic": "programming",
    "created_at": "2025-09-29T15:47:16",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 10,
    "question": "What does JSON stand for? [variant 12]",
    "options": [
      "Java Source Object Notation",
      "JavaScript Object Notation",
      "Just Simple Object Notation",
      "Joined Syntax Object Notation"
    ],
    "answer": "JavaScript Object Notation"
  },
  {
    "id": 20139,
    "uuid": "23d73be7-2190-4896-8694-b5201914d980",
    "topic": "programming",
    "created_at": "2025-09-29T15:47:16",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "question": "Which hook is used for managing state in a functional React component? [variant 13]",
    "options": [
      "useEffect",
      "useState",
      "useReducer",
      "useMemo"
    ],
    "answer": "useState"
  },
  {
    "id": 20140,
    "uuid": "5e81a1ae-39bd-4a42-9535-9aee46de855e",
    "topic": "programming",
    "created_at": "2025-09-29T15:47:16",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 2,
    "question": "What does the '?' symbol mean in a TypeScript interface property? [variant 13]",
    "options": [
      "Optional property",
      "Private property",
      "Nullable property",
      "Readonly property"
    ],
    "answer": "Optional property"
  },
  {
    "id": 20141,
    "uuid": "0e64a379-9d92-46a6-bf3d-f7c37ee75365",
    "topic": "programming",
    "created_at": "2025-09-29T15:47:16",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 3,
    "question": "Which component is used to make a scrollable list in React Native? [variant 13]",
    "options": [
      "FlatList",
      "ScrollView",
      "SectionList",
      "All of the above"
    ],
    "answer": "All of the above"
  },
  {
    "id": 20142,
    "uuid": "a44327c2-5458-4915-89d7-98ad70287239",
    "topic": "programming",
    "created_at": "2025-09-29T15:47:16",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 4,
    "question": "What does 'flex-direction: row;' do in CSS Flexbox? [variant 13]",
    "options": [
      "Stacks items vertically",
      "Stacks items horizontally",
      "Centers items",
      "Wraps items"
    ],
    "answer": "Stacks items horizontally"
  },
  {
    "id": 20143,
    "uuid": "52b6901b-6511-484f-9732-104aeb89d944",
    "topic": "programming",
    "created_at": "2025-09-29T15:47:16",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 5,
    "question": "What does the <title> tag define in HTML? [variant 13]",
    "options": [
      "The main heading",
      "The page title in browser tab",
      "The body content",
      "The footer"
    ],
    "answer": "The page title in browser tab"
  },
  {
    "id": 20144,
    "uuid": "12caa876-4920-4abf-8d2e-ce68269bb621",
    "topic": "programming",
    "created_at": "2025-09-29T15:47:16",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 6,
    "question": "Which of the following is a server-side scripting language? [variant 13]",
    "options": [
      "HTML",
      "CSS",
      "PHP",
      "React"
    ],
    "answer": "PHP"
  },
  {
    "id": 20145,
    "uuid": "d90ffc40-6ed5-4f4a-8a02-ab56b5c804f8",
    "topic": "programming",
    "created_at": "2025-09-29T15:47:16",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 7,
    "question": "What is the output of len('Hello World') in Python? [variant 13]",
    "options": [
      "10",
      "11",
      "12",
      "13"
    ],
    "answer": "11"
  },
  {
    "id": 20146,
    "uuid": "6840ad81-229c-4538-bc5a-68a16c5b8dee",
    "topic": "programming",
    "created_at": "2025-09-29T15:47:16",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 8,
    "question": "Which SQL command is used to extract data from a database? [variant 13]",
    "options": [
      "INSERT",
      "SELECT",
      "UPDATE",
      "DELETE"
    ],
    "answer": "SELECT"
  },
  {
    "id": 20147,
    "uuid": "949c3684-0e89-4d61-ae68-d6bf93c10cb3",
    "topic": "programming",
    "created_at": "2025-09-29T15:47:16",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 9,
    "question": "Which operator is used to compare equality in JavaScript? [variant 13]",
    "options": [
      "=",
      "==",
      "===",
      "!="
    ],
    "answer": "==="
  },
  {
    "id": 20148,
    "uuid": "30193b60-5c31-4e45-9096-2d0b7d8f2e99",
    "topic": "programming",
    "created_at": "2025-09-29T15:47:16",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 10,
    "question": "What does JSON stand for? [variant 13]",
    "options": [
      "Java Source Object Notation",
      "JavaScript Object Notation",
      "Just Simple Object Notation",
      "Joined Syntax Object Notation"
    ],
    "answer": "JavaScript Object Notation"
  },
  {
    "id": 20149,
    "uuid": "be8e4640-2697-402f-8ae6-91479ffd79cf",
    "topic": "programming",
    "created_at": "2025-09-29T15:47:16",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "question": "Which hook is used for managing state in a functional React component? [variant 14]",
    "options": [
      "useEffect",
      "useState",
      "useReducer",
      "useMemo"
    ],
    "answer": "useState"
  },
  {
    "id": 20150,
    "uuid": "a8bc942c-94e8-41f1-bc0e-1d17b38defe3",
    "topic": "programming",
    "created_at": "2025-09-29T15:47:16",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 2,
    "question": "What does the '?' symbol mean in a TypeScript interface property? [variant 14]",
    "options": [
      "Optional property",
      "Private property",
      "Nullable property",
      "Readonly property"
    ],
    "answer": "Optional property"
  },
  {
    "id": 20151,
    "uuid": "1b710008-902d-4e96-ba1a-dd02f6f59352",
    "topic": "programming",
    "created_at": "2025-09-29T15:47:16",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 3,
    "question": "Which component is used to make a scrollable list in React Native? [variant 14]",
    "options": [
      "FlatList",
      "ScrollView",
      "SectionList",
      "All of the above"
    ],
    "answer": "All of the above"
  },
  {
    "id": 20152,
    "uuid": "69f41331-3fa4-4c03-b793-683e0986c85f",
    "topic": "programming",
    "created_at": "2025-09-29T15:47:16",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 4,
    "question": "What does 'flex-direction: row;' do in CSS Flexbox? [variant 14]",
    "options": [
      "Stacks items vertically",
      "Stacks items horizontally",
      "Centers items",
      "Wraps items"
    ],
    "answer": "Stacks items horizontally"
  },
  {
    "id": 20153,
    "uuid": "8203d81c-4593-481a-bdc6-a0b5fc75534f",
    "topic": "programming",
    "created_at": "2025-09-29T15:47:16",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 5,
    "question": "What does the <title> tag define in HTML? [variant 14]",
    "options": [
      "The main heading",
      "The page title in browser tab",
      "The body content",
      "The footer"
    ],
    "answer": "The page title in browser tab"
  },
  {
    "id": 20154,
    "uuid": "b0df4b37-da73-45c2-91bc-4264f24959f0",
    "topic": "programming",
    "created_at": "2025-09-29T15:47:16",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 6,
    "question": "Which of the following is a server-side scripting language? [variant 14]",
    "options": [
      "HTML",
      "CSS",
      "PHP",
      "React"
    ],
    "answer": "PHP"
  },
  {
    "id": 20155,
    "uuid": "bd2f5113-7d95-43fc-acd1-6b0cbd8f3e85",
    "topic": "programming",
    "created_at": "2025-09-29T15:47:16",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 7,
    "question": "What is the output of len('Hello World') in Python? [variant 14]",
    "options": [
      "10",
      "11",
      "12",
      "13"
    ],
    "answer": "11"
  },
  {
    "id": 20156,
    "uuid": "c1352b21-88a6-4cda-abaf-e73a0788ea9e",
    "topic": "programming",
    "created_at": "2025-09-29T15:47:16",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 8,
    "question": "Which SQL command is used to extract data from a database? [variant 14]",
    "options": [
      "INSERT",
      "SELECT",
      "UPDATE",
      "DELETE"
    ],
    "answer": "SELECT"
  },
  {
    "id": 20157,
    "uuid": "5bc1556c-497a-44b0-b9c1-877933722dff",
    "topic": "programming",
    "created_at": "2025-09-29T15:47:16",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 9,
    "question": "Which operator is used to compare equality in JavaScript? [variant 14]",
    "options": [
      "=",
      "==",
      "===",
      "!="
    ],
    "answer": "==="
  },
  {
    "id": 20158,
    "uuid": "2f77efb4-7d7a-46db-b058-1fda3dd79144",
    "topic": "programming",
    "created_at": "2025-09-29T15:47:16",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 10,
    "question": "What does JSON stand for? [variant 14]",
    "options": [
      "Java Source Object Notation",
      "JavaScript Object Notation",
      "Just Simple Object Notation",
      "Joined Syntax Object Notation"
    ],
    "answer": "JavaScript Object Notation"
  },
  {
    "id": 20159,
    "uuid": "198c6726-6a52-468d-8a2a-02d5d1314f34",
    "topic": "oop",
    "created_at": "2025-09-29T15:47:16",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "question": "Which OOP principle allows using the same method name with different implementations?",
    "options": [
      "Inheritance",
      "Encapsulation",
      "Polymorphism",
      "Abstraction"
    ],
    "answer": "Polymorphism"
  },
  {
    "id": 20160,
    "uuid": "15f4db30-b9a8-4fd7-a0b3-ce473667daf4",
    "topic": "oop",
    "created_at": "2025-09-29T15:47:16",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 2,
    "question": "What is the process of hiding internal details and showing only necessary features?",
    "options": [
      "Inheritance",
      "Encapsulation",
      "Polymorphism",
      "Abstraction"
    ],
    "answer": "Abstraction"
  },
  {
    "id": 20161,
    "uuid": "499d2867-6b55-4ea0-83f2-3ce096e7334a",
    "topic": "oop",
    "created_at": "2025-09-29T15:47:16",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 3,
    "question": "Which OOP concept groups variables and methods into a single unit?",
    "options": [
      "Class",
      "Object",
      "Encapsulation",
      "Method"
    ],
    "answer": "Class"
  },
  {
    "id": 20162,
    "uuid": "1db3b9df-e774-449a-88a0-2f6235d1d168",
    "topic": "oop",
    "created_at": "2025-09-29T15:47:16",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 4,
    "question": "In OOP, what is an instance of a class called?",
    "options": [
      "Method",
      "Object",
      "Field",
      "Constructor"
    ],
    "answer": "Object"
  },
  {
    "id": 20163,
    "uuid": "31d939a3-b79a-416f-b0da-a1ad53eacd99",
    "topic": "oop",
    "created_at": "2025-09-29T15:47:16",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 5,
    "question": "Which OOP principle enables one class to derive properties from another?",
    "options": [
      "Polymorphism",
      "Inheritance",
      "Encapsulation",
      "Overloading"
    ],
    "answer": "Inheritance"
  },
  {
    "id": 20164,
    "uuid": "195f9fed-6018-412d-a4d6-9994f5f862cc",
    "topic": "oop",
    "created_at": "2025-09-29T15:47:16",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 6,
    "question": "What is it called when a subclass provides a specific implementation of a method already defined in its superclass?",
    "options": [
      "Overloading",
      "Overriding",
      "Inheritance",
      "Encapsulation"
    ],
    "answer": "Overriding"
  },
  {
    "id": 20165,
    "uuid": "d6f6fbdb-f45f-4ecf-8fb8-01b6f7d5c496",
    "topic": "oop",
    "created_at": "2025-09-29T15:47:16",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 7,
    "question": "Which keyword is used to create a new object in Java?",
    "options": [
      "create",
      "make",
      "new",
      "object"
    ],
    "answer": "new"
  },
  {
    "id": 20166,
    "uuid": "024e2a5f-0d8e-4278-be39-cf1430c64276",
    "topic": "oop",
    "created_at": "2025-09-29T15:47:16",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 8,
    "question": "Which access modifier in Java makes members accessible only within the same class?",
    "options": [
      "public",
      "protected",
      "private",
      "default"
    ],
    "answer": "private"
  },
  {
    "id": 20167,
    "uuid": "ad7bb182-4f02-4dcd-9934-b455def2ec4e",
    "topic": "oop",
    "created_at": "2025-09-29T15:47:16",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 9,
    "question": "Which OOP principle emphasizes 'one interface, many implementations'?",
    "options": [
      "Encapsulation",
      "Polymorphism",
      "Abstraction",
      "Inheritance"
    ],
    "answer": "Polymorphism"
  },
  {
    "id": 20168,
    "uuid": "850b3a8c-efce-431a-b466-ebe761cbce55",
    "topic": "oop",
    "created_at": "2025-09-29T15:47:16",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 10,
    "question": "Which special method in Python classes is used as a constructor?",
    "options": [
      "__create__",
      "__init__",
      "__start__",
      "__constructor__"
    ],
    "answer": "__init__"
  },
  {
    "id": 20169,
    "uuid": "99d00118-12fd-4820-b14a-d57a0c59c7ae",
    "topic": "oop",
    "created_at": "2025-09-29T15:47:16",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "question": "Which OOP principle allows using the same method name with different implementations? [variant 1]",
    "options": [
      "Inheritance",
      "Encapsulation",
      "Polymorphism",
      "Abstraction"
    ],
    "answer": "Polymorphism"
  },
  {
    "id": 20170,
    "uuid": "8af81c8c-0bea-4a72-ab2f-90272893b41d",
    "topic": "oop",
    "created_at": "2025-09-29T15:47:16",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 2,
    "question": "What is the process of hiding internal details and showing only necessary features? [variant 1]",
    "options": [
      "Inheritance",
      "Encapsulation",
      "Polymorphism",
      "Abstraction"
    ],
    "answer": "Abstraction"
  },
  {
    "id": 20171,
    "uuid": "2f0bd3c5-d0a2-4a68-8c43-70a0fece6fad",
    "topic": "oop",
    "created_at": "2025-09-29T15:47:16",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 3,
    "question": "Which OOP concept groups variables and methods into a single unit? [variant 1]",
    "options": [
      "Class",
      "Object",
      "Encapsulation",
      "Method"
    ],
    "answer": "Class"
  },
  {
    "id": 20172,
    "uuid": "dc514582-7bbb-481f-995e-d11cfa0d0cc4",
    "topic": "oop",
    "created_at": "2025-09-29T15:47:16",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 4,
    "question": "In OOP, what is an instance of a class called? [variant 1]",
    "options": [
      "Method",
      "Object",
      "Field",
      "Constructor"
    ],
    "answer": "Object"
  },
  {
    "id": 20173,
    "uuid": "54046812-eadc-40de-9502-0a07ff52f74f",
    "topic": "oop",
    "created_at": "2025-09-29T15:47:16",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 5,
    "question": "Which OOP principle enables one class to derive properties from another? [variant 1]",
    "options": [
      "Polymorphism",
      "Inheritance",
      "Encapsulation",
      "Overloading"
    ],
    "answer": "Inheritance"
  },
  {
    "id": 20174,
    "uuid": "a1f9197e-cd47-4f68-ac52-24ccbd5941b8",
    "topic": "oop",
    "created_at": "2025-09-29T15:47:16",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 6,
    "question": "What is it called when a subclass provides a specific implementation of a method already defined in its superclass? [variant 1]",
    "options": [
      "Overloading",
      "Overriding",
      "Inheritance",
      "Encapsulation"
    ],
    "answer": "Overriding"
  },
  {
    "id": 20175,
    "uuid": "03ef9202-9cf2-4fad-822e-a82166ace8fd",
    "topic": "oop",
    "created_at": "2025-09-29T15:47:16",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 7,
    "question": "Which keyword is used to create a new object in Java? [variant 1]",
    "options": [
      "create",
      "make",
      "new",
      "object"
    ],
    "answer": "new"
  },
  {
    "id": 20176,
    "uuid": "5bb08295-616d-473a-a80a-70195681b9a8",
    "topic": "oop",
    "created_at": "2025-09-29T15:47:16",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 8,
    "question": "Which access modifier in Java makes members accessible only within the same class? [variant 1]",
    "options": [
      "public",
      "protected",
      "private",
      "default"
    ],
    "answer": "private"
  },
  {
    "id": 20177,
    "uuid": "c5e9f75e-2e79-42a9-98b8-9c86ce32114e",
    "topic": "oop",
    "created_at": "2025-09-29T15:47:16",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 9,
    "question": "Which OOP principle emphasizes 'one interface, many implementations'? [variant 1]",
    "options": [
      "Encapsulation",
      "Polymorphism",
      "Abstraction",
      "Inheritance"
    ],
    "answer": "Polymorphism"
  },
  {
    "id": 20178,
    "uuid": "9947fa9d-fdba-4597-b716-79b046782a98",
    "topic": "oop",
    "created_at": "2025-09-29T15:47:16",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 10,
    "question": "Which special method in Python classes is used as a constructor? [variant 1]",
    "options": [
      "__create__",
      "__init__",
      "__start__",
      "__constructor__"
    ],
    "answer": "__init__"
  },
  {
    "id": 20179,
    "uuid": "d8cca536-1174-4014-aa4a-d451d861ab02",
    "topic": "oop",
    "created_at": "2025-09-29T15:47:16",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "question": "Which OOP principle allows using the same method name with different implementations? [variant 2]",
    "options": [
      "Inheritance",
      "Encapsulation",
      "Polymorphism",
      "Abstraction"
    ],
    "answer": "Polymorphism"
  },
  {
    "id": 20180,
    "uuid": "bd99ec81-972d-470e-8669-37fc5732f199",
    "topic": "oop",
    "created_at": "2025-09-29T15:47:16",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 2,
    "question": "What is the process of hiding internal details and showing only necessary features? [variant 2]",
    "options": [
      "Inheritance",
      "Encapsulation",
      "Polymorphism",
      "Abstraction"
    ],
    "answer": "Abstraction"
  },
  {
    "id": 20181,
    "uuid": "15b26199-5d60-4285-9c82-7eb930932fcf",
    "topic": "oop",
    "created_at": "2025-09-29T15:47:16",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 3,
    "question": "Which OOP concept groups variables and methods into a single unit? [variant 2]",
    "options": [
      "Class",
      "Object",
      "Encapsulation",
      "Method"
    ],
    "answer": "Class"
  },
  {
    "id": 20182,
    "uuid": "b0a3937a-0f00-430d-8bca-ac19fa242043",
    "topic": "oop",
    "created_at": "2025-09-29T15:47:16",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 4,
    "question": "In OOP, what is an instance of a class called? [variant 2]",
    "options": [
      "Method",
      "Object",
      "Field",
      "Constructor"
    ],
    "answer": "Object"
  },
  {
    "id": 20183,
    "uuid": "068c18a1-c5f8-4954-9ea3-9a923c1ef1b6",
    "topic": "oop",
    "created_at": "2025-09-29T15:47:16",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 5,
    "question": "Which OOP principle enables one class to derive properties from another? [variant 2]",
    "options": [
      "Polymorphism",
      "Inheritance",
      "Encapsulation",
      "Overloading"
    ],
    "answer": "Inheritance"
  },
  {
    "id": 20184,
    "uuid": "ccd606e3-61b1-48ff-b068-5d12ebce5581",
    "topic": "oop",
    "created_at": "2025-09-29T15:47:16",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 6,
    "question": "What is it called when a subclass provides a specific implementation of a method already defined in its superclass? [variant 2]",
    "options": [
      "Overloading",
      "Overriding",
      "Inheritance",
      "Encapsulation"
    ],
    "answer": "Overriding"
  },
  {
    "id": 20185,
    "uuid": "0b005640-a9f2-4eb5-88ca-40d87c470a68",
    "topic": "oop",
    "created_at": "2025-09-29T15:47:16",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 7,
    "question": "Which keyword is used to create a new object in Java? [variant 2]",
    "options": [
      "create",
      "make",
      "new",
      "object"
    ],
    "answer": "new"
  },
  {
    "id": 20186,
    "uuid": "6607c412-d2ea-42f4-be47-5e2be577d7a1",
    "topic": "oop",
    "created_at": "2025-09-29T15:47:16",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 8,
    "question": "Which access modifier in Java makes members accessible only within the same class? [variant 2]",
    "options": [
      "public",
      "protected",
      "private",
      "default"
    ],
    "answer": "private"
  },
  {
    "id": 20187,
    "uuid": "cbf2b64b-2cee-4654-b06d-454ab256e563",
    "topic": "oop",
    "created_at": "2025-09-29T15:47:16",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 9,
    "question": "Which OOP principle emphasizes 'one interface, many implementations'? [variant 2]",
    "options": [
      "Encapsulation",
      "Polymorphism",
      "Abstraction",
      "Inheritance"
    ],
    "answer": "Polymorphism"
  },
  {
    "id": 20188,
    "uuid": "9449ce85-ad54-4a93-a9be-3f16107aa7f7",
    "topic": "oop",
    "created_at": "2025-09-29T15:47:16",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 10,
    "question": "Which special method in Python classes is used as a constructor? [variant 2]",
    "options": [
      "__create__",
      "__init__",
      "__start__",
      "__constructor__"
    ],
    "answer": "__init__"
  },
  {
    "id": 20189,
    "uuid": "614e5330-e052-477a-af82-556c2f4beb35",
    "topic": "oop",
    "created_at": "2025-09-29T15:47:16",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "question": "Which OOP principle allows using the same method name with different implementations? [variant 3]",
    "options": [
      "Inheritance",
      "Encapsulation",
      "Polymorphism",
      "Abstraction"
    ],
    "answer": "Polymorphism"
  },
  {
    "id": 20190,
    "uuid": "803430be-380e-4037-a8f6-89c0f097b3a8",
    "topic": "oop",
    "created_at": "2025-09-29T15:47:16",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 2,
    "question": "What is the process of hiding internal details and showing only necessary features? [variant 3]",
    "options": [
      "Inheritance",
      "Encapsulation",
      "Polymorphism",
      "Abstraction"
    ],
    "answer": "Abstraction"
  },
  {
    "id": 20191,
    "uuid": "2142b470-25f0-4afc-bc78-f33bf3c5e4a9",
    "topic": "oop",
    "created_at": "2025-09-29T15:47:16",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 3,
    "question": "Which OOP concept groups variables and methods into a single unit? [variant 3]",
    "options": [
      "Class",
      "Object",
      "Encapsulation",
      "Method"
    ],
    "answer": "Class"
  },
  {
    "id": 20192,
    "uuid": "8ee61c9e-a5a5-45f3-bfa5-d3f7b8442901",
    "topic": "oop",
    "created_at": "2025-09-29T15:47:16",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 4,
    "question": "In OOP, what is an instance of a class called? [variant 3]",
    "options": [
      "Method",
      "Object",
      "Field",
      "Constructor"
    ],
    "answer": "Object"
  },
  {
    "id": 20193,
    "uuid": "4fc2cbe0-2d35-4887-8ca6-3961231f8d22",
    "topic": "oop",
    "created_at": "2025-09-29T15:47:16",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 5,
    "question": "Which OOP principle enables one class to derive properties from another? [variant 3]",
    "options": [
      "Polymorphism",
      "Inheritance",
      "Encapsulation",
      "Overloading"
    ],
    "answer": "Inheritance"
  },
  {
    "id": 20194,
    "uuid": "4d3b7d9f-8574-499b-9cc4-cf7dd4a2bbd2",
    "topic": "oop",
    "created_at": "2025-09-29T15:47:16",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 6,
    "question": "What is it called when a subclass provides a specific implementation of a method already defined in its superclass? [variant 3]",
    "options": [
      "Overloading",
      "Overriding",
      "Inheritance",
      "Encapsulation"
    ],
    "answer": "Overriding"
  },
  {
    "id": 20195,
    "uuid": "6c3f28da-4802-4fc3-859c-1d983a8def24",
    "topic": "oop",
    "created_at": "2025-09-29T15:47:16",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 7,
    "question": "Which keyword is used to create a new object in Java? [variant 3]",
    "options": [
      "create",
      "make",
      "new",
      "object"
    ],
    "answer": "new"
  },
  {
    "id": 20196,
    "uuid": "2e36d5ff-d131-4da7-bbb7-644a7f23c2e9",
    "topic": "oop",
    "created_at": "2025-09-29T15:47:16",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 8,
    "question": "Which access modifier in Java makes members accessible only within the same class? [variant 3]",
    "options": [
      "public",
      "protected",
      "private",
      "default"
    ],
    "answer": "private"
  },
  {
    "id": 20197,
    "uuid": "ba022c22-9f82-4399-8bb4-2ea4fb99d930",
    "topic": "oop",
    "created_at": "2025-09-29T15:47:16",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 9,
    "question": "Which OOP principle emphasizes 'one interface, many implementations'? [variant 3]",
    "options": [
      "Encapsulation",
      "Polymorphism",
      "Abstraction",
      "Inheritance"
    ],
    "answer": "Polymorphism"
  },
  {
    "id": 20198,
    "uuid": "fee15d8c-7db9-4193-86e1-319153639e4d",
    "topic": "oop",
    "created_at": "2025-09-29T15:47:16",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 10,
    "question": "Which special method in Python classes is used as a constructor? [variant 3]",
    "options": [
      "__create__",
      "__init__",
      "__start__",
      "__constructor__"
    ],
    "answer": "__init__"
  },
  {
    "id": 20199,
    "uuid": "db1af3e6-cc07-4635-9118-ceb7a366a5bc",
    "topic": "oop",
    "created_at": "2025-09-29T15:47:16",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 1,
    "question": "Which OOP principle allows using the same method name with different implementations? [variant 4]",
    "options": [
      "Inheritance",
      "Encapsulation",
      "Polymorphism",
      "Abstraction"
    ],
    "answer": "Polymorphism"
  },
  {
    "id": 20200,
    "uuid": "a261f934-25aa-4267-914c-ee66721c50ca",
    "topic": "oop",
    "created_at": "2025-09-29T15:47:16",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 2,
    "question": "What is the process of hiding internal details and showing only necessary features? [variant 4]",
    "options": [
      "Inheritance",
      "Encapsulation",
      "Polymorphism",
      "Abstraction"
    ],
    "answer": "Abstraction"
  },
  {
    "id": 20201,
    "uuid": "59990f25-753a-4b72-bd07-999c540889a6",
    "topic": "oop",
    "created_at": "2025-09-29T15:47:16",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 3,
    "question": "Which OOP concept groups variables and methods into a single unit? [variant 4]",
    "options": [
      "Class",
      "Object",
      "Encapsulation",
      "Method"
    ],
    "answer": "Class"
  },
  {
    "id": 20202,
    "uuid": "665b0c35-54f3-4b74-881b-326e8362d9e6",
    "topic": "oop",
    "created_at": "2025-09-29T15:47:16",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 4,
    "question": "In OOP, what is an instance of a class called? [variant 4]",
    "options": [
      "Method",
      "Object",
      "Field",
      "Constructor"
    ],
    "answer": "Object"
  },
  {
    "id": 20203,
    "uuid": "d4f93618-2c59-40c3-a907-6f7761d0b56a",
    "topic": "oop",
    "created_at": "2025-09-29T15:47:16",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 5,
    "question": "Which OOP principle enables one class to derive properties from another? [variant 4]",
    "options": [
      "Polymorphism",
      "Inheritance",
      "Encapsulation",
      "Overloading"
    ],
    "answer": "Inheritance"
  },
  {
    "id": 20204,
    "uuid": "b6ebf922-c7fc-43b5-9eb6-64de9c51b3f8",
    "topic": "oop",
    "created_at": "2025-09-29T15:47:16",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 6,
    "question": "What is it called when a subclass provides a specific implementation of a method already defined in its superclass? [variant 4]",
    "options": [
      "Overloading",
      "Overriding",
      "Inheritance",
      "Encapsulation"
    ],
    "answer": "Overriding"
  },
  {
    "id": 20205,
    "uuid": "e5f16869-30db-467e-8f97-2520f01f3d74",
    "topic": "oop",
    "created_at": "2025-09-29T15:47:16",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 7,
    "question": "Which keyword is used to create a new object in Java? [variant 4]",
    "options": [
      "create",
      "make",
      "new",
      "object"
    ],
    "answer": "new"
  },
  {
    "id": 20206,
    "uuid": "c1c5b0cc-001e-493a-ac4b-cfa5ccf9dcfb",
    "topic": "oop",
    "created_at": "2025-09-29T15:47:16",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 8,
    "question": "Which access modifier in Java makes members accessible only within the same class? [variant 4]",
    "options": [
      "public",
      "protected",
      "private",
      "default"
    ],
    "answer": "private"
  },
  {
    "id": 20207,
    "uuid": "1811935e-4271-4003-97a1-5e30467537ae",
    "topic": "oop",
    "created_at": "2025-09-29T15:47:16",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 9,
    "question": "Which OOP principle emphasizes 'one interface, many implementations'? [variant 4]",
    "options": [
      "Encapsulation",
      "Polymorphism",
      "Abstraction",
      "Inheritance"
    ],
    "answer": "Polymorphism"
  },
  {
    "id": 20208,
    "uuid": "511f5903-14ba-4691-a053-62d364cf0eae",
    "topic": "oop",
    "created_at": "2025-09-29T15:47:16",
    "type": "multiple_choice",
    "difficulty": 10,
    "question": "Which special method in Python classes is used as a constructor? [variant 4]",
    "options": [
      "__create__",
      "__init__",
      "__start__",
      "__constructor__"
    ],
    "answer": "__init__"
  }
]